<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Merged Feed</title><link>urn:merged-feed</link><description>Merged feed (100 items)</description><atom:link href="urn:merged-feed" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 09:43:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Prolific Russian ransomware operator living in California enjoys rare leniency awaiting trial</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/ianis-antropenko-zeppelin-ransomware-russian-cybercrime/</link><description>Prolific Russian ransomware operator living in California enjoys rare leniency awaiting trial  (Getty Images) Prolific Russian ransomware operator living in California enjoys rare leniency awaiting trial Ianis Aleksandrovich Antropenko allegedly committed ransomware attacks from 2018 to 2022. He’s been out on bond since his arrest almost a year ago, despite multiple run-ins with… By Matt Kapko</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/ianis-antropenko-zeppelin-ransomware-russian-cybercrime/</guid></item><item><title>Who needs VC funding? How cybercriminals spread their ill-gotten gains to everyday business ventures</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/what-cybercriminals-do-with-their-money-sophos/</link><description>Who needs VC funding? How cybercriminals spread their ill-gotten gains to everyday business ventures  Briefcase full of U.S. currency. (Getty Images) Who needs VC funding? How cybercriminals spread their ill-gotten gains to everyday business ventures The benefits of cybercrime aren't all flashy cars and watches. Sophos X-Ops researchers discovered it also fuels a far-reaching mix of ordinary, sometimes unremarkable businesses. By Matt Kapko</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/what-cybercriminals-do-with-their-money-sophos/</guid></item><item><title>Trump and others want to ramp up cyber offense, but there’s plenty of doubt about the idea</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/aggressive-cyber-offense-trump-administration-us-strategy-debate/</link><description>Trump and others want to ramp up cyber offense, but there’s plenty of doubt about the idea  Trump and others want to ramp up cyber offense, but there’s plenty of doubt about the idea By Tim Starks Mark Pomerleau</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/aggressive-cyber-offense-trump-administration-us-strategy-debate/</guid></item><item><title>Who is sending those scammy text messages about unpaid tolls?</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/toll-road-text-message-scam-swells-nationwide-how-to-stop/</link><description>Who is sending those scammy text messages about unpaid tolls?  Who is sending those scammy text messages about unpaid tolls? By Matt Kapko</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/toll-road-text-message-scam-swells-nationwide-how-to-stop/</guid></item><item><title>What defenders are learning from Black Basta’s leaked chat logs</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/black-basta-internal-chat-leak/</link><description>What defenders are learning from Black Basta’s leaked chat logs  What defenders are learning from Black Basta’s leaked chat logs By Matt Kapko</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/black-basta-internal-chat-leak/</guid></item><item><title>Despite challenges, the CVE program is a public-private partnership that has shown resilience</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/cve-program-history-mitre-nist-1999-2024/</link><description>Despite challenges, the CVE program is a public-private partnership that has shown resilience  Despite challenges, the CVE program is a public-private partnership that has shown resilience By Cynthia Brumfield</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/cve-program-history-mitre-nist-1999-2024/</guid></item><item><title>Legal barriers complicate justice for spyware victims</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/spyware-court-cases-nso-group-meta-whatsapp-apple/</link><description>Legal barriers complicate justice for spyware victims  Legal barriers complicate justice for spyware victims By Tim Starks</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/spyware-court-cases-nso-group-meta-whatsapp-apple/</guid></item><item><title>Why cyber modernization requires partners with technical plus acquisition expertise</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/why-cyber-modernization-requires-partners-with-technical-plus-acquisition-expertise/</link><description>Why cyber modernization requires partners with technical plus acquisition expertise  Image: Giannina Vera, Scoop News Group Why cyber modernization requires partners with technical plus acquisition expertise By Katie Baxter</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/why-cyber-modernization-requires-partners-with-technical-plus-acquisition-expertise/</guid></item><item><title>Why identity is the definitive cyber defense for federal agencies</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/why-identity-is-the-definitive-cyber-defense-for-federal-agencies/</link><description>Why identity is the definitive cyber defense for federal agencies  Image: Scoop News Group Why identity is the definitive cyber defense for federal agencies By Daniel Wilbricht</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/why-identity-is-the-definitive-cyber-defense-for-federal-agencies/</guid></item><item><title>Agencies push for digital transformation amid security challenges</title><link>https://fedscoop.com/agencies-push-for-digital-transformation-amid-security-challenges/</link><description>Agencies push for digital transformation amid security challenges  Agencies push for digital transformation amid security challenges By Scoop News Group</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://fedscoop.com/agencies-push-for-digital-transformation-amid-security-challenges/</guid></item><item><title>Want to scale cyber defenders? Focus on AI-enabled security and organization-wide training</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/want-to-scale-cyber-defenders-focus-on-ai-enabled-security-and-organization-wide-training/</link><description>Want to scale cyber defenders? Focus on AI-enabled security and organization-wide training  Want to scale cyber defenders? Focus on AI-enabled security and organization-wide training By Jay Bhalodia</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/want-to-scale-cyber-defenders-focus-on-ai-enabled-security-and-organization-wide-training/</guid></item><item><title>Why blocking cyber threats is no longer enough</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/video/why-blocking-cyber-threats-is-no-longer-enough/</link><description>Why blocking cyber threats is no longer enough  Why blocking cyber threats is no longer enough By Scoop News Group</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/video/why-blocking-cyber-threats-is-no-longer-enough/</guid></item><item><title>To Catch a Thief: China’s Rise to Cyber Supremacy</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/video/to-catch-a-thief-chinas-rise-to-cyber-supremacy/</link><description>To Catch a Thief: China’s Rise to Cyber Supremacy  To Catch a Thief: China’s Rise to Cyber Supremacy By Scoop News Group</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/video/to-catch-a-thief-chinas-rise-to-cyber-supremacy/</guid></item><item><title>Red Hat’s Adam Clater on navigating zero trust’s unknowns</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/video/red-hats-adam-clater-on-navigating-zero-trusts-unknowns/</link><description>Red Hat’s Adam Clater on navigating zero trust’s unknowns  Red Hat’s Adam Clater on navigating zero trust’s unknowns By Scoop News Group</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/video/red-hats-adam-clater-on-navigating-zero-trusts-unknowns/</guid></item><item><title>Datadog’s Brian Mikkelsen on unifying zero-trust security efforts</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/video/datadogs-brian-mikkelsen-on-unifying-zero-trust-security-efforts/</link><description>Datadog’s Brian Mikkelsen on unifying zero-trust security efforts  Datadog’s Brian Mikkelsen on unifying zero-trust security efforts By Scoop News Group</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/video/datadogs-brian-mikkelsen-on-unifying-zero-trust-security-efforts/</guid></item><item><title>Phosphorus’ Sonu Shankar on IoT Vulnerabilities and Salt Typhoon Tactics</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/radio/phosphorus-sonu-shankar-iot-vulnerabilities-salt-typhoon-npm-scare/</link><description>Phosphorus’ Sonu Shankar on IoT Vulnerabilities and Salt Typhoon Tactics  Phosphorus’ Sonu Shankar on IoT Vulnerabilities and Salt Typhoon Tactics By CyberScoop Staff</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/radio/phosphorus-sonu-shankar-iot-vulnerabilities-salt-typhoon-npm-scare/</guid></item><item><title>Halcyon’s Cynthia Kaiser on the state of ransomware</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/radio/cisa-2015-lapse-kevin-hanes-ceo-reveal-security-machine-identities-2/</link><description>Halcyon’s Cynthia Kaiser on the state of ransomware  Halcyon’s Cynthia Kaiser on the state of ransomware By CyberScoop Staff</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/radio/cisa-2015-lapse-kevin-hanes-ceo-reveal-security-machine-identities-2/</guid></item><item><title>What happens if CISA 2015 lapses?</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/radio/cisa-2015-lapse-kevin-hanes-ceo-reveal-security-machine-identities/</link><description>What happens if CISA 2015 lapses?  What happens if CISA 2015 lapses? By CyberScoop Staff</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/radio/cisa-2015-lapse-kevin-hanes-ceo-reveal-security-machine-identities/</guid></item><item><title>Dave DeWalt on how to get a board to buy in on cybersecurity</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/radio/dave-dewalt-nightdragon-board-buy-in-cybersecurity/</link><description>Dave DeWalt on how to get a board to buy in on cybersecurity  Dave DeWalt on how to get a board to buy in on cybersecurity By CyberScoop Staff</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/radio/dave-dewalt-nightdragon-board-buy-in-cybersecurity/</guid></item><item><title>Critical infrastructure security tech needs to be as good as our smartphones, top NSC cyber official says</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/alexei-bulazel-critical-infrastructure-security-tech-needs-to-be-as-good-as-our-smartphones/</link><description>Critical infrastructure security tech needs to be as good as our smartphones, top NSC cyber official says  Bulazel mentioned the energy sector in particular, given the potential for hackers to turn off the power in the United States. It’s a sector that relies in large measure on supervisory control and data acquisition (SCADA) systems to monitor and control industrial processes. (Image Credit: AndreyPopov via Getty Images) Critical infrastructure security tech needs to be as good as our smartphones, top NSC cyber official says</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/alexei-bulazel-critical-infrastructure-security-tech-needs-to-be-as-good-as-our-smartphones/</guid></item><item><title>Microsoft Patch Tuesday addresses 81 vulnerabilities, none actively exploited</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/microsoft-patch-tuesday-september-2025/</link><description>Microsoft Patch Tuesday addresses 81 vulnerabilities, none actively exploited  A sign is seen at Microsoft headquarters on July 3, 2024, in Redmond, Washington. (David Ryder/Getty Images) Microsoft Patch Tuesday addresses 81 vulnerabilities, none actively exploited</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/microsoft-patch-tuesday-september-2025/</guid></item><item><title>U.S. indicts Ukrainian national for hundreds of ransomware attacks using multiple variants</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/nefilim-ransomware-indictment-volodymyr-tymoshchuk-department-of-justice/</link><description>U.S. indicts Ukrainian national for hundreds of ransomware attacks using multiple variants  A seal reading “Department of Justice Federal Bureau of Investigation” is displayed on the J. Edgar Hoover FBI building in Washington, DC, o August 9, 2022. (Photo by STEFANI REYNOLDS/AFP via Getty Images) U.S. indicts Ukrainian national for hundreds of ransomware attacks using multiple variants</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/nefilim-ransomware-indictment-volodymyr-tymoshchuk-department-of-justice/</guid></item><item><title>Former WhatsApp security manager sues company for privacy violations, professional retaliation</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/meta-whatsapp-lawsuit-privacy-violations-relatiation/</link><description>Former WhatsApp security manager sues company for privacy violations, professional retaliation  A picture taken on March 23, 2022 in Moscow shows the US instant messaging software Whatsapp logo on a smartphone screen.(Photo by -/AFP via Getty Images) Former WhatsApp security manager sues company for privacy violations, professional retaliation</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/meta-whatsapp-lawsuit-privacy-violations-relatiation/</guid></item><item><title>National cyber director: U.S. strategy needs to shift cyber risk from Americans to its adversaries</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/us-cybersecurity-strategy-sean-cairncross-shift-risk-china-trump-biden-cisa/</link><description>National cyber director: U.S. strategy needs to shift cyber risk from Americans to its adversaries  Then-Millenium challenge corporation CEO Sean Cairncross speaks during a ceremony on Aug. 5, 2019 at the presidential palace in Abidjan. (Photo by ISSOUF SANOGO / AFP)        (Photo credit should read ISSOUF SANOGO/AFP via Getty Images) National cyber director: U.S. strategy needs to shift cyber risk from Americans to its adversaries</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/us-cybersecurity-strategy-sean-cairncross-shift-risk-china-trump-biden-cisa/</guid></item><item><title>Mitsubishi Electric to acquire Nozomi Networks in $1 billion deal</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/nozomi-networks-mitsubishi-electric-acquisition-ot-ics-cybersecurity/</link><description>Mitsubishi Electric to acquire Nozomi Networks in $1 billion deal  Mitsubishi Electric’s Nagoya Works factory in Japan. (Wikipedia user 円周率３パーセン / CC-BY-4.0) Mitsubishi Electric to acquire Nozomi Networks in $1 billion deal</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/nozomi-networks-mitsubishi-electric-acquisition-ot-ics-cybersecurity/</guid></item><item><title>Treasury Department targets Southeast Asia scam hubs with sanctions</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/southeast-asia-scam-hubs-sanctions/</link><description>Treasury Department targets Southeast Asia scam hubs with sanctions  The sun flares over the headquarters of the U.S. Treasury on Jan. 3, 2024, in Washington, D.C. 
(Photo by J. David Ake/Getty Images) Treasury Department targets Southeast Asia scam hubs with sanctions</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/southeast-asia-scam-hubs-sanctions/</guid></item><item><title>Salesloft Drift security incident started with undetected GitHub access</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/salesloft-drift-attack-root-cause-github-oauth/</link><description>Salesloft Drift security incident started with undetected GitHub access  Salesloft confirmed the impact is much more severe and widespread.  (imageBROKER/Timon Schneider/Alamy) Salesloft Drift security incident started with undetected GitHub access</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/salesloft-drift-attack-root-cause-github-oauth/</guid></item><item><title>CISA pushes final cyber incident reporting rule to May 2026</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/cisa-pushes-final-cyber-incident-reporting-rule-to-may-2026/</link><description>CISA pushes final cyber incident reporting rule to May 2026  Image showing the Colonial Pipeline Houston Station facility in Pasadena, Texas (Photo by Francois PICARD / AFP) (Photo by FRANCOIS PICARD/AFP via Getty Images) CISA pushes final cyber incident reporting rule to May 2026</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/cisa-pushes-final-cyber-incident-reporting-rule-to-may-2026/</guid></item><item><title>Supreme Court blocks FTC commissioner Slaughter’s reinstatement</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/ftc-slaughter-reinstatement-blocked-by-supreme-court/</link><description>Supreme Court blocks FTC commissioner Slaughter’s reinstatement  The front of the U.S. Supreme Court building is seen after sunset on June 24, 2024, in Washington, DC. (Photo by J. David Ake/Getty Images) Supreme Court blocks FTC commissioner Slaughter’s reinstatement</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/ftc-slaughter-reinstatement-blocked-by-supreme-court/</guid></item><item><title>NYU team behind AI-powered malware dubbed ‘PromptLock’</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/ai-ransomware-promptlock-nyu-behind-code-discovered-by-security-researchers/</link><description>NYU team behind AI-powered malware dubbed ‘PromptLock’  (Getty Images) NYU team behind AI-powered malware dubbed ‘PromptLock’</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/ai-ransomware-promptlock-nyu-behind-code-discovered-by-security-researchers/</guid></item><item><title>AI can help track an ever-growing body of vulnerabilities, CISA official says</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/ai-can-help-track-an-ever-growing-body-of-vulnerabilities-cisa-official-says/</link><description>AI can help track an ever-growing body of vulnerabilities, CISA official says  From left, Tanium’s Sam Kinch, GDIT’s Matt Hayden, the Commerce Department’s Ryan Higgins, and CISA’s Chris Butera take part in a panel discussion at a GDIT event on Sept. 4, 2025 in Washington, D.C. (Scoop News Group photo) AI can help track an ever-growing body of vulnerabilities, CISA official says</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/ai-can-help-track-an-ever-growing-body-of-vulnerabilities-cisa-official-says/</guid></item><item><title>Sitecore zero-day vulnerability springs up from exposed machine key</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/sitecore-zero-day-vulnerability/</link><description>Sitecore zero-day vulnerability springs up from exposed machine key  (Getty Images) Sitecore zero-day vulnerability springs up from exposed machine key</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/sitecore-zero-day-vulnerability/</guid></item><item><title>Bridging Silos: Streamlining Direct And Programmatic Advertising At U.S. News &amp; World Report</title><link>https://admonsters.com/bridging-silos-streamlining-direct-and-programmatic-advertising-at-u-s-news-world-report/</link><description>Bridging Silos: Streamlining Direct And Programmatic Advertising At U.S. News &amp; World Report  Bridging Silos: Streamlining Direct And Programmatic Advertising At U.S. News &amp; World Report</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/bridging-silos-streamlining-direct-and-programmatic-advertising-at-u-s-news-world-report/</guid></item><item><title>No title</title><link>https://admonsters.com/publisher-blues-10-bold-moves-to-rewire-news-for-the-next-decade/</link><description>In 2000, US newspapers made more money than ever before, but have since then lost about two-thirds of that revenue. Here are 10 big, bankable ideas for turning the page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/publisher-blues-10-bold-moves-to-rewire-news-for-the-next-decade/</guid></item><item><title>No title</title><link>https://admonsters.com/publishers-vs-ai-dealimaking-vs-rulemaking/</link><description>The shift to AI-driven content discovery are hurting publishers, small and large. Norine Rogers, founder of the recipe site Norine’s Nest, said unregulated AI has become an existential threat to her business.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/publishers-vs-ai-dealimaking-vs-rulemaking/</guid></item><item><title>No title</title><link>https://admonsters.com/what-ad-ops-teams-need-to-know-about-privacy-now/</link><description>Privacy Lawyer Jessica Lee answers these questions for publishers: How much liability do publishers carry for downstream vendor behavior? Are probabilistic age estimates enough? What does “strictly necessary” really mean for measurement?</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/what-ad-ops-teams-need-to-know-about-privacy-now/</guid></item><item><title>No title</title><link>https://admonsters.com/one-band-one-sound/</link><description>When publishers gather to address sales, product, and operations alignment, old frustrations resurface. But, so do new frameworks, candid stories, and solutions worth taking home.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/one-band-one-sound/</guid></item><item><title>No title</title><link>https://admonsters.com/singing-the-ai-scraping-blues-at-sell-side-summit-nashville/</link><description>The Nashville Sell Side Summit theme “Beyond the Browser,” resonated with publisher concerns around AI-powered, zero-click answer engines and the need to meet audiences outside of their own websites, which are receiving less referral traffic from search and social.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/singing-the-ai-scraping-blues-at-sell-side-summit-nashville/</guid></item><item><title>No title</title><link>https://admonsters.com/how-swivels-ai-agents-are-rewriting-the-ad-ops-playbook/</link><description>Swivel is putting AI agents to work for publishers, automating the messy middle of ad ops so teams can focus on strategy. From faster troubleshooting to smarter workflows, here’s how they’re reshaping the sell-side playbook.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/how-swivels-ai-agents-are-rewriting-the-ad-ops-playbook/</guid></item><item><title>More</title><description>More  More Events Monstership Sponsorship Jobs The Power List Data Management Display Header Bidding Malvertising Mobile Native Non-Human Traffic Private Marketplaces Programmatic Real-Time Bidding Video Viewability</description><guid isPermaLink="false">More||||||</guid></item><item><title>Programmatic</title><link>https://admonsters.com/category/programmatic/</link><description>Programmatic  Programmatic</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/category/programmatic/</guid></item><item><title>Topics</title><description>Topics  Topics Ad Quality Cookies CTV Data Management Header Bidding Identity Mobile Native Programmatic Real-Time Bidding Video Viewability</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Topics||||||</guid></item><item><title>CTV</title><link>https://admonsters.com/category/ctv/</link><description>CTV  CTV</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/category/ctv/</guid></item><item><title>Identity</title><link>https://admonsters.com/category/identity/</link><description>Identity  Identity</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/category/identity/</guid></item><item><title>programmatic70</title><link>https://admonsters.com/tag/programmatic/</link><description>programmatic70  programmatic 70</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/tag/programmatic/</guid></item><item><title>Skip to content</title><link>https://admonsters.com/#content</link><description>Subscribe to Our Free Newsletters</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/#content</guid></item><item><title>No title</title><link>https://admonsters.com/oswald-mendez-details-diego-the-ai-behind-canela-medias-audience-rewards-program/</link><description>For Oswald Méndez, every day as CMO of Canela Media looks different, and that’s precisely what he loves about the job.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/oswald-mendez-details-diego-the-ai-behind-canela-medias-audience-rewards-program/</guid></item><item><title>Balancing Innovation And Interoperability: Navigating Prebid’s Transaction ID Change</title><link>https://admonsters.com/navigating-prebids-transaction-id-change/</link><description>AdMonsters Sell Side Summit Sell Side Summit Fort Lauderdale 2025</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/navigating-prebids-transaction-id-change/</guid></item><item><title>No title</title><link>https://admonsters.com/playbook/monetizing-audiences-in-cookieless-environments/</link><description>As privacy constraints and AI-driven search upend the value of traditional signals, publishers are scrambling to keep every impression countable and valuable—especially on browsers like Safari and Firefox. But more than half admit they’re not monetizing that cookieless traffic effectively. That’s a lot of lost revenue. According to new research,…</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/playbook/monetizing-audiences-in-cookieless-environments/</guid></item><item><title>mobile115</title><link>https://admonsters.com/tag/mobile/</link><description>mobile115  mobile 115 video 112 Connect 94 google 85 viewability 71 programmatic 70 header bidding 63 gdpr 54 privacy 50 cookieless 49</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/tag/mobile/</guid></item><item><title>Marketing winners and losers of the week</title><link>https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-winners-losers-pokemon-oracle-tootsie-pop-novo-nordisk-labubu/</link><description>It was a good week for Pokémon, Tootsie Pops and Oracle—plus, Labubu’s moment may be coming to an end.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-winners-losers-pokemon-oracle-tootsie-pop-novo-nordisk-labubu/</guid></item><item><title>Agency news you need to know this week</title><link>https://adage.com/agencies/aa-agency-brief-72-and-sunny-stagwell-laughlin-constable/</link><description>Agency news you need to know this week  Agency Brief Agency news you need to know this week Ad Age Crossword Puzzle Ad Age crossword puzzle—this week’s snack theme leaves no crumbs Brand Marketing How brands are embracing book culture to build real-life ties to consumers</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/agencies/aa-agency-brief-72-and-sunny-stagwell-laughlin-constable/</guid></item><item><title>Ad Age crossword puzzle—this week’s snack theme leaves no crumbs</title><link>https://adage.com/news/aa-crossword-puzzle-food-beverage-september-12-2025/</link><description>Ad Age crossword puzzle—this week’s snack theme leaves no crumbs  Ad Age Crossword Puzzle Ad Age crossword puzzle—this week’s snack theme leaves no crumbs</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/news/aa-crossword-puzzle-food-beverage-september-12-2025/</guid></item><item><title>How brands are embracing book culture to build real-life ties to consumers</title><link>https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-brands-book-culture-warby-parker-jimmy-johns-book-clubs/</link><description>How brands are embracing book culture to build real-life ties to consumers  Brand Marketing How brands are embracing book culture to build real-life ties to consumers</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-brands-book-culture-warby-parker-jimmy-johns-book-clubs/</guid></item><item><title>18 creative campaigns to know about today</title><link>https://adage.com/creativity/campaigns-commercials/aa-creative-ads-today-amazon-prime-audi-bmw-booking-duracell-monzo/</link><description>See Duracell’s ad criticizing Energizer for its non-U.S. manufacturing and an iconic New Zealand road’s fun loyalty pop-up.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/creativity/campaigns-commercials/aa-creative-ads-today-amazon-prime-audi-bmw-booking-duracell-monzo/</guid></item><item><title>World spins for humans at BBDO’s ‘No Bot Shop’ pop-up in L.A.</title><link>https://adage.com/creativity/work/aa-world-no-bot-shop/</link><description>World spins for humans at BBDO’s ‘No Bot Shop’ pop-up in L.A.  Work World spins for humans at BBDO’s ‘No Bot Shop’ pop-up in L.A. Work Peugeot brings crosswalk characters to life in campaign from Highdive and Accenture Song</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/creativity/work/aa-world-no-bot-shop/</guid></item><item><title>Peugeot brings crosswalk characters to life in campaign from Highdive and Accenture Song</title><link>https://adage.com/creativity/work/aa-peugeot-crosswalk/</link><description>Peugeot brings crosswalk characters to life in campaign from Highdive and Accenture Song  Work Peugeot brings crosswalk characters to life in campaign from Highdive and Accenture Song</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/creativity/work/aa-peugeot-crosswalk/</guid></item><item><title>Why client anthropologists will lead agency strategy in 2030</title><link>https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-client-anthropologists-will-lead-agency-strategy-in-2030/</link><description>As AI takes over execution and insight becomes the true differentiator, agencies will rely on cultural experts who translate human truth into strategy.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-client-anthropologists-will-lead-agency-strategy-in-2030/</guid></item><item><title>Why experiential marketing will lead by 2030</title><link>https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-experiential-marketing-will-lead-by-2030/</link><description>Why experiential marketing will lead by 2030  Why experiential marketing will lead by 2030 How multigenerational talent will shape agency creativity in 2030 Advertising in 2030—smaller, simpler and secondary to CX</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-experiential-marketing-will-lead-by-2030/</guid></item><item><title>How multigenerational talent will shape agency creativity in 2030</title><link>https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-five-generations-will-power-agencies-in-2030/</link><description>How multigenerational talent will shape agency creativity in 2030  How multigenerational talent will shape agency creativity in 2030</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-five-generations-will-power-agencies-in-2030/</guid></item><item><title>Advertising in 2030—smaller, simpler and secondary to CX</title><link>https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-advertising-will-be-smaller-and-simpler-by-2030/</link><description>Advertising in 2030—smaller, simpler and secondary to CX  Advertising in 2030—smaller, simpler and secondary to CX</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-advertising-will-be-smaller-and-simpler-by-2030/</guid></item><item><title>Tracking ad agency account reviews—the latest on brand creative, media and more</title><link>https://adage.com/article/agency-news/tracking-ad-agency-account-reviews-brand-creative-media-pr-social/2566056/</link><description>From the consultants leading them to the incumbents, everything you need to know.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/article/agency-news/tracking-ad-agency-account-reviews-brand-creative-media-pr-social/2566056/</guid></item><item><title>20 brands catching Gen Z’s attention right now</title><link>https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-gen-z-brands-q2-2025-poppi-sofi-coinbase/</link><description>20 brands catching Gen Z’s attention right now  20 brands catching Gen Z’s attention right now The 12 biggest CMO hires of the year so far 20 brands catching baby boomers’ attention right now</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-gen-z-brands-q2-2025-poppi-sofi-coinbase/</guid></item><item><title>The 12 biggest CMO hires of the year so far</title><link>https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-cmo-hirings-job-trends-first-half-2025/</link><description>The 12 biggest CMO hires of the year so far  The 12 biggest CMO hires of the year so far</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-cmo-hirings-job-trends-first-half-2025/</guid></item><item><title>20 brands catching baby boomers’ attention right now</title><link>https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-boomer-brands-q2-2025-old-spice-ace-hardware-nature-valley/</link><description>20 brands catching baby boomers’ attention right now  20 brands catching baby boomers’ attention right now</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-boomer-brands-q2-2025-old-spice-ace-hardware-nature-valley/</guid></item><item><title>Why tech needs to start designing for the 50-plus market</title><link>https://adage.com/opinion/aa-why-marketers-ignore-50-plus-tech-consumers/</link><description>Tech adoption is surging among older adults, representing a lucrative opportunity for marketers.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/opinion/aa-why-marketers-ignore-50-plus-tech-consumers/</guid></item><item><title>How transparency and access can redefine retail media marketing</title><link>https://adage.com/studio-30/aa-how-transparency-and-access-can-redefine-retail-media-marketing/</link><description>How transparency and access can redefine retail media marketing  Sponsored Publishing Partner CVS Media Exchange Publishing Partner: CVS Media Exchange How transparency and access can redefine retail media marketing Image</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/studio-30/aa-how-transparency-and-access-can-redefine-retail-media-marketing/</guid></item><item><title>Inside agency holding company power dynamics—what the centralized model means for jobs and new business</title><link>https://adage.com/ad-age-video-podcast/insider/aa-inside-agency-holding-company-power-dynamics/</link><description>Holding companies are changing their business models in preparation for the industry's future. Agency reporter Ewan Larkin digs into what that means for job hierarchies and the marketplace.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/ad-age-video-podcast/insider/aa-inside-agency-holding-company-power-dynamics/</guid></item><item><title>Advice on being an NFL sponsor, with the CMO of Little Caesars</title><link>https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-little-caesars-cmo-nfl-sponsor-deal-dear/</link><description>Advice on being an NFL sponsor, with the CMO of Little Caesars  Advice on being an NFL sponsor, with the CMO of Little Caesars The case for brand-agency marriage counseling—and why it’s so valuable before launching a review Manscaped’s CMO on unconventional media strategies and learning from virality What marketers can learn from Cracker Barrel and American Eagle’s social controversies</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-little-caesars-cmo-nfl-sponsor-deal-dear/</guid></item><item><title>The case for brand-agency marriage counseling—and why it’s so valuable before launching a review</title><link>https://adage.com/ad-age-video-podcast/insider/aa-the-case-for-brand-agency-marriage-counselling/</link><description>The case for brand-agency marriage counseling—and why it’s so valuable before launching a review  The case for brand-agency marriage counseling—and why it’s so valuable before launching a review</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/ad-age-video-podcast/insider/aa-the-case-for-brand-agency-marriage-counselling/</guid></item><item><title>Manscaped’s CMO on unconventional media strategies and learning from virality</title><link>https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-manscaped-cmo-marketers-brief-podcast/</link><description>Manscaped’s CMO on unconventional media strategies and learning from virality  Manscaped’s CMO on unconventional media strategies and learning from virality</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-manscaped-cmo-marketers-brief-podcast/</guid></item><item><title>What marketers can learn from Cracker Barrel and American Eagle’s social controversies</title><link>https://adage.com/ad-age-video-podcast/insider/aa-cracker-barrel-american-eagle-surviving-social-uproar/</link><description>What marketers can learn from Cracker Barrel and American Eagle’s social controversies  What marketers can learn from Cracker Barrel and American Eagle’s social controversies</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/ad-age-video-podcast/insider/aa-cracker-barrel-american-eagle-surviving-social-uproar/</guid></item><item><title>24 Gen Zers to watch in marketing and advertising</title><link>https://adage.com/article/marketing-news-strategy/gen-zers-watch-marketing-and-advertising/2604081/</link><description>24 Gen Zers to watch in marketing and advertising  Brand Marketing 24 Gen Zers to watch in marketing and advertising Datacenter Gen Z’s attitudes about dining out, restaurant discovery, apps and more Influencers &amp; Creators Gen Z marketing glossary</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/article/marketing-news-strategy/gen-zers-watch-marketing-and-advertising/2604081/</guid></item><item><title>Gen Z’s attitudes about dining out, restaurant discovery, apps and more</title><link>https://adage.com/datacenter/aa-datacenter-weekly-gen-z-attitutes-about-restaurants-dining-out/</link><description>Gen Z’s attitudes about dining out, restaurant discovery, apps and more  Datacenter Gen Z’s attitudes about dining out, restaurant discovery, apps and more</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/datacenter/aa-datacenter-weekly-gen-z-attitutes-about-restaurants-dining-out/</guid></item><item><title>Gen Z marketing glossary</title><link>https://adage.com/article/digital-marketing-ad-tech-news/gen-z-marketing-glossary-2025-words-and-terms-brands-need-know/2604206/</link><description>Gen Z marketing glossary  Influencers &amp; Creators Gen Z marketing glossary</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/article/digital-marketing-ad-tech-news/gen-z-marketing-glossary-2025-words-and-terms-brands-need-know/2604206/</guid></item><item><title>No title</title><description>Copyright © 2025. Crain Communications, Inc. All Rights Reserved.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">No title||||||</guid></item><item><title>The Sherpa Model of Training and the Future of Surgical Mentoring</title><link>https://journals.lww.com/plasreconsurg/_layouts/15/OAKS.Journals/feed.aspx?FeedType=LatestArticles</link><description>&lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/plasreconsurg/fulltext/2025/09000/the_sherpa_model_of_training_and_the_future_of.1.aspx"&gt;&lt;img align="left" alt="image" border="0" src="https://images.journals.lww.com/plasreconsurg/SmallThumb.00006534-202509000-00001.F1.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;No abstract available</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://journals.lww.com/plasreconsurg/_layouts/15/OAKS.Journals/feed.aspx?FeedType=LatestArticles</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0500</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sherpa Model of Training and the Future of Surgical Mentoring</title><link>https://journals.lww.com/plasreconsurg/_layouts/15/OAKS.Journals/feed.aspx?FeedType=CurrentIssue</link><description>&lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/plasreconsurg/fulltext/2025/09000/the_sherpa_model_of_training_and_the_future_of.1.aspx"&gt;&lt;img align="left" alt="image" border="0" src="https://images.journals.lww.com/plasreconsurg/SmallThumb.00006534-202509000-00001.F1.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;No abstract available</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://journals.lww.com/plasreconsurg/_layouts/15/OAKS.Journals/feed.aspx?FeedType=CurrentIssue</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0500</pubDate></item><item><title>Josh Kraft’s Bid for Boston Mayor Takes Hit in Prelim Vote2 days ago</title><link>https://www.sportico.com/personalities/owners/2025/josh-kraft-boston-mayor-voting-results-1234870256/</link><description>Josh Kraft’s Bid for Boston Mayor Takes Hit in Prelim Vote2 days ago  Josh Kraft’s Bid for Boston Mayor Takes Hit in Prelim Vote 2 days ago</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.sportico.com/personalities/owners/2025/josh-kraft-boston-mayor-voting-results-1234870256/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 09:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>No title</title><description>Josh Kraft’s Bid for Boston Mayor Takes Hit in Prelim Vote 2 days ago</description><guid isPermaLink="false">No title||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 09:43:22 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 09:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The latest AI-powered martech news and releases</title><link>https://martech.org/feed/</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="" class="attachment-large size-large wp-post-image" height="457" src="https://martech.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/roundup999-800x457.jpg" style="margin-bottom: 15px;" width="800" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OpenAI just upped its burn rate for the next couple of years from $35 billion to $115 billion. That's a heck of a rounding error.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://martech.org/the-latest-ai-powered-martech-news-and-releases/"&gt;The latest AI-powered martech news and releases&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://martech.org"&gt;MarTech&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://martech.org/feed/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 12:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How Maintainer Burnout Is Causing a Kubernetes Security Disaster</title><link>https://thenewstack.io/blog/feed/</link><description>&lt;img alt="" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="768" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/0c405f89-eso-1024x768.png" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like far too many open source projects, we don&amp;#8217;t give Kubernetes External Secrets Operator (ESO) enough attention. We just assume&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/how-maintainer-burnout-is-causing-a-kubernetes-security-disaster/"&gt;How Maintainer Burnout Is Causing a Kubernetes Security Disaster&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://thenewstack.io/blog/feed/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>A California bill that would regulate AI companion chatbots is close to becoming law</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/feed/</link><description>If SB 243 is enacted, California would become the first state to require operators to implement safety protocols for AI companions and hold companies legally accountable if their chatbots fail to meet those standards.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/feed/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>No title</title><description>Jordyn Woods Expands Her Fashion Label With Inclusive Footwear Collection Designed for All Shapes and Sizes 10 hrs ago</description><guid isPermaLink="false">No title||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 23:43:22 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 23:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tensions Rise at Stagwell As Hold Co Defends Research for Israeli Government</title><link>https://www.adweek.com/feed/</link><description>Pushback over a project for the Israeli Ministry of Foreign Affairs led the holding company to cancel an event in London.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.adweek.com/feed/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 04:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Mexico Targets Asian Nations With Tariffs of Up to 50%5 hrs ago</title><link>https://sourcingjournal.com/topics/trade/mexico-asia-china-tariffs-50-apparel-footwear-textiles-trade-1234777047/</link><description>Mexico Targets Asian Nations With Tariffs of Up to 50%5 hrs ago  Mexico Targets Asian Nations With Tariffs of Up to 50% 5 hrs ago</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sourcingjournal.com/topics/trade/mexico-asia-china-tariffs-50-apparel-footwear-textiles-trade-1234777047/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 04:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>No title</title><description>Mexico Targets Asian Nations With Tariffs of Up to 50% 5 hrs ago</description><guid isPermaLink="false">No title||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 04:43:22 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 04:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next for Streamr.ai Now That It’s Been Acquired By Magnite?</title><link>https://www.adexchanger.com/feed/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;On Tuesday, Magnite announced it had acquired Streamr.ai, which specializes in developing AI-generated assets for small businesses to use in their CTV campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com/ctv-roundup/whats-next-for-streamr-ai-now-that-its-been-acquired-by-magnite/"&gt;What’s Next for Streamr.ai Now That It’s Been Acquired By Magnite?&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com"&gt;AdExchanger&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.adexchanger.com/feed/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 05:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cloud-Native Security in 2025: Why Runtime Visibility Must Take Center Stage</title><link>https://feeds.feedburner.com/TheHackersNews</link><description>The security landscape for cloud-native applications is undergoing a profound transformation. Containers, Kubernetes, and serverless technologies are now the default for modern enterprises, accelerating delivery but also expanding the attack surface in ways traditional security models can’t keep up with.
As adoption grows, so does complexity. Security teams are asked to monitor sprawling hybrid</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://feeds.feedburner.com/TheHackersNews</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:30:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Podcast: Why Software Development Sucks And 7 Mental Models To Help Fix It</title><link>https://feed.infoq.com/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/podcasts/software-development-sucks-mental-models/en/smallimage/engineering-culture-podcast-thumbnail-1757334515552.jpg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shane Hastie, Lead Editor for Culture &amp; Methods, spoke to Thanos Diacakis about how teams often struggle with software delivery. He proposes a shift in mental models and a four-step framework to systematically improve software development by focusing on bottlenecks, balancing different types of work beyond just feature delivery, and investing 20-30% of effort in improving how the team works.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Thanos Diacakis&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://feed.infoq.com/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Research and Markets</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Research%2520and%2520Markets</link><description>Dublin, Sept.  12, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- The "Data Management and Analysis Market for Agritech - A Global and Regional Analysis: Focus on Data Capturing Methods and Supporting Technologies,...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Research%2520and%2520Markets</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 05:17:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Remittix</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Remittix</link><description>KOŠICE, Slovakia , Sept.  12, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- The crypto universe is running ahead, and innovation is revolutionizing the manner in which digital assets connect with the real world. One of...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Remittix</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 05:17:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Remittix</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Remittix?page=1</link><description>KOŠICE, Slovakia , Sept.  12, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- The crypto universe is running ahead, and innovation is revolutionizing the manner in which digital assets connect with the real world. One of...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Remittix?page=1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 05:17:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Temenos</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Temenos?page=1</link><description>GRAND-LANCY, Suiza, Sept.  12, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Temenos (SIX: TEMN), una de las empresas líderes mundiales en tecnología de banca, ha anunciado hoy que ha sido distinguido como ganador...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Temenos?page=1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 05:26:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>YY Group</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/YY%2520Group?page=1</link><description>Singapore, Sept.  12, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- YY Group Holding Limited (Nasdaq: YYGH) (“YY Group” or the “Company”) today announced the closing of its previously announced registered direct offering...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/YY%2520Group?page=1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 05:30:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Research and Markets</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Research%2520and%2520Markets?page=1</link><description>Dublin, Sept.  12, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- The "Foodservice Global Industry Guide 2020-2029" report has been added to  ResearchAndMarkets.com's offering.Global Foodservice industry profile provides...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Research%2520and%2520Markets?page=1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 05:32:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Serabi Gold plc</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Serabi%2520Gold%2520plc?page=1</link><description>Serabi Gold Files NI 43-101 Technical Report for the Palito Complex  Serabi Gold (AIM:SRB, TSX:SBI; OTCQX: SRBIF) the Brazilian focused gold mining and development company, is pleased to announce that...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Serabi%2520Gold%2520plc?page=1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 05:32:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Indocia</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Indocia?page=1</link><description>Singapore, Sept.  12, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) --     Indocia.com, a blockchain solutions provider, today announced the alpha launch of its non-custodial wallet with integrated ecosystem tools. The...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Indocia?page=1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 05:40:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Bitget Limited</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Bitget%2520Limited?page=1</link><description>Bitget hosts Smart Awards 2025 on September 25, honoring top traders and celebrating its 7th anniversary with global community recognition.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Bitget%2520Limited?page=1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 05:41:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Canaccord Genuity Wealth Limited</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Canaccord%2520Genuity%2520Wealth%2520Limited?page=1</link><description>FORM 8.3  PUBLIC OPENING POSITION DISCLOSURE/DEALING DISCLOSURE BY A PERSON WITH INTERESTS IN RELEVANT SECURITIES REPRESENTING 1% OR MORERule 8.3 of the Takeover Code (the “Code”)  1.        KEY...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Canaccord%2520Genuity%2520Wealth%2520Limited?page=1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 05:41:00 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>