<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Merged Feed</title><link>urn:merged-feed</link><description>Merged feed (100 items)</description><atom:link href="urn:merged-feed" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:49:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>A house full of open windows: Why telecoms may never purge their networks of Salt Typhoon</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/salt-typhoon-chinese-hackers-us-telecom-breach/</link><description>A house full of open windows: Why telecoms may never purge their networks of Salt Typhoon  (Scoop News Group graphic) A house full of open windows: Why telecoms may never purge their networks of Salt Typhoon Experts tell CyberScoop that the U.S. telecom system is just too technologically fragmented to gather a clear picture of threats, and too big to ever fully eject… By Derek B. Johnson</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/salt-typhoon-chinese-hackers-us-telecom-breach/</guid></item><item><title>‘Whatever we did was not enough’: How Salt Typhoon slipped through the government’s blind spots</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/salt-typhoon-us-government-response/</link><description>‘Whatever we did was not enough’: How Salt Typhoon slipped through the government’s blind spots  (Graphic by Scoop News Group) ‘Whatever we did was not enough’: How Salt Typhoon slipped through the government’s blind spots Seven sources tell CyberScoop that a lack of coordination and miscommunication between federal agencies and the telecommunications industry left critical networks exposed to the Chinese hacking group. By Tim Starks</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/salt-typhoon-us-government-response/</guid></item><item><title>Prolific Russian ransomware operator living in California enjoys rare leniency awaiting trial</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/ianis-antropenko-zeppelin-ransomware-russian-cybercrime/</link><description>Prolific Russian ransomware operator living in California enjoys rare leniency awaiting trial  (Getty Images) Prolific Russian ransomware operator living in California enjoys rare leniency awaiting trial Ianis Aleksandrovich Antropenko allegedly committed ransomware attacks from 2018 to 2022. He’s been out on bond since his arrest almost a year ago, despite multiple run-ins with… By Matt Kapko</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/ianis-antropenko-zeppelin-ransomware-russian-cybercrime/</guid></item><item><title>Who needs VC funding? How cybercriminals spread their ill-gotten gains to everyday business ventures</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/what-cybercriminals-do-with-their-money-sophos/</link><description>Who needs VC funding? How cybercriminals spread their ill-gotten gains to everyday business ventures  Briefcase full of U.S. currency. (Getty Images) Who needs VC funding? How cybercriminals spread their ill-gotten gains to everyday business ventures The benefits of cybercrime aren't all flashy cars and watches. Sophos X-Ops researchers discovered it also fuels a far-reaching mix of ordinary, sometimes unremarkable businesses. By Matt Kapko</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/what-cybercriminals-do-with-their-money-sophos/</guid></item><item><title>Trump and others want to ramp up cyber offense, but there’s plenty of doubt about the idea</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/aggressive-cyber-offense-trump-administration-us-strategy-debate/</link><description>Trump and others want to ramp up cyber offense, but there’s plenty of doubt about the idea  Trump and others want to ramp up cyber offense, but there’s plenty of doubt about the idea By Tim Starks Mark Pomerleau</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/aggressive-cyber-offense-trump-administration-us-strategy-debate/</guid></item><item><title>Who is sending those scammy text messages about unpaid tolls?</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/toll-road-text-message-scam-swells-nationwide-how-to-stop/</link><description>Who is sending those scammy text messages about unpaid tolls?  Who is sending those scammy text messages about unpaid tolls? By Matt Kapko</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/toll-road-text-message-scam-swells-nationwide-how-to-stop/</guid></item><item><title>What defenders are learning from Black Basta’s leaked chat logs</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/black-basta-internal-chat-leak/</link><description>What defenders are learning from Black Basta’s leaked chat logs  What defenders are learning from Black Basta’s leaked chat logs By Matt Kapko</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/black-basta-internal-chat-leak/</guid></item><item><title>Despite challenges, the CVE program is a public-private partnership that has shown resilience</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/cve-program-history-mitre-nist-1999-2024/</link><description>Despite challenges, the CVE program is a public-private partnership that has shown resilience  Despite challenges, the CVE program is a public-private partnership that has shown resilience By Cynthia Brumfield</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/cve-program-history-mitre-nist-1999-2024/</guid></item><item><title>Legal barriers complicate justice for spyware victims</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/spyware-court-cases-nso-group-meta-whatsapp-apple/</link><description>Legal barriers complicate justice for spyware victims  Legal barriers complicate justice for spyware victims By Tim Starks</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/spyware-court-cases-nso-group-meta-whatsapp-apple/</guid></item><item><title>Why cyber modernization requires partners with technical plus acquisition expertise</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/why-cyber-modernization-requires-partners-with-technical-plus-acquisition-expertise/</link><description>Why cyber modernization requires partners with technical plus acquisition expertise  Image: Giannina Vera, Scoop News Group Why cyber modernization requires partners with technical plus acquisition expertise By Katie Baxter</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/why-cyber-modernization-requires-partners-with-technical-plus-acquisition-expertise/</guid></item><item><title>Why identity is the definitive cyber defense for federal agencies</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/why-identity-is-the-definitive-cyber-defense-for-federal-agencies/</link><description>Why identity is the definitive cyber defense for federal agencies  Image: Scoop News Group Why identity is the definitive cyber defense for federal agencies By Daniel Wilbricht</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/why-identity-is-the-definitive-cyber-defense-for-federal-agencies/</guid></item><item><title>Agencies push for digital transformation amid security challenges</title><link>https://fedscoop.com/agencies-push-for-digital-transformation-amid-security-challenges/</link><description>Agencies push for digital transformation amid security challenges  Agencies push for digital transformation amid security challenges By Scoop News Group</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://fedscoop.com/agencies-push-for-digital-transformation-amid-security-challenges/</guid></item><item><title>Want to scale cyber defenders? Focus on AI-enabled security and organization-wide training</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/want-to-scale-cyber-defenders-focus-on-ai-enabled-security-and-organization-wide-training/</link><description>Want to scale cyber defenders? Focus on AI-enabled security and organization-wide training  Want to scale cyber defenders? Focus on AI-enabled security and organization-wide training By Jay Bhalodia</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/want-to-scale-cyber-defenders-focus-on-ai-enabled-security-and-organization-wide-training/</guid></item><item><title>Why blocking cyber threats is no longer enough</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/video/why-blocking-cyber-threats-is-no-longer-enough/</link><description>Why blocking cyber threats is no longer enough  Why blocking cyber threats is no longer enough By Scoop News Group</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/video/why-blocking-cyber-threats-is-no-longer-enough/</guid></item><item><title>To Catch a Thief: China’s Rise to Cyber Supremacy</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/video/to-catch-a-thief-chinas-rise-to-cyber-supremacy/</link><description>To Catch a Thief: China’s Rise to Cyber Supremacy  To Catch a Thief: China’s Rise to Cyber Supremacy By Scoop News Group</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/video/to-catch-a-thief-chinas-rise-to-cyber-supremacy/</guid></item><item><title>Red Hat’s Adam Clater on navigating zero trust’s unknowns</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/video/red-hats-adam-clater-on-navigating-zero-trusts-unknowns/</link><description>Red Hat’s Adam Clater on navigating zero trust’s unknowns  Red Hat’s Adam Clater on navigating zero trust’s unknowns By Scoop News Group</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/video/red-hats-adam-clater-on-navigating-zero-trusts-unknowns/</guid></item><item><title>Datadog’s Brian Mikkelsen on unifying zero-trust security efforts</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/video/datadogs-brian-mikkelsen-on-unifying-zero-trust-security-efforts/</link><description>Datadog’s Brian Mikkelsen on unifying zero-trust security efforts  Datadog’s Brian Mikkelsen on unifying zero-trust security efforts By Scoop News Group</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/video/datadogs-brian-mikkelsen-on-unifying-zero-trust-security-efforts/</guid></item><item><title>Halcyon’s Cynthia Kaiser on the state of ransomware</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/radio/cisa-2015-lapse-kevin-hanes-ceo-reveal-security-machine-identities-2/</link><description>Halcyon’s Cynthia Kaiser on the state of ransomware  Halcyon’s Cynthia Kaiser on the state of ransomware By CyberScoop Staff</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/radio/cisa-2015-lapse-kevin-hanes-ceo-reveal-security-machine-identities-2/</guid></item><item><title>What happens if CISA 2015 lapses?</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/radio/cisa-2015-lapse-kevin-hanes-ceo-reveal-security-machine-identities/</link><description>What happens if CISA 2015 lapses?  What happens if CISA 2015 lapses? By CyberScoop Staff</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/radio/cisa-2015-lapse-kevin-hanes-ceo-reveal-security-machine-identities/</guid></item><item><title>Dave DeWalt on how to get a board to buy in on cybersecurity</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/radio/dave-dewalt-nightdragon-board-buy-in-cybersecurity/</link><description>Dave DeWalt on how to get a board to buy in on cybersecurity  Dave DeWalt on how to get a board to buy in on cybersecurity By CyberScoop Staff</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/radio/dave-dewalt-nightdragon-board-buy-in-cybersecurity/</guid></item><item><title>Three proactive strategies for defending against insider threats</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/radio/three-proactive-strategies-for-defending-against-insider-threats/</link><description>Three proactive strategies for defending against insider threats  Three proactive strategies for defending against insider threats By Scoop News Group</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/radio/three-proactive-strategies-for-defending-against-insider-threats/</guid></item><item><title>Salesloft Drift security incident started with undetected GitHub access</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/salesloft-drift-attack-root-cause-github-oauth/</link><description>Salesloft Drift security incident started with undetected GitHub access  Salesloft confirmed the impact is much more severe and widespread.  (imageBROKER/Timon Schneider/Alamy) Salesloft Drift security incident started with undetected GitHub access</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/salesloft-drift-attack-root-cause-github-oauth/</guid></item><item><title>CISA pushes final cyber incident reporting rule to May 2026</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/cisa-pushes-final-cyber-incident-reporting-rule-to-may-2026/</link><description>CISA pushes final cyber incident reporting rule to May 2026  Image showing the Colonial Pipeline Houston Station facility in Pasadena, Texas (Photo by Francois PICARD / AFP) (Photo by FRANCOIS PICARD/AFP via Getty Images) CISA pushes final cyber incident reporting rule to May 2026</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/cisa-pushes-final-cyber-incident-reporting-rule-to-may-2026/</guid></item><item><title>Supreme Court blocks FTC commissioner Slaughter’s reinstatement</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/ftc-slaughter-reinstatement-blocked-by-supreme-court/</link><description>Supreme Court blocks FTC commissioner Slaughter’s reinstatement  The front of the U.S. Supreme Court building is seen after sunset on June 24, 2024, in Washington, DC. (Photo by J. David Ake/Getty Images) Supreme Court blocks FTC commissioner Slaughter’s reinstatement</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/ftc-slaughter-reinstatement-blocked-by-supreme-court/</guid></item><item><title>NYU team behind AI-powered malware dubbed ‘PromptLock’</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/ai-ransomware-promptlock-nyu-behind-code-discovered-by-security-researchers/</link><description>NYU team behind AI-powered malware dubbed ‘PromptLock’  (Getty Images) NYU team behind AI-powered malware dubbed ‘PromptLock’</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/ai-ransomware-promptlock-nyu-behind-code-discovered-by-security-researchers/</guid></item><item><title>AI can help track an ever-growing body of vulnerabilities, CISA official says</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/ai-can-help-track-an-ever-growing-body-of-vulnerabilities-cisa-official-says/</link><description>AI can help track an ever-growing body of vulnerabilities, CISA official says  From left, Tanium’s Sam Kinch, GDIT’s Matt Hayden, the Commerce Department’s Ryan Higgins, and CISA’s Chris Butera take part in a panel discussion at a GDIT event on Sept. 4, 2025 in Washington, D.C. (Scoop News Group photo) AI can help track an ever-growing body of vulnerabilities, CISA official says</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/ai-can-help-track-an-ever-growing-body-of-vulnerabilities-cisa-official-says/</guid></item><item><title>Sitecore zero-day vulnerability springs up from exposed machine key</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/sitecore-zero-day-vulnerability/</link><description>Sitecore zero-day vulnerability springs up from exposed machine key  (Getty Images) Sitecore zero-day vulnerability springs up from exposed machine key</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/sitecore-zero-day-vulnerability/</guid></item><item><title>Streameast, world’s largest pirated live sports network, shut down by Egyptian authorities</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/streameast-piracy-live-sports-network-shut-down/</link><description>Streameast, world’s largest pirated live sports network, shut down by Egyptian authorities  Egyptian police confiscated three laptops, four smartphones and Visa cards during an coordinated law enforcement action to shut down Streameast (Egyptian Police via ACE) Streameast, world’s largest pirated live sports network, shut down by Egyptian authorities</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/streameast-piracy-live-sports-network-shut-down/</guid></item><item><title>Cato Networks acquires AI security startup Aim Security</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/cato-networks-acquires-ai-security-startup-aim-security/</link><description>Cato Networks acquires AI security startup Aim Security  (Cato Networks) Cato Networks acquires AI security startup Aim Security</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/cato-networks-acquires-ai-security-startup-aim-security/</guid></item><item><title>CISA guide seeks a unified approach to software ‘ingredients lists’</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/cisa-guide-seeks-a-unified-approach-to-software-ingredients-lists/</link><description>CISA guide seeks a unified approach to software ‘ingredients lists’  Food and drink abstract with many Artificial flavors, Food additives, Food coloring, Preservatives, and artificial sweeteners. 	Hailshadow, iStock / Getty Images Plus CISA guide seeks a unified approach to software ‘ingredients lists’</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/cisa-guide-seeks-a-unified-approach-to-software-ingredients-lists/</guid></item><item><title>House panel approves cyber information sharing, grant legislation as expiration deadlines loom</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/house-panel-approves-cyber-information-sharing-grant-legislation-as-expiration-deadlines-loom/</link><description>House panel approves cyber information sharing, grant legislation as expiration deadlines loom  (L-R) Rep. Nick LaLota R-N.Y., Rep. Tony Gonzales, R-Texas, Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene, R-Ga. and Rep. Andrew Garbarino, R-N.Y., listen during a hearing with the House Committee on Homeland Security on Jan. 30, 2024. (Photo by Anna Moneymaker/Getty Images) House panel approves cyber information sharing, grant legislation as expiration deadlines loom</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/house-panel-approves-cyber-information-sharing-grant-legislation-as-expiration-deadlines-loom/</guid></item><item><title>FTC announces settlement with toy robot makers that tracked location of children</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/ftc-settlement-apitor-childrens-privacy-violation/</link><description>FTC announces settlement with toy robot makers that tracked location of children  Apitor collected data without informing parents or asking for permission, the FTC said, violating federal parental consent requirements. (Image Source: Apitor Technology) FTC announces settlement with toy robot makers that tracked location of children</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/ftc-settlement-apitor-childrens-privacy-violation/</guid></item><item><title>Google patches two Android zero-days, 120 defects total in September security update</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/android-security-update-september-2025/</link><description>Google patches two Android zero-days, 120 defects total in September security update  Workers enter a building on the Google headquarters campus on July 23, 2025, in Mountain View, California. (Justin Sullivan/Getty Images) Google patches two Android zero-days, 120 defects total in September security update</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/android-security-update-september-2025/</guid></item><item><title>Court rules ‘fired’ FTC commissioners be reinstated — again</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/court-rules-ftc-commissioners-reinstated-again-rebecca-slaughter-alvaro-bedoya/</link><description>Court rules ‘fired’ FTC commissioners be reinstated — again  In a 2-1 decision, an appeals court upheld a 1935 Supreme Court precedent restricting the president’s ability to fire FTC commissioners. (Photo by Shuran Huang for The Washington Post via Getty Images) Court rules ‘fired’ FTC commissioners be reinstated — again</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/court-rules-ftc-commissioners-reinstated-again-rebecca-slaughter-alvaro-bedoya/</guid></item><item><title>Topics</title><description>Topics  Topics Ad Quality Cookies CTV Data Management Header Bidding Identity Mobile Native Programmatic Real-Time Bidding Video Viewability</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Topics||||||</guid></item><item><title>CTV</title><link>https://admonsters.com/category/ctv/</link><description>CTV  CTV</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/category/ctv/</guid></item><item><title>Identity</title><link>https://admonsters.com/category/identity/</link><description>Identity  Identity</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/category/identity/</guid></item><item><title>Programmatic</title><link>https://admonsters.com/category/programmatic/</link><description>Programmatic  Programmatic</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/category/programmatic/</guid></item><item><title>programmatic70</title><link>https://admonsters.com/tag/programmatic/</link><description>programmatic70  programmatic 70</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/tag/programmatic/</guid></item><item><title>Skip to content</title><link>https://admonsters.com/#content</link><description>Subscribe to Our Free Newsletters</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/#content</guid></item><item><title>More</title><description>More  More Events Monstership Sponsorship Jobs The Power List Data Management Display Header Bidding Malvertising Mobile Native Non-Human Traffic Private Marketplaces Programmatic Real-Time Bidding Video Viewability Events Events Other Events Monstership Monstership Sponsorship Topics Ad Quality Cookies CTV Data Management Header Bidding Identity Mobile Native Programmatic Real-Time Bidding Video Viewability Decoder Wrapper Playbooks Jobs</description><guid isPermaLink="false">More||||||</guid></item><item><title>Driving Digital Growth with Matt Barsomian, VP of Digital Partnerships at NESN</title><link>https://admonsters.com/driving-digital-growth-with-matt-barsomian-vp-of-digital-partnerships-at-nesn/</link><description>New England Sports Network’s Matt Barsomian talks streaming, women’s sports, and signal loss. He shares insights on how publishers can find new plays in a rapidly shifting ad game.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/driving-digital-growth-with-matt-barsomian-vp-of-digital-partnerships-at-nesn/</guid></item><item><title>Inside People Inc.’s (Dotdash Meredith) Antitrust Lawsuit Against Google</title><link>https://admonsters.com/inside-people-inc-dotdash-merediths-antitrust-lawsuit-against-google/</link><description>Inside People Inc.’s (Dotdash Meredith) Antitrust Lawsuit Against Google  Inside People Inc.’s (Dotdash Meredith) Antitrust Lawsuit Against Google Bridging Silos: Streamlining Direct And Programmatic Advertising At U.S. News &amp; World Report Publisher Blues: 10 Bold Moves To Rewire News For The Next Decade</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/inside-people-inc-dotdash-merediths-antitrust-lawsuit-against-google/</guid></item><item><title>Bridging Silos: Streamlining Direct And Programmatic Advertising At U.S. News &amp; World Report</title><link>https://admonsters.com/bridging-silos-streamlining-direct-and-programmatic-advertising-at-u-s-news-world-report/</link><description>Bridging Silos: Streamlining Direct And Programmatic Advertising At U.S. News &amp; World Report  Bridging Silos: Streamlining Direct And Programmatic Advertising At U.S. News &amp; World Report</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/bridging-silos-streamlining-direct-and-programmatic-advertising-at-u-s-news-world-report/</guid></item><item><title>Publisher Blues: 10 Bold Moves To Rewire News For The Next Decade</title><link>https://admonsters.com/publisher-blues-10-bold-moves-to-rewire-news-for-the-next-decade/</link><description>Publisher Blues: 10 Bold Moves To Rewire News For The Next Decade  Publisher Blues: 10 Bold Moves To Rewire News For The Next Decade</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/publisher-blues-10-bold-moves-to-rewire-news-for-the-next-decade/</guid></item><item><title>No title</title><link>https://admonsters.com/how-a-30-line-javascript-snippet-took-our-ad-viewability-from-55-to-89/</link><description>Jared Collett at Major League Fishing came up with a JavaScript snippet that pauses refresh if the ad isn’t in view. It shot their viewability up from 55% to 89%.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/how-a-30-line-javascript-snippet-took-our-ad-viewability-from-55-to-89/</guid></item><item><title>What Ad Ops Teams Need to Know About Privacy Now</title><link>https://admonsters.com/what-ad-ops-teams-need-to-know-about-privacy-now/</link><description>Privacy Lawyer Jessica Lee answers these questions for publishers: How much liability do publishers carry for downstream vendor behavior? Are probabilistic age estimates enough? What does “strictly necessary” really mean for measurement?</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/what-ad-ops-teams-need-to-know-about-privacy-now/</guid></item><item><title>One Band, One Sound</title><link>https://admonsters.com/one-band-one-sound/</link><description>When publishers gather to address sales, product, and operations alignment, old frustrations resurface. But, so do new frameworks, candid stories, and solutions worth taking home.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/one-band-one-sound/</guid></item><item><title>Singing The AI Scraping Blues At Sell Side Summit Nashville</title><link>https://admonsters.com/singing-the-ai-scraping-blues-at-sell-side-summit-nashville/</link><description>The Nashville Sell Side Summit theme “Beyond the Browser,” resonated with publisher concerns around AI-powered, zero-click answer engines and the need to meet audiences outside of their own websites, which are receiving less referral traffic from search and social.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/singing-the-ai-scraping-blues-at-sell-side-summit-nashville/</guid></item><item><title>From Manual Mayhem to Machine Mastery: How Swivel’s AI Agents Are Rewriting the Ad Ops Playbook</title><link>https://admonsters.com/how-swivels-ai-agents-are-rewriting-the-ad-ops-playbook/</link><description>Swivel is putting AI agents to work for publishers, automating the messy middle of ad ops so teams can focus on strategy. From faster troubleshooting to smarter workflows, here’s how they’re reshaping the sell-side playbook.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/how-swivels-ai-agents-are-rewriting-the-ad-ops-playbook/</guid></item><item><title>How Sell-Side Curation Is Reshaping The Future Of Programmatic</title><link>https://admonsters.com/how-sell-side-curation-is-reshaping-the-future-of-programmatic/</link><description>The rise of sell-side curation is a response to signal loss and a strategic reorientation of the programmatic ecosystem, one that unites data fidelity, cost efficiency and omnichannel scale in one fell swoop.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/how-sell-side-curation-is-reshaping-the-future-of-programmatic/</guid></item><item><title>No title</title><link>https://admonsters.com/playbook/monetizing-audiences-in-cookieless-environments/</link><description>As privacy constraints and AI-driven search upend the value of traditional signals, publishers are scrambling to keep every impression countable and valuable—especially on browsers like Safari and Firefox. But more than half admit they’re not monetizing that cookieless traffic effectively. That’s a lot of lost revenue. According to new research,…</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/playbook/monetizing-audiences-in-cookieless-environments/</guid></item><item><title>mobile115</title><link>https://admonsters.com/tag/mobile/</link><description>mobile115  mobile 115 video 112 Connect 94 google 85 viewability 71 programmatic 70 header bidding 63 gdpr 54 privacy 50 cookieless 49</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/tag/mobile/</guid></item><item><title>Publishers vs. AI: Dealmaking and Rulemaking</title><link>https://admonsters.com/publishers-vs-ai-dealimaking-vs-rulemaking/</link><description>Publishers vs. AI: Dealmaking and Rulemaking  Publishers vs. AI: Dealmaking and Rulemaking How A 30-Line JavaScript Snippet Took Our Ad Viewability from 55% To 89% Balancing Innovation And Interoperability: Navigating Prebid’s Transaction ID Change Inside People Inc.’s (Dotdash Meredith) Antitrust Lawsuit Against Google The Yield Doctor’s Prescription for Bigger Bids? Lower Floors. View All</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/publishers-vs-ai-dealimaking-vs-rulemaking/</guid></item><item><title>No title</title><link>https://admonsters.com/</link><description>Twitter Facebook LinkedIn</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/</guid></item><item><title>Behind Ford’s new campaign and tagline—CMO explains global approach and strategy</title><link>https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-ford-global-campaign-ready-set-ford-tagline/</link><description>Why the automaker is moving from a vehicle-first marketing approach to one that targets lifestyles.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-ford-global-campaign-ready-set-ford-tagline/</guid></item><item><title>How AI ad automation is forcing agencies to redefine their role with Meta</title><link>https://adage.com/technology/ai/aa-meta-ad-automation-agencies/</link><description>How AI ad automation is forcing agencies to redefine their role with Meta  AI How AI ad automation is forcing agencies to redefine their role with Meta</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/technology/ai/aa-meta-ad-automation-agencies/</guid></item><item><title>Dentsu Creative names John Mescall to global creative role</title><link>https://adage.com/agencies/creative-agencies/aa-dentsu-creative-john-mescall-global-creative-partners/</link><description>Dentsu Creative names John Mescall to global creative role  Creative Agencies Dentsu Creative names John Mescall to global creative role</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/agencies/creative-agencies/aa-dentsu-creative-john-mescall-global-creative-partners/</guid></item><item><title>Blue Moon renames the orange as ‘BlueMoonGarnish’ for its 30th anniversary</title><link>https://adage.com/creativity/work/aa-blue-moon-bluemoongarnish/</link><description>Mischief @ No Fixed Address campaign includes a reskinning of the Orange Line transit routes in Chicago and Boston.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/creativity/work/aa-blue-moon-bluemoongarnish/</guid></item><item><title>Liquid Death and Spinal Tap team up for an 11-pack of canned water</title><link>https://adage.com/creativity/work/aa-liquid-death-spinal-tap-11-pack/</link><description>Liquid Death and Spinal Tap team up for an 11-pack of canned water  Work Liquid Death and Spinal Tap team up for an 11-pack of canned water</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/creativity/work/aa-liquid-death-spinal-tap-11-pack/</guid></item><item><title>11 creative campaigns to know about today</title><link>https://adage.com/creativity/campaigns-commercials/aa-creative-ads-today-blue-diamond-bosch-heinz-hot-wheels-lipton/</link><description>11 creative campaigns to know about today  Roundup 11 creative campaigns to know about today</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/creativity/campaigns-commercials/aa-creative-ads-today-blue-diamond-bosch-heinz-hot-wheels-lipton/</guid></item><item><title>In 2030, a brand’s edge will be employees who live its values</title><link>https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-employees-who-live-brand-values-will-lead-in-2030/</link><description>In 2030, a brand’s edge will be employees who live its values  In 2030, a brand’s edge will be employees who live its values</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-employees-who-live-brand-values-will-lead-in-2030/</guid></item><item><title>AI-to-AI persuasion will transform marketing in 2030</title><link>https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-agencies-will-matter-more-in-2030-ai-first-ad-world/</link><description>AI-to-AI persuasion will transform marketing in 2030  AI-to-AI persuasion will transform marketing in 2030</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-agencies-will-matter-more-in-2030-ai-first-ad-world/</guid></item><item><title>Tracking ad agency account reviews—the latest on brand creative, media and more</title><link>https://adage.com/article/agency-news/tracking-ad-agency-account-reviews-brand-creative-media-pr-social/2566056/</link><description>From the consultants leading them to the incumbents, everything you need to know.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/article/agency-news/tracking-ad-agency-account-reviews-brand-creative-media-pr-social/2566056/</guid></item><item><title>The 12 biggest CMO hires of the year so far</title><link>https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-cmo-hirings-job-trends-first-half-2025/</link><description>The 12 biggest CMO hires of the year so far  The 12 biggest CMO hires of the year so far</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-cmo-hirings-job-trends-first-half-2025/</guid></item><item><title>20 brands catching baby boomers’ attention right now</title><link>https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-boomer-brands-q2-2025-old-spice-ace-hardware-nature-valley/</link><description>20 brands catching baby boomers’ attention right now  20 brands catching baby boomers’ attention right now</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-boomer-brands-q2-2025-old-spice-ace-hardware-nature-valley/</guid></item><item><title>Advertising in 2030—smaller, simpler and secondary to CX</title><link>https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-advertising-will-be-smaller-and-simpler-by-2030/</link><description>Why brands will shift investment toward customer experience, product design and real value creation.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-advertising-will-be-smaller-and-simpler-by-2030/</guid></item><item><title>Why Gen Z spends on experiences, not things</title><link>https://adage.com/opinion/aa-gen-z-spends-on-experiences-not-material-goods/</link><description>Generation is driven by a desire for connection, exploration and belonging—not generational novelty.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/opinion/aa-gen-z-spends-on-experiences-not-material-goods/</guid></item><item><title>Why advertising in 2030 will help us, not entertain us</title><link>https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-advertising-in-2030-will-help-not-entertain/</link><description>Advertising will shift to enablement—delivering ambient, useful and assistive experiences that integrate seamlessly into everyday life and technology.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-advertising-in-2030-will-help-not-entertain/</guid></item><item><title>Gaming’s new frontier: Media strategies for brands and agencies</title><link>https://adage.com/studio-30/aa-gaming-media-strategies-for-brands-publishers/</link><description>Gaming’s new frontier: Media strategies for brands and agencies  Publishing Partner Activision Blizzard Media Publishing Partner: Activision Blizzard Media Gaming’s new frontier: Media strategies for brands and agencies</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/studio-30/aa-gaming-media-strategies-for-brands-publishers/</guid></item><item><title>Advice on being an NFL sponsor, with the CMO of Little Caesars</title><link>https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-little-caesars-cmo-nfl-sponsor-deal-dear/</link><description>Greg Hamilton joins the Marketer’s Brief Podcast to talk about the chain’s four years as an NFL sponsor.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-little-caesars-cmo-nfl-sponsor-deal-dear/</guid></item><item><title>The case for brand-agency marriage counseling—and why it’s so valuable before launching a review</title><link>https://adage.com/ad-age-video-podcast/insider/aa-the-case-for-brand-agency-marriage-counselling/</link><description>The case for brand-agency marriage counseling—and why it’s so valuable before launching a review  The case for brand-agency marriage counseling—and why it’s so valuable before launching a review</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/ad-age-video-podcast/insider/aa-the-case-for-brand-agency-marriage-counselling/</guid></item><item><title>Manscaped’s CMO on unconventional media strategies and learning from virality</title><link>https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-manscaped-cmo-marketers-brief-podcast/</link><description>Manscaped’s CMO on unconventional media strategies and learning from virality  Manscaped’s CMO on unconventional media strategies and learning from virality</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-manscaped-cmo-marketers-brief-podcast/</guid></item><item><title>What marketers can learn from Cracker Barrel and American Eagle’s social controversies</title><link>https://adage.com/ad-age-video-podcast/insider/aa-cracker-barrel-american-eagle-surviving-social-uproar/</link><description>What marketers can learn from Cracker Barrel and American Eagle’s social controversies  What marketers can learn from Cracker Barrel and American Eagle’s social controversies</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/ad-age-video-podcast/insider/aa-cracker-barrel-american-eagle-surviving-social-uproar/</guid></item><item><title>How to create loyal Gen Z connections, with Hinge CMO Jackie Jantos</title><link>https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-loyal-gen-z-connections-hinge-cmo/</link><description>How to create loyal Gen Z connections, with Hinge CMO Jackie Jantos  How to create loyal Gen Z connections, with Hinge CMO Jackie Jantos</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-loyal-gen-z-connections-hinge-cmo/</guid></item><item><title>20 brands catching Gen Z’s attention right now</title><link>https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-gen-z-brands-q2-2025-poppi-sofi-coinbase/</link><description>Poppi, SoFi, Coinbase, Revolve and Timberland are among the brands generating interest from Gen Z.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-gen-z-brands-q2-2025-poppi-sofi-coinbase/</guid></item><item><title>24 Gen Zers to watch in marketing and advertising</title><link>https://adage.com/article/marketing-news-strategy/gen-zers-watch-marketing-and-advertising/2604081/</link><description>24 Gen Zers to watch in marketing and advertising  Brand Marketing 24 Gen Zers to watch in marketing and advertising</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/article/marketing-news-strategy/gen-zers-watch-marketing-and-advertising/2604081/</guid></item><item><title>Gen Z’s attitudes about dining out, restaurant discovery, apps and more</title><link>https://adage.com/datacenter/aa-datacenter-weekly-gen-z-attitutes-about-restaurants-dining-out/</link><description>Gen Z’s attitudes about dining out, restaurant discovery, apps and more  Datacenter Gen Z’s attitudes about dining out, restaurant discovery, apps and more</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/datacenter/aa-datacenter-weekly-gen-z-attitutes-about-restaurants-dining-out/</guid></item><item><title>Gen Z marketing glossary</title><link>https://adage.com/article/digital-marketing-ad-tech-news/gen-z-marketing-glossary-2025-words-and-terms-brands-need-know/2604206/</link><description>Gen Z marketing glossary  Influencers &amp; Creators Gen Z marketing glossary</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/article/digital-marketing-ad-tech-news/gen-z-marketing-glossary-2025-words-and-terms-brands-need-know/2604206/</guid></item><item><title>No title</title><description>Copyright © 2025. Crain Communications, Inc. All Rights Reserved.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">No title||||||</guid></item><item><title>Medical Weight Management Considerations in Plastic Surgery</title><link>https://journals.lww.com/plasreconsurg/_layouts/15/OAKS.Journals/feed.aspx?FeedType=CurrentIssue</link><description>&lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/plasreconsurg/fulltext/2025/09000/medical_weight_management_considerations_in.36.aspx"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;No abstract available</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://journals.lww.com/plasreconsurg/_layouts/15/OAKS.Journals/feed.aspx?FeedType=CurrentIssue</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0500</pubDate></item><item><title>Reply: Risk of Attention-Deficit/Hyperactivity Disorder, Autism Spectrum Disorder, and Executive Function Impairment in Metopic Craniosynostosis</title><link>https://journals.lww.com/plasreconsurg/_layouts/15/OAKS.Journals/feed.aspx?FeedType=LatestArticles</link><description>&lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/plasreconsurg/fulltext/2025/09000/reply__risk_of_attention_deficit_hyperactivity.35.aspx"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;No abstract available</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://journals.lww.com/plasreconsurg/_layouts/15/OAKS.Journals/feed.aspx?FeedType=LatestArticles</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0500</pubDate></item><item><title>When Browsers Become the Attack Surface: Rethinking Security for Scattered Spider</title><link>https://feeds.feedburner.com/TheHackersNews</link><description>As enterprises continue to shift their operations to the browser, security teams face a growing set of cyber challenges. In fact, over 80% of security incidents now originate from web applications accessed via Chrome, Edge, Firefox, and other browsers. One particularly fast-evolving adversary, Scattered Spider, has made it their mission to wreak havoc on enterprises by specifically targeting</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://feeds.feedburner.com/TheHackersNews</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:25:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Microsoft’s Rust Bet: From Blue Screens to Safer Code</title><link>https://thenewstack.io/blog/feed/</link><description>&lt;img alt="" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="683" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/5c3fa957-philip-oroni-cnsr8wbbzpq-unsplash-1-1024x683.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft has tinkered with Windows security for decades. Now the company is trying to fix it with Rust, and they&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/microsofts-rust-bet-from-blue-screens-to-safer-code/"&gt;Microsoft&amp;#8217;s Rust Bet: From Blue Screens to Safer Code&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://thenewstack.io/blog/feed/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 23:00:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Presentation: The Friction Fix: Building Collaborative Relationships Between Teams</title><link>https://feed.infoq.com/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/presentations/friction-collaborative-relationships/en/mediumimage/cat-morris-diana-montalion-medium-1756283787988.jpg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diana Montalion and Cat Morris discuss why large-scale transformations often fail, pinpointing six systemic friction points. They explain how architects can drive change by understanding organizational systems, designing knowledge flow, and architecting relationships. They argue that focusing on outcomes, managing resistance, and adopting a learning-driven mindset are critical to success.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Cat Morris, Diana Montalion&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://feed.infoq.com/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 11:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>PubMatic Is Suing Google For Monopolistic Behavior, The Second Such SSP Case</title><link>https://www.adexchanger.com/feed/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;On Monday, PubMatic became the second sell-side platform to file a follow-on antitrust lawsuit against Google.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com/platforms/pubmatic-is-suing-google-for-monopolistic-behavior-the-second-such-ssp-case/"&gt;PubMatic Is Suing Google For Monopolistic Behavior, The Second Such SSP Case&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com"&gt;AdExchanger&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.adexchanger.com/feed/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Richelieu Dennis Is Adcolor&amp;#8217;s 2025 Beacon Award Winner</title><link>https://www.adweek.com/feed/</link><description>The entrepreneur behind Sundial Brands, the New Voices Fund, and a growing media empire embodies the spirit of '‘'rising up while reaching back.'</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.adweek.com/feed/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>4 ways AI is reshaping marketing operations (and how to prepare)</title><link>https://martech.org/feed/</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="A businessperson working on a Rubik&amp;#039;s cube." class="attachment-large size-large wp-post-image" height="450" src="https://martech.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/20250722_1427_Businessperson-Solving-Cube_simple_compose_01k0sp5c4jevs8w2gkg8baq9ce-800x450.png" style="margin-bottom: 15px;" width="800" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Manual data cleanup slowing you down? AI automates hygiene, enriches insights and optimizes campaigns. Let's make your workflows smarter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://martech.org/4-ways-ai-is-reshaping-marketing-operations-and-how-to-prepare/"&gt;4 ways AI is reshaping marketing operations (and how to prepare)&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://martech.org"&gt;MarTech&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://martech.org/feed/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 12:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple’s creator-centric iPhone 17 Pro will make the vlogging camera obsolete</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/feed/</link><description>The iPhone camera has long checked all the boxes for anything that a casual user might need, making a digital camera obsolete for most consumers.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/feed/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Research and Markets</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Research%2520and%2520Markets</link><description>Dublin, Sept.  10, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- The "High Speed Interconnect - Global Strategic Business Report" report has been added to  ResearchAndMarkets.com's offering.   The global market for High...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Research%2520and%2520Markets</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 09:26:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>State Street International (Ireland) Limited</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/State%2520Street%2520International%2520(Ireland)%2520Limited?page=1</link><description>FORM 8.3  IRISH TAKEOVER PANEL  DISCLOSURE UNDER RULE 8.3 OF THE IRISH TAKEOVER PANEL ACT, 1997, TAKEOVER RULES, 2013  DEALINGS BY PERSONS WITH INTERESTS IN RELEVANT SECURITIES REPRESENTING 1% OR MORE...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/State%2520Street%2520International%2520(Ireland)%2520Limited?page=1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 09:30:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Research and Markets</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Research%2520and%2520Markets?page=1</link><description>Dublin, Sept.  10, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- The "Hot Topics Case Study: Global Snacks and Confectionery Market Dynamics" report has been added to  ResearchAndMarkets.com's offering.The total market...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Research%2520and%2520Markets?page=1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 09:31:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>ODW Logistics</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/ODW%2520Logistics?page=1</link><description>COLUMBUS, Ohio, Sept.  10, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- ODW Logistics (ODW) announced today that Renee Dudzinski, Senior Team Lead, has been named a recipient of the 2025 Women in Supply Chain Award. The...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/ODW%2520Logistics?page=1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 09:37:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Remee Wire &amp; Cable</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Remee%2520Wire%2520&amp;%2520Cable</link><description>Remee Wire &amp; Cable announced the launch of their newly expanded line of broadcast and audio/video cables under the brand ClearCast™.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Remee%2520Wire%2520&amp;%2520Cable</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 09:38:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>YY Group</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/YY%2520Group?page=1</link><description>Singapore, Sept.  10, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- YY Group Holding Limited (Nasdaq: YYGH) (“YY Group” or the “Company”) today announced the pricing of a registered offering consisting of 6,666,668...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/YY%2520Group?page=1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 09:38:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Grabar Law Office</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Grabar%2520Law%2520Office?page=1</link><description>PHILADELPHIA, Sept.  10, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) --   Applied Therapeutics (NASDAQ: APLT) – Class Action Reaches Settlement:  Grabar Law Office is investigating claims on behalf of shareholders of...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Grabar%2520Law%2520Office?page=1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 09:38:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Remee Wire &amp; Cable</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Remee%2520Wire%2520&amp;%2520Cable?page=1</link><description>Remee Wire &amp; Cable announced the launch of their newly expanded line of broadcast and audio/video cables under the brand ClearCast™.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Remee%2520Wire%2520&amp;%2520Cable?page=1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 09:38:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Gold Limited</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Blue%2520Gold%2520Limited?page=1</link><description>NEW YORK, Sept.  10, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Blue Gold Limited (Nasdaq: BGL) ("Blue Gold" or the “Company”), a next-generation gold development and technology company, today announced the...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Blue%2520Gold%2520Limited?page=1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 09:40:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>FLSmidth A/S</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/FLSmidth%2520A%252FS?page=1</link><description>PRESS RELEASE FLSmidth &amp; Co. A/S10 September 2025, Copenhagen, Denmark  Following a long-standing partnership, a progressive Indian miner and steelmaker has yet again selected FLS to deliver core...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/FLSmidth%2520A%252FS?page=1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 09:45:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Precedence Research</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Precedence%2520Research?page=1</link><description>Ottawa, Sept.  10, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- The global sustainable palm oil market size stood at USD 75.28 billion in 2024 and is anticipated to increase from USD 78.70 billion in 2025 to around USD...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Precedence%2520Research?page=1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 09:45:00 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>