<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Merged Feed</title><link>urn:merged-feed</link><description>Merged feed (100 items)</description><atom:link href="urn:merged-feed" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:29:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Prolific Russian ransomware operator living in California enjoys rare leniency awaiting trial</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/ianis-antropenko-zeppelin-ransomware-russian-cybercrime/</link><description>Prolific Russian ransomware operator living in California enjoys rare leniency awaiting trial  (Getty Images) Prolific Russian ransomware operator living in California enjoys rare leniency awaiting trial Ianis Aleksandrovich Antropenko allegedly committed ransomware attacks from 2018 to 2022. He’s been out on bond since his arrest almost a year ago, despite multiple run-ins with… By Matt Kapko</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/ianis-antropenko-zeppelin-ransomware-russian-cybercrime/</guid></item><item><title>Who needs VC funding? How cybercriminals spread their ill-gotten gains to everyday business ventures</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/what-cybercriminals-do-with-their-money-sophos/</link><description>Who needs VC funding? How cybercriminals spread their ill-gotten gains to everyday business ventures  Briefcase full of U.S. currency. (Getty Images) Who needs VC funding? How cybercriminals spread their ill-gotten gains to everyday business ventures The benefits of cybercrime aren't all flashy cars and watches. Sophos X-Ops researchers discovered it also fuels a far-reaching mix of ordinary, sometimes unremarkable businesses. By Matt Kapko</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/what-cybercriminals-do-with-their-money-sophos/</guid></item><item><title>Trump and others want to ramp up cyber offense, but there’s plenty of doubt about the idea</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/aggressive-cyber-offense-trump-administration-us-strategy-debate/</link><description>Trump and others want to ramp up cyber offense, but there’s plenty of doubt about the idea  Trump and others want to ramp up cyber offense, but there’s plenty of doubt about the idea By Tim Starks Mark Pomerleau</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/aggressive-cyber-offense-trump-administration-us-strategy-debate/</guid></item><item><title>Who is sending those scammy text messages about unpaid tolls?</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/toll-road-text-message-scam-swells-nationwide-how-to-stop/</link><description>Who is sending those scammy text messages about unpaid tolls?  Who is sending those scammy text messages about unpaid tolls? By Matt Kapko</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/toll-road-text-message-scam-swells-nationwide-how-to-stop/</guid></item><item><title>What defenders are learning from Black Basta’s leaked chat logs</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/black-basta-internal-chat-leak/</link><description>What defenders are learning from Black Basta’s leaked chat logs  What defenders are learning from Black Basta’s leaked chat logs By Matt Kapko</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/black-basta-internal-chat-leak/</guid></item><item><title>Despite challenges, the CVE program is a public-private partnership that has shown resilience</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/cve-program-history-mitre-nist-1999-2024/</link><description>Despite challenges, the CVE program is a public-private partnership that has shown resilience  Despite challenges, the CVE program is a public-private partnership that has shown resilience By Cynthia Brumfield</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/cve-program-history-mitre-nist-1999-2024/</guid></item><item><title>Legal barriers complicate justice for spyware victims</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/spyware-court-cases-nso-group-meta-whatsapp-apple/</link><description>Legal barriers complicate justice for spyware victims  Legal barriers complicate justice for spyware victims By Tim Starks</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/spyware-court-cases-nso-group-meta-whatsapp-apple/</guid></item><item><title>Why cyber modernization requires partners with technical plus acquisition expertise</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/why-cyber-modernization-requires-partners-with-technical-plus-acquisition-expertise/</link><description>Why cyber modernization requires partners with technical plus acquisition expertise  Image: Giannina Vera, Scoop News Group Why cyber modernization requires partners with technical plus acquisition expertise By Katie Baxter</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/why-cyber-modernization-requires-partners-with-technical-plus-acquisition-expertise/</guid></item><item><title>Why identity is the definitive cyber defense for federal agencies</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/why-identity-is-the-definitive-cyber-defense-for-federal-agencies/</link><description>Why identity is the definitive cyber defense for federal agencies  Image: Scoop News Group Why identity is the definitive cyber defense for federal agencies By Daniel Wilbricht</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/why-identity-is-the-definitive-cyber-defense-for-federal-agencies/</guid></item><item><title>Agencies push for digital transformation amid security challenges</title><link>https://fedscoop.com/agencies-push-for-digital-transformation-amid-security-challenges/</link><description>Agencies push for digital transformation amid security challenges  Agencies push for digital transformation amid security challenges By Scoop News Group</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://fedscoop.com/agencies-push-for-digital-transformation-amid-security-challenges/</guid></item><item><title>Want to scale cyber defenders? Focus on AI-enabled security and organization-wide training</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/want-to-scale-cyber-defenders-focus-on-ai-enabled-security-and-organization-wide-training/</link><description>Want to scale cyber defenders? Focus on AI-enabled security and organization-wide training  Want to scale cyber defenders? Focus on AI-enabled security and organization-wide training By Jay Bhalodia</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/want-to-scale-cyber-defenders-focus-on-ai-enabled-security-and-organization-wide-training/</guid></item><item><title>Why blocking cyber threats is no longer enough</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/video/why-blocking-cyber-threats-is-no-longer-enough/</link><description>Why blocking cyber threats is no longer enough  Why blocking cyber threats is no longer enough By Scoop News Group</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/video/why-blocking-cyber-threats-is-no-longer-enough/</guid></item><item><title>To Catch a Thief: China’s Rise to Cyber Supremacy</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/video/to-catch-a-thief-chinas-rise-to-cyber-supremacy/</link><description>To Catch a Thief: China’s Rise to Cyber Supremacy  To Catch a Thief: China’s Rise to Cyber Supremacy By Scoop News Group</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/video/to-catch-a-thief-chinas-rise-to-cyber-supremacy/</guid></item><item><title>Red Hat’s Adam Clater on navigating zero trust’s unknowns</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/video/red-hats-adam-clater-on-navigating-zero-trusts-unknowns/</link><description>Red Hat’s Adam Clater on navigating zero trust’s unknowns  Red Hat’s Adam Clater on navigating zero trust’s unknowns By Scoop News Group</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/video/red-hats-adam-clater-on-navigating-zero-trusts-unknowns/</guid></item><item><title>Datadog’s Brian Mikkelsen on unifying zero-trust security efforts</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/video/datadogs-brian-mikkelsen-on-unifying-zero-trust-security-efforts/</link><description>Datadog’s Brian Mikkelsen on unifying zero-trust security efforts  Datadog’s Brian Mikkelsen on unifying zero-trust security efforts By Scoop News Group</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/video/datadogs-brian-mikkelsen-on-unifying-zero-trust-security-efforts/</guid></item><item><title>Halcyon’s Cynthia Kaiser on the state of ransomware</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/radio/cisa-2015-lapse-kevin-hanes-ceo-reveal-security-machine-identities-2/</link><description>Halcyon’s Cynthia Kaiser on the state of ransomware  Halcyon’s Cynthia Kaiser on the state of ransomware By CyberScoop Staff</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/radio/cisa-2015-lapse-kevin-hanes-ceo-reveal-security-machine-identities-2/</guid></item><item><title>What happens if CISA 2015 lapses?</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/radio/cisa-2015-lapse-kevin-hanes-ceo-reveal-security-machine-identities/</link><description>What happens if CISA 2015 lapses?  What happens if CISA 2015 lapses? By CyberScoop Staff</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/radio/cisa-2015-lapse-kevin-hanes-ceo-reveal-security-machine-identities/</guid></item><item><title>Dave DeWalt on how to get a board to buy in on cybersecurity</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/radio/dave-dewalt-nightdragon-board-buy-in-cybersecurity/</link><description>Dave DeWalt on how to get a board to buy in on cybersecurity  Dave DeWalt on how to get a board to buy in on cybersecurity By CyberScoop Staff</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/radio/dave-dewalt-nightdragon-board-buy-in-cybersecurity/</guid></item><item><title>Three proactive strategies for defending against insider threats</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/radio/three-proactive-strategies-for-defending-against-insider-threats/</link><description>Three proactive strategies for defending against insider threats  Three proactive strategies for defending against insider threats By Scoop News Group</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/radio/three-proactive-strategies-for-defending-against-insider-threats/</guid></item><item><title>NYU team behind AI-powered malware dubbed ‘PromptLock’</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/ai-ransomware-promptlock-nyu-behind-code-discovered-by-security-researchers/</link><description>NYU team behind AI-powered malware dubbed ‘PromptLock’  (Getty Images) NYU team behind AI-powered malware dubbed ‘PromptLock’</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/ai-ransomware-promptlock-nyu-behind-code-discovered-by-security-researchers/</guid></item><item><title>AI can help track an ever-growing body of vulnerabilities, CISA official says</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/ai-can-help-track-an-ever-growing-body-of-vulnerabilities-cisa-official-says/</link><description>AI can help track an ever-growing body of vulnerabilities, CISA official says  From left, Tanium’s Sam Kinch, GDIT’s Matt Hayden, the Commerce Department’s Ryan Higgins, and CISA’s Chris Butera take part in a panel discussion at a GDIT event on Sept. 4, 2025 in Washington, D.C. (Scoop News Group photo) AI can help track an ever-growing body of vulnerabilities, CISA official says</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/ai-can-help-track-an-ever-growing-body-of-vulnerabilities-cisa-official-says/</guid></item><item><title>Sitecore zero-day vulnerability springs up from exposed machine key</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/sitecore-zero-day-vulnerability/</link><description>Sitecore zero-day vulnerability springs up from exposed machine key  (Getty Images) Sitecore zero-day vulnerability springs up from exposed machine key</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/sitecore-zero-day-vulnerability/</guid></item><item><title>Streameast, world’s largest pirated live sports network, shut down by Egyptian authorities</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/streameast-piracy-live-sports-network-shut-down/</link><description>Streameast, world’s largest pirated live sports network, shut down by Egyptian authorities  Egyptian police confiscated three laptops, four smartphones and Visa cards during an coordinated law enforcement action to shut down Streameast (Egyptian Police via ACE) Streameast, world’s largest pirated live sports network, shut down by Egyptian authorities</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/streameast-piracy-live-sports-network-shut-down/</guid></item><item><title>Cato Networks acquires AI security startup Aim Security</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/cato-networks-acquires-ai-security-startup-aim-security/</link><description>Cato Networks acquires AI security startup Aim Security  (Cato Networks) Cato Networks acquires AI security startup Aim Security</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/cato-networks-acquires-ai-security-startup-aim-security/</guid></item><item><title>CISA guide seeks a unified approach to software ‘ingredients lists’</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/cisa-guide-seeks-a-unified-approach-to-software-ingredients-lists/</link><description>CISA guide seeks a unified approach to software ‘ingredients lists’  Food and drink abstract with many Artificial flavors, Food additives, Food coloring, Preservatives, and artificial sweeteners. 	Hailshadow, iStock / Getty Images Plus CISA guide seeks a unified approach to software ‘ingredients lists’</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/cisa-guide-seeks-a-unified-approach-to-software-ingredients-lists/</guid></item><item><title>House panel approves cyber information sharing, grant legislation as expiration deadlines loom</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/house-panel-approves-cyber-information-sharing-grant-legislation-as-expiration-deadlines-loom/</link><description>House panel approves cyber information sharing, grant legislation as expiration deadlines loom  (L-R) Rep. Nick LaLota R-N.Y., Rep. Tony Gonzales, R-Texas, Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene, R-Ga. and Rep. Andrew Garbarino, R-N.Y., listen during a hearing with the House Committee on Homeland Security on Jan. 30, 2024. (Photo by Anna Moneymaker/Getty Images) House panel approves cyber information sharing, grant legislation as expiration deadlines loom</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/house-panel-approves-cyber-information-sharing-grant-legislation-as-expiration-deadlines-loom/</guid></item><item><title>FTC announces settlement with toy robot makers that tracked location of children</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/ftc-settlement-apitor-childrens-privacy-violation/</link><description>FTC announces settlement with toy robot makers that tracked location of children  Apitor collected data without informing parents or asking for permission, the FTC said, violating federal parental consent requirements. (Image Source: Apitor Technology) FTC announces settlement with toy robot makers that tracked location of children</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/ftc-settlement-apitor-childrens-privacy-violation/</guid></item><item><title>Google patches two Android zero-days, 120 defects total in September security update</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/android-security-update-september-2025/</link><description>Google patches two Android zero-days, 120 defects total in September security update  Workers enter a building on the Google headquarters campus on July 23, 2025, in Mountain View, California. (Justin Sullivan/Getty Images) Google patches two Android zero-days, 120 defects total in September security update</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/android-security-update-september-2025/</guid></item><item><title>Court rules ‘fired’ FTC commissioners be reinstated — again</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/court-rules-ftc-commissioners-reinstated-again-rebecca-slaughter-alvaro-bedoya/</link><description>Court rules ‘fired’ FTC commissioners be reinstated — again  In a 2-1 decision, an appeals court upheld a 1935 Supreme Court precedent restricting the president’s ability to fire FTC commissioners. (Photo by Shuran Huang for The Washington Post via Getty Images) Court rules ‘fired’ FTC commissioners be reinstated — again</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/court-rules-ftc-commissioners-reinstated-again-rebecca-slaughter-alvaro-bedoya/</guid></item><item><title>Salesloft Drift attacks hit Cloudflare, Palo Alto Networks, Zscaler</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/salesloft-drift-attacks-cloudflare-palo-alto-networks-zscaler/</link><description>Salesloft Drift attacks hit Cloudflare, Palo Alto Networks, Zscaler  Salesloft confirmed the impact is much more severe and widespread.  (imageBROKER/Timon Schneider/Alamy) Salesloft Drift attacks hit Cloudflare, Palo Alto Networks, Zscaler</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/salesloft-drift-attacks-cloudflare-palo-alto-networks-zscaler/</guid></item><item><title>CISA taps Nicholas Andersen for executive assistant director of cybersecurity</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/cisa-nicholas-andersen-executive-assistant-director-of-cybersecurity/</link><description>CISA taps Nicholas Andersen for executive assistant director of cybersecurity  (Scoop News Group) CISA taps Nicholas Andersen for executive assistant director of cybersecurity</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/cisa-nicholas-andersen-executive-assistant-director-of-cybersecurity/</guid></item><item><title>Varonis buys AI email security firm SlashNext</title><link>https://cyberscoop.com/varonis-slashnext-acquisition-ai-email-security/</link><description>Varonis buys AI email security firm SlashNext  The Varonis building in Herzliya, Israel. (Image by wikipedia user David Shay / CC-BY-4.0) Varonis buys AI email security firm SlashNext</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cyberscoop.com/varonis-slashnext-acquisition-ai-email-security/</guid></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://www.businesswire.com/privacy</link><description>Privacy Policy  Privacy Policy</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.businesswire.com/privacy</guid></item><item><title>Cookie Policy</title><link>https://www.businesswire.com/cookie-policy</link><description>Cookie Policy  Cookie Policy</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.businesswire.com/cookie-policy</guid></item><item><title>Copyright</title><link>https://www.businesswire.com/copyright</link><description>Copyright  Copyright</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.businesswire.com/copyright</guid></item><item><title>Accessibility Statement</title><link>https://www.businesswire.com/accessibility-statement</link><description>Accessibility Statement  Accessibility Statement</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.businesswire.com/accessibility-statement</guid></item><item><title>Terms of Use</title><link>https://www.businesswire.com/terms-of-use</link><description>Terms of Use  Terms of Use</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.businesswire.com/terms-of-use</guid></item><item><title>No title</title><link>https://twitter.com/businesswire/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://twitter.com/businesswire/</guid></item><item><title>No title</title><link>https://www.linkedin.com/company/business-wire/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.linkedin.com/company/business-wire/</guid></item><item><title>No title</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/user/businesswire</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.youtube.com/user/businesswire</guid></item><item><title>No title</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/BusinessWire/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.facebook.com/BusinessWire/</guid></item><item><title>No title</title><link>https://www.instagram.com/businesswire</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.instagram.com/businesswire</guid></item><item><title>Topics</title><description>Topics  Topics Ad Quality Cookies CTV Data Management Header Bidding Identity Mobile Native Programmatic Real-Time Bidding Video Viewability</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Topics||||||</guid></item><item><title>CTV</title><link>https://admonsters.com/category/ctv/</link><description>CTV  CTV</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/category/ctv/</guid></item><item><title>Identity</title><link>https://admonsters.com/category/identity/</link><description>Identity  Identity</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/category/identity/</guid></item><item><title>Programmatic</title><link>https://admonsters.com/category/programmatic/</link><description>Programmatic  Programmatic</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/category/programmatic/</guid></item><item><title>programmatic70</title><link>https://admonsters.com/tag/programmatic/</link><description>programmatic70  programmatic 70</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/tag/programmatic/</guid></item><item><title>Skip to content</title><link>https://admonsters.com/#content</link><description>Subscribe to Our Free Newsletters</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/#content</guid></item><item><title>More</title><description>More  More Events Monstership Sponsorship Jobs The Power List Data Management Display Header Bidding Malvertising Mobile Native Non-Human Traffic Private Marketplaces Programmatic Real-Time Bidding Video Viewability Events Events Other Events Monstership Monstership Sponsorship Topics Ad Quality Cookies CTV Data Management Header Bidding Identity Mobile Native Programmatic Real-Time Bidding Video Viewability Decoder Wrapper Playbooks Jobs</description><guid isPermaLink="false">More||||||</guid></item><item><title>Driving Digital Growth with Matt Barsomian, VP of Digital Partnerships at NESN</title><link>https://admonsters.com/driving-digital-growth-with-matt-barsomian-vp-of-digital-partnerships-at-nesn/</link><description>New England Sports Network’s Matt Barsomian talks streaming, women’s sports, and signal loss. He shares insights on how publishers can find new plays in a rapidly shifting ad game.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/driving-digital-growth-with-matt-barsomian-vp-of-digital-partnerships-at-nesn/</guid></item><item><title>Inside People Inc.’s (Dotdash Meredith) Antitrust Lawsuit Against Google</title><link>https://admonsters.com/inside-people-inc-dotdash-merediths-antitrust-lawsuit-against-google/</link><description>Inside People Inc.’s (Dotdash Meredith) Antitrust Lawsuit Against Google  Inside People Inc.’s (Dotdash Meredith) Antitrust Lawsuit Against Google Bridging Silos: Streamlining Direct And Programmatic Advertising At U.S. News &amp; World Report Publisher Blues: 10 Bold Moves To Rewire News For The Next Decade</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/inside-people-inc-dotdash-merediths-antitrust-lawsuit-against-google/</guid></item><item><title>Bridging Silos: Streamlining Direct And Programmatic Advertising At U.S. News &amp; World Report</title><link>https://admonsters.com/bridging-silos-streamlining-direct-and-programmatic-advertising-at-u-s-news-world-report/</link><description>Bridging Silos: Streamlining Direct And Programmatic Advertising At U.S. News &amp; World Report  Bridging Silos: Streamlining Direct And Programmatic Advertising At U.S. News &amp; World Report</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/bridging-silos-streamlining-direct-and-programmatic-advertising-at-u-s-news-world-report/</guid></item><item><title>Publisher Blues: 10 Bold Moves To Rewire News For The Next Decade</title><link>https://admonsters.com/publisher-blues-10-bold-moves-to-rewire-news-for-the-next-decade/</link><description>Publisher Blues: 10 Bold Moves To Rewire News For The Next Decade  Publisher Blues: 10 Bold Moves To Rewire News For The Next Decade</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/publisher-blues-10-bold-moves-to-rewire-news-for-the-next-decade/</guid></item><item><title>No title</title><link>https://admonsters.com/how-a-30-line-javascript-snippet-took-our-ad-viewability-from-55-to-89/</link><description>Jared Collett at Major League Fishing came up with a JavaScript snippet that pauses refresh if the ad isn’t in view. It shot their viewability up from 55% to 89%.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/how-a-30-line-javascript-snippet-took-our-ad-viewability-from-55-to-89/</guid></item><item><title>What Ad Ops Teams Need to Know About Privacy Now</title><link>https://admonsters.com/what-ad-ops-teams-need-to-know-about-privacy-now/</link><description>Privacy Lawyer Jessica Lee answers these questions for publishers: How much liability do publishers carry for downstream vendor behavior? Are probabilistic age estimates enough? What does “strictly necessary” really mean for measurement?</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/what-ad-ops-teams-need-to-know-about-privacy-now/</guid></item><item><title>One Band, One Sound</title><link>https://admonsters.com/one-band-one-sound/</link><description>When publishers gather to address sales, product, and operations alignment, old frustrations resurface. But, so do new frameworks, candid stories, and solutions worth taking home.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/one-band-one-sound/</guid></item><item><title>Singing The AI Scraping Blues At Sell Side Summit Nashville</title><link>https://admonsters.com/singing-the-ai-scraping-blues-at-sell-side-summit-nashville/</link><description>The Nashville Sell Side Summit theme “Beyond the Browser,” resonated with publisher concerns around AI-powered, zero-click answer engines and the need to meet audiences outside of their own websites, which are receiving less referral traffic from search and social.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/singing-the-ai-scraping-blues-at-sell-side-summit-nashville/</guid></item><item><title>From Manual Mayhem to Machine Mastery: How Swivel’s AI Agents Are Rewriting the Ad Ops Playbook</title><link>https://admonsters.com/how-swivels-ai-agents-are-rewriting-the-ad-ops-playbook/</link><description>Swivel is putting AI agents to work for publishers, automating the messy middle of ad ops so teams can focus on strategy. From faster troubleshooting to smarter workflows, here’s how they’re reshaping the sell-side playbook.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/how-swivels-ai-agents-are-rewriting-the-ad-ops-playbook/</guid></item><item><title>How Sell-Side Curation Is Reshaping The Future Of Programmatic</title><link>https://admonsters.com/how-sell-side-curation-is-reshaping-the-future-of-programmatic/</link><description>The rise of sell-side curation is a response to signal loss and a strategic reorientation of the programmatic ecosystem, one that unites data fidelity, cost efficiency and omnichannel scale in one fell swoop.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/how-sell-side-curation-is-reshaping-the-future-of-programmatic/</guid></item><item><title>No title</title><link>https://admonsters.com/playbook/monetizing-audiences-in-cookieless-environments/</link><description>As privacy constraints and AI-driven search upend the value of traditional signals, publishers are scrambling to keep every impression countable and valuable—especially on browsers like Safari and Firefox. But more than half admit they’re not monetizing that cookieless traffic effectively. That’s a lot of lost revenue. According to new research,…</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/playbook/monetizing-audiences-in-cookieless-environments/</guid></item><item><title>mobile115</title><link>https://admonsters.com/tag/mobile/</link><description>mobile115  mobile 115 video 112 Connect 94 google 85 viewability 71 programmatic 70 header bidding 63 gdpr 54 privacy 50 cookieless 49</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/tag/mobile/</guid></item><item><title>Publishers vs. AI: Dealmaking and Rulemaking</title><link>https://admonsters.com/publishers-vs-ai-dealimaking-vs-rulemaking/</link><description>Publishers vs. AI: Dealmaking and Rulemaking  Publishers vs. AI: Dealmaking and Rulemaking How A 30-Line JavaScript Snippet Took Our Ad Viewability from 55% To 89% Balancing Innovation And Interoperability: Navigating Prebid’s Transaction ID Change Inside People Inc.’s (Dotdash Meredith) Antitrust Lawsuit Against Google What Ad Ops Teams Need to Know About Privacy Now View All</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/publishers-vs-ai-dealimaking-vs-rulemaking/</guid></item><item><title>No title</title><link>https://admonsters.com/</link><description>Twitter Facebook LinkedIn</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://admonsters.com/</guid></item><item><title>Goodby Silverstein &amp; Partners hires former Droga5 exec as first CEO</title><link>https://adage.com/agencies/aa-goodby-silverstein-partners-hires-sarah-thompson-ceo/</link><description>Goodby Silverstein &amp; Partners is hiring Sarah Thompson as its first-ever CEO and partner.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/agencies/aa-goodby-silverstein-partners-hires-sarah-thompson-ceo/</guid></item><item><title>Behind the #PerfumeTok fragrance boom—how Gen Z is driving sales of designer brands and dupes</title><link>https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-fragrance-culture-booming-gen-z-perfumetok-designer-dupes/</link><description>Behind the #PerfumeTok fragrance boom—how Gen Z is driving sales of designer brands and dupes  Brand Marketing Behind the #PerfumeTok fragrance boom—how Gen Z is driving sales of designer brands and dupes</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-fragrance-culture-booming-gen-z-perfumetok-designer-dupes/</guid></item><item><title>Creator and influencer trends brand marketers need to know about right now</title><link>https://adage.com/influencers-creators/aa-trends-doritos-red-bull-rhode/</link><description>Creator and influencer trends brand marketers need to know about right now  Influencers &amp; Creators Creator and influencer trends brand marketers need to know about right now</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/influencers-creators/aa-trends-doritos-red-bull-rhode/</guid></item><item><title>Inside Ralph Lauren’s AI partnership with Microsoft and its new chatbot</title><link>https://adage.com/technology/ai/aa-ralph-lauren-chatbot-and-microsoft-partnership/</link><description>Inside Ralph Lauren’s AI partnership with Microsoft and its new chatbot  AI Inside Ralph Lauren’s AI partnership with Microsoft and its new chatbot</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/technology/ai/aa-ralph-lauren-chatbot-and-microsoft-partnership/</guid></item><item><title>Liquid Death and Spinal Tap team up for an 11-pack of canned water</title><link>https://adage.com/creativity/work/aa-liquid-death-spinal-tap-11-pack/</link><description>The water brand’s new campaign goes to 11 ahead of “Spinal Tap II: The End Continues,” coming this Friday.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/creativity/work/aa-liquid-death-spinal-tap-11-pack/</guid></item><item><title>11 creative campaigns to know about today</title><link>https://adage.com/creativity/campaigns-commercials/aa-creative-ads-today-blue-diamond-bosch-heinz-hot-wheels-lipton/</link><description>11 creative campaigns to know about today  Roundup 11 creative campaigns to know about today</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/creativity/campaigns-commercials/aa-creative-ads-today-blue-diamond-bosch-heinz-hot-wheels-lipton/</guid></item><item><title>‘Got Milk?’ marks 30 years of the Milk Mustache campaign</title><link>https://adage.com/creativity/work/aa-got-milk-mustache-30-years-photo-studio-tour/</link><description>‘Got Milk?’ marks 30 years of the Milk Mustache campaign  Work ‘Got Milk?’ marks 30 years of the Milk Mustache campaign</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/creativity/work/aa-got-milk-mustache-30-years-photo-studio-tour/</guid></item><item><title>Why agencies in 2030 will need chief trust officers</title><link>https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-agencies-in-2030-will-need-chief-trust-officer/</link><description>Why agencies in 2030 will need chief trust officers  Why agencies in 2030 will need chief trust officers</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-agencies-in-2030-will-need-chief-trust-officer/</guid></item><item><title>The best dating apps in 2030 will offer cultures, not just features</title><link>https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-best-dating-apps-in-2030-will-be-built-on-brand/</link><description>The best dating apps in 2030 will offer cultures, not just features  The best dating apps in 2030 will offer cultures, not just features</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-best-dating-apps-in-2030-will-be-built-on-brand/</guid></item><item><title>Tracking ad agency account reviews—the latest on brand creative, media and more</title><link>https://adage.com/article/agency-news/tracking-ad-agency-account-reviews-brand-creative-media-pr-social/2566056/</link><description>From the consultants leading them to the incumbents, everything you need to know.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/article/agency-news/tracking-ad-agency-account-reviews-brand-creative-media-pr-social/2566056/</guid></item><item><title>The 12 biggest CMO hires of the year so far</title><link>https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-cmo-hirings-job-trends-first-half-2025/</link><description>The 12 biggest CMO hires of the year so far  The 12 biggest CMO hires of the year so far</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-cmo-hirings-job-trends-first-half-2025/</guid></item><item><title>20 brands catching baby boomers’ attention right now</title><link>https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-boomer-brands-q2-2025-old-spice-ace-hardware-nature-valley/</link><description>20 brands catching baby boomers’ attention right now  20 brands catching baby boomers’ attention right now</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-boomer-brands-q2-2025-old-spice-ace-hardware-nature-valley/</guid></item><item><title>In 2030, a brand’s edge will be employees who live its values</title><link>https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-employees-who-live-brand-values-will-lead-in-2030/</link><description>The brands that thrive will make internal culture their most powerful growth engine.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-employees-who-live-brand-values-will-lead-in-2030/</guid></item><item><title>AI-to-AI persuasion will transform marketing in 2030</title><link>https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-agencies-will-matter-more-in-2030-ai-first-ad-world/</link><description>Advertising will be shaped by AI agents negotiating for consumers—but agencies will be cognitive architects and creators of human-centered cultural stories.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/trends-predictions/future-of-advertising-2030/aa-why-agencies-will-matter-more-in-2030-ai-first-ad-world/</guid></item><item><title>5 habit hacks to help marketers actually use AI</title><link>https://adage.com/opinion/aa-marketers-must-build-habits-to-make-ai-work/</link><description>AI will transform marketing only if organizations build lasting, habitual behaviors around its use.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/opinion/aa-marketers-must-build-habits-to-make-ai-work/</guid></item><item><title>Sports marketing’s playbook for performance</title><link>https://adage.com/studio-30/publishing-partners/aa-audacy-sports-marketing/</link><description>Sports marketing’s playbook for performance  Publishing Partner Audacy Publishing Partner: Audacy Sports marketing’s playbook for performance</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/studio-30/publishing-partners/aa-audacy-sports-marketing/</guid></item><item><title>The case for brand-agency marriage counseling—and why it’s so valuable before launching a review</title><link>https://adage.com/ad-age-video-podcast/insider/aa-the-case-for-brand-agency-marriage-counselling/</link><description>Instead of an account review, consultants are recommending brand-agency counseling. Ad Age senior agency reporter Lindsay Rittenhouse goes inside the process.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/ad-age-video-podcast/insider/aa-the-case-for-brand-agency-marriage-counselling/</guid></item><item><title>Manscaped’s CMO on unconventional media strategies and learning from virality</title><link>https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-manscaped-cmo-marketers-brief-podcast/</link><description>Manscaped’s CMO on unconventional media strategies and learning from virality  Manscaped’s CMO on unconventional media strategies and learning from virality</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-manscaped-cmo-marketers-brief-podcast/</guid></item><item><title>What marketers can learn from Cracker Barrel and American Eagle’s social controversies</title><link>https://adage.com/ad-age-video-podcast/insider/aa-cracker-barrel-american-eagle-surviving-social-uproar/</link><description>What marketers can learn from Cracker Barrel and American Eagle’s social controversies  What marketers can learn from Cracker Barrel and American Eagle’s social controversies</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/ad-age-video-podcast/insider/aa-cracker-barrel-american-eagle-surviving-social-uproar/</guid></item><item><title>How to create loyal Gen Z connections, with Hinge CMO Jackie Jantos</title><link>https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-loyal-gen-z-connections-hinge-cmo/</link><description>How to create loyal Gen Z connections, with Hinge CMO Jackie Jantos  How to create loyal Gen Z connections, with Hinge CMO Jackie Jantos</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-loyal-gen-z-connections-hinge-cmo/</guid></item><item><title>How CVS Media Exchange connects health and wellness shoppers with the right brands</title><link>https://adage.com/ad-age-video-podcast/aa-how-cvs-media-exchange-connects-health-focused-shoppers-with-right-brands-podcast/</link><description>How CVS Media Exchange connects health and wellness shoppers with the right brands  Publishing Partner: CVS Media Exchange How CVS Media Exchange connects health and wellness shoppers with the right brands</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/ad-age-video-podcast/aa-how-cvs-media-exchange-connects-health-focused-shoppers-with-right-brands-podcast/</guid></item><item><title>20 brands catching Gen Z’s attention right now</title><link>https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-gen-z-brands-q2-2025-poppi-sofi-coinbase/</link><description>Poppi, SoFi, Coinbase, Revolve and Timberland are among the brands generating interest from Gen Z.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/brand-marketing/aa-gen-z-brands-q2-2025-poppi-sofi-coinbase/</guid></item><item><title>24 Gen Zers to watch in marketing and advertising</title><link>https://adage.com/article/marketing-news-strategy/gen-zers-watch-marketing-and-advertising/2604081/</link><description>24 Gen Zers to watch in marketing and advertising  Brand Marketing 24 Gen Zers to watch in marketing and advertising</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/article/marketing-news-strategy/gen-zers-watch-marketing-and-advertising/2604081/</guid></item><item><title>Gen Z’s attitudes about dining out, restaurant discovery, apps and more</title><link>https://adage.com/datacenter/aa-datacenter-weekly-gen-z-attitutes-about-restaurants-dining-out/</link><description>Gen Z’s attitudes about dining out, restaurant discovery, apps and more  Datacenter Gen Z’s attitudes about dining out, restaurant discovery, apps and more</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/datacenter/aa-datacenter-weekly-gen-z-attitutes-about-restaurants-dining-out/</guid></item><item><title>Gen Z marketing glossary</title><link>https://adage.com/article/digital-marketing-ad-tech-news/gen-z-marketing-glossary-2025-words-and-terms-brands-need-know/2604206/</link><description>Gen Z marketing glossary  Influencers &amp; Creators Gen Z marketing glossary</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://adage.com/article/digital-marketing-ad-tech-news/gen-z-marketing-glossary-2025-words-and-terms-brands-need-know/2604206/</guid></item><item><title>No title</title><description>Copyright © 2025. Crain Communications, Inc. All Rights Reserved.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">No title||||||</guid></item><item><title>Medical Weight Management Considerations in Plastic Surgery</title><link>https://journals.lww.com/plasreconsurg/_layouts/15/OAKS.Journals/feed.aspx?FeedType=CurrentIssue</link><description>&lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/plasreconsurg/fulltext/2025/09000/medical_weight_management_considerations_in.36.aspx"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;No abstract available</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://journals.lww.com/plasreconsurg/_layouts/15/OAKS.Journals/feed.aspx?FeedType=CurrentIssue</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0500</pubDate></item><item><title>Reply: Risk of Attention-Deficit/Hyperactivity Disorder, Autism Spectrum Disorder, and Executive Function Impairment in Metopic Craniosynostosis</title><link>https://journals.lww.com/plasreconsurg/_layouts/15/OAKS.Journals/feed.aspx?FeedType=LatestArticles</link><description>&lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/plasreconsurg/fulltext/2025/09000/reply__risk_of_attention_deficit_hyperactivity.35.aspx"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;No abstract available</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://journals.lww.com/plasreconsurg/_layouts/15/OAKS.Journals/feed.aspx?FeedType=LatestArticles</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0500</pubDate></item><item><title>Abandoned Sogou Zhuyin Update Server Hijacked, Weaponized in Taiwan Espionage Campaign</title><link>https://feeds.feedburner.com/TheHackersNews</link><description>An abandoned update server associated with input method editor (IME) software Sogou Zhuyin was leveraged by threat actors as part of an espionage campaign to deliver several malware families, including C6DOOR and GTELAM, in attacks primarily targeting users across Eastern Asia.
"Attackers employed sophisticated infection chains, such as hijacked software updates and fake cloud storage or login</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://feeds.feedburner.com/TheHackersNews</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 18:42:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Your Legacy APIs Are a Roadblock for AI Agents</title><link>https://thenewstack.io/blog/feed/</link><description>&lt;img alt="" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="675" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/c645b466-road-construction-7165205_1280-1024x675.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;For years, APIs were built with a clear consumer in mind: a human developer on another team who could interpret&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/why-your-legacy-apis-are-a-roadblock-for-ai-agents/"&gt;Why Your Legacy APIs Are a Roadblock for AI Agents&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://thenewstack.io/blog/feed/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:00:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Podcast: The Evolution of Code Review: From Bug-Finding to Team Building</title><link>https://feed.infoq.com/</link><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/podcasts/evolution-code-review-bug-finding/en/smallimage/engineering-culture-podcast-thumbnail-1756728305842.jpg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this podcast, Shane Hastie, Lead Editor for Culture &amp; Methods, spoke to Greg Foster about the evolution and purpose of code reviews, building teams with kindness, expertise, and urgency, and how AI tools are changing software development.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Greg Foster&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://feed.infoq.com/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Live Sports Wins Direct Deals, But The CTV Scatter Market Is Perfect For Programmatic</title><link>https://www.adexchanger.com/feed/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;With the razzle-dazzle portion of the upfronts long over, the ad industry is now learning the impact of those presentations. Early indications forecast softer upfront deals than in years past, but what we’re seeing is more complicated than that. Live sports remains one of the hottest commodities, with NBC boasting its biggest sports upfront ever. [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com/on-tv-and-video/live-sports-wins-direct-deals-but-the-ctv-scatter-market-is-perfect-for-programmatic/"&gt;Live Sports Wins Direct Deals, But The CTV Scatter Market Is Perfect For Programmatic&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com"&gt;AdExchanger&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.adexchanger.com/feed/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Laying the groundwork for smarter, AI-driven marketing</title><link>https://martech.org/feed/</link><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="A marketer celebrating good numbers." class="attachment-large size-large wp-post-image" height="450" src="https://martech.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/ChatGPT-Image-Aug-19-2025-02_18_00-PM-800x450.png" style="margin-bottom: 15px;" width="800" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rules-based campaigns limit your agility. AI decisioning reacts in milliseconds for peak relevance. Learn to build the data and governance to unlock it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://martech.org/laying-the-groundwork-for-smarter-ai-driven-marketing/"&gt;Laying the groundwork for smarter, AI-driven marketing&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://martech.org"&gt;MarTech&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://martech.org/feed/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>(Not So) Mad Man: Jimmy Fallon Is Turning Ads Into Must-See TV</title><link>https://www.adweek.com/feed/</link><description>ADWEEK met Fallon in NYC to discuss how the late-night host mixes family-friendly comedy, cringe, and campaigns in On Brand and takes on TV's uncertain future.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.adweek.com/feed/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Nuclearn gets $10.5M to help the nuclear industry embrace AI</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/feed/</link><description>Nuclearn has developed AI tools to help reactor operators automate routine paperwork. "Think of it as the junior employee," the company tells customers.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcrunch.com/feed/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Toll Brothers, Inc.</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Toll%2520Brothersδ%2520Inc§</link><description>ORLANDO, Fla., Sept.  09, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Toll Brothers Campus Living, a division of Toll Brothers, Inc. (NYSE: TOL), the nation’s leading builder of luxury homes, and joint venture partner...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Toll%2520Brothersδ%2520Inc§</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:13:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Toll Brothers, Inc.</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Toll%2520Brothersδ%2520Inc§?page=1</link><description>ORLANDO, Fla., Sept.  09, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Toll Brothers Campus Living, a division of Toll Brothers, Inc. (NYSE: TOL), the nation’s leading builder of luxury homes, and joint venture partner...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Toll%2520Brothersδ%2520Inc§?page=1</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:13:00 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>