<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Merged Feed</title><link>urn:merged-feed</link><description>Merged feed (100 items)</description><atom:link href="urn:merged-feed" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 08:30:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Article: Engineering a Time Series Database Using Open Source: Rebuilding InfluxDB 3 in Apache Arrow and Rust</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/articles/timeseries-db-rust/en/headerimage/time-series-database-using-open-source-rebuilding-InfluxDB-in-apache-arrow-rust-header-1757058446201.jpg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;At times, to evolve your product, you need to rebuild it from scratch. The article provides the story behind the rewrite of InfluxDB from scratch using a different programming language - Rust - and stack -  Apache Flight, Data Fusion, Apache Arrow and Parquet (FDAP). It emphasises the benefits, as well as the mechanics behind its operation and the different versions of the product.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Paul Dix&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Article: Engineering a Time Series Database Using Open Source: Rebuilding InfluxDB 3 in Apache Arrow and Rust||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 09:00:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Time-Saving Guide for Service Providers: Automating vCISO and Compliance Services</title><description>Introduction
Managed service providers (MSPs) and managed security service providers (MSSPs) are under increasing pressure to deliver strong cybersecurity outcomes in a landscape marked by rising threats and evolving compliance requirements. At the same time, clients want better protection without managing cybersecurity themselves. Service providers must balance these growing demands with the</description><guid isPermaLink="false">The Time-Saving Guide for Service Providers: Automating vCISO and Compliance Services||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 14:55:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 14:55:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Honeycomb Hosted MCP Brings Observability Data into the IDE</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/news/2025/09/honeycomb-hosted-mcp/en/headerimage/header-1757190377363.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Honeycomb has launched its hosted Model Context Protocol (MCP), giving developers real-time access to observability data inside IDEs and AI tools like GitHub Copilot. Available as a managed service on AWS Marketplace, it removes the need for self-hosting and streamlines debugging by surfacing traces, metrics, and logs without context-switching.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Mark Silvester&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Honeycomb Hosted MCP Brings Observability Data into the IDE||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Clockwork’s FleetIQ Aims To Fix AI’s Costly Network Bottleneck</title><description>&lt;img alt="" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="683" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/51079913-donald-wu-mrgtyitjrna-unsplash-1024x683.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;GPUs are steadily getting faster, but as enterprises, neoclouds and the entrenched hyperscalers look to get more efficiency out of&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/clockworks-fleetiq-aims-to-fix-ais-costly-network-bottleneck/"&gt;Clockwork&amp;#8217;s FleetIQ Aims To Fix AI&amp;#8217;s Costly Network Bottleneck&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Clockwork’s FleetIQ Aims To Fix AI’s Costly Network Bottleneck||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:31 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple iPhone Air and iPhone 17 Feature A19 Chips With Spyware-Resistant Memory Safety</title><description>Apple on Tuesday revealed a new security feature called Memory Integrity Enforcement (MIE) that's built into its newly introduced iPhone models, including iPhone 17 and iPhone Air.
MIE, per the tech giant, offers "always-on memory safety protection" across critical attack surfaces such as the kernel and over 70 userland processes without sacrificing device performance by designing its A19 and</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Apple iPhone Air and iPhone 17 Feature A19 Chips With Spyware-Resistant Memory Safety||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:51:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:51:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Microsoft Fixes 80 Flaws — Including SMB PrivEsc and Azure CVSS 10.0 Bugs</title><description>Microsoft on Tuesday addressed a set of 80 security flaws in its software, including one vulnerability that has been disclosed as publicly known at the time of release.
Of the 80 vulnerabilities, eight are rated Critical and 72 are rated Important in severity. None of the shortcomings has been exploited in the wild as a zero-day. Like last month, 38 of the disclosed flaws are related to</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Microsoft Fixes 80 Flaws — Including SMB PrivEsc and Azure CVSS 10.0 Bugs||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:44:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:44:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Qodo Aware Is a ‘Second Brain’ for AI Coding Agents</title><description>&lt;img alt="A black and white brain." class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/bddc11e3-shawn-day-znkhpagiolm-unsplash-1024x576.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most AI coding agents use similar large language models (LLMs) under the hood. Where they differentiate is in their context&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/qodo-aware-is-a-second-brain-for-ai-coding-agents/"&gt;Qodo Aware Is a &amp;#8216;Second Brain&amp;#8217; for AI Coding Agents&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Qodo Aware Is a ‘Second Brain’ for AI Coding Agents||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:00:56 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CHILLYHELL macOS Backdoor and ZynorRAT RAT Threaten macOS, Windows, and Linux Systems</title><description>Cybersecurity researchers have discovered two new malware families, including a modular Apple macOS backdoor called CHILLYHELL and a Go-based remote access trojan (RAT) named ZynorRAT that can target both Windows and Linux systems.
According to an analysis from Jamf Threat Labs, ChillyHell is written in C++ and is developed for Intel architectures.
CHILLYHELL is the name assigned to a malware</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CHILLYHELL macOS Backdoor and ZynorRAT RAT Threaten macOS, Windows, and Linux Systems||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 18:34:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 18:34:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Presentation: The Data Backbone of LLM Systems</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/presentations/llm-data-code-model-prompt/en/mediumimage/paul-iusztin-medium-1756298947850.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drawing from his 8 years of experience in AI, Paul Iusztin breaks down the core components of a scalable architecture, emphasizing the importance of RAG. He shares practical patterns, including the Feature Training Inference architecture, and provides a detailed use case for creating a "Second Brain" AI assistant, covering everything from data pipelines to observability and agentic layers.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Paul Iusztin&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Presentation: The Data Backbone of LLM Systems||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:40:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Agents vs. Agentic AI: A Kubernetes Developer’s Guide</title><description>&lt;img alt="agents" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/77336087-aakash-dhage-plqw2qp-16k-unsplash-1024x576.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The distinction between AI agents and agentic AI has become critical for developers building containerized applications and microservices. While these&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/ai-agents-vs-agentic-ai-a-kubernetes-developers-guide/"&gt;AI Agents vs. Agentic AI: A Kubernetes Developer’s Guide&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">AI Agents vs. Agentic AI: A Kubernetes Developer’s Guide||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 14:00:36 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 14:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Health Care DSP DeepIntent Sells $637 Million Majority Stake To PE Firm Vitruvian Partners</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A dose of private equity is apparently just what the doctor ordered. On Tuesday, UK-based PE firm Vitruvian Partners made a $637 million strategic investment in DeepIntent, a health care-focused demand-side platform that specializes in helping pharma brands reach patients and providers using programmatic advertising. Although Vitruvian’s portfolio includes a bunch of software, consumer tech [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com/technology/health-care-dsp-deepintent-sells-637-million-majority-stake-to-pe-firm-vitruvian-partners/"&gt;Health Care DSP DeepIntent Sells $637 Million Majority Stake To PE Firm Vitruvian Partners&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com"&gt;AdExchanger&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Health Care DSP DeepIntent Sells $637 Million Majority Stake To PE Firm Vitruvian Partners||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 14:29:29 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 14:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>When Is MCP Actually Worth It?</title><description>&lt;img alt="Logo for the Model Context Protocol. This is a guide to when you should use MCP and when it&amp;#039;s unnecessary." class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/97717475-mcp-logo-2-1024x576.png" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Model Context Protocol (MCP) has emerged as an open standard for connecting AI agents with external data and services. Since&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/when-is-mcp-actually-worth-it/"&gt;When Is MCP Actually Worth It?&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">When Is MCP Actually Worth It?||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:00:08 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Chinese APT Deploys EggStreme Fileless Malware to Breach Philippine Military Systems</title><description>An advanced persistent threat (APT) group from China has been attributed to the compromise of a Philippines-based military company using a previously undocumented fileless malware framework called EggStreme.
"This multi-stage toolset achieves persistent, low-profile espionage by injecting malicious code directly into memory and leveraging DLL sideloading to execute payloads," Bitdefender</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Chinese APT Deploys EggStreme Fileless Malware to Breach Philippine Military Systems||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 21:16:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 21:16:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Work With Local AI in the Zed IDE</title><description>&lt;img alt="" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="683" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/81587bd6-tim-mossholder-qvwngmotbik-unsplash-1024x683.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those who believe AI is a great way to not only learn a new programming language but also to&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/how-to-work-with-local-ai-in-the-zed-ide/"&gt;How To Work With Local AI in the Zed IDE&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">How To Work With Local AI in the Zed IDE||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:00:44 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:00:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Five Steps to Build AI Agents that Actually Deliver Business Results</title><description>&lt;img alt="" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="683" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/ea8fc2db-thought-catalog-uk78i6vk3sc-unsplash-1024x683.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the age of digital transformation, businesses have faced a trade-off: Speed and scale often come at the cost of&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/five-steps-to-build-ai-agents-that-actually-deliver-business-results/"&gt;Five Steps to Build AI Agents that Actually Deliver Business Results&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Five Steps to Build AI Agents that Actually Deliver Business Results||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:00:37 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Vibe Coding Fails Enterprise Reality Check</title><description>&lt;img alt="" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="683" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/b992c0c9-philip-oroni-_v-asnc8cve-unsplash-1024x683.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The promise is irresistible: Describe what you want in plain English, and AI spits out working code. This &amp;#8220;vibe coding&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/vibe-coding-fails-enterprise-reality-check/"&gt;Vibe Coding Fails Enterprise Reality Check&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Vibe Coding Fails Enterprise Reality Check||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 23:00:06 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 23:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>For SSPs, What’s In A Name?; A Pillar Of The Community</title><description>&lt;p&gt;SSPs aren't thrilled by TTD characterizing them as "resellers"; Amazon DSP just announced a new partnership to sell Netflix inventory; and pharma brands will be subject to stricter regulations, per the FDA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com/daily-news-roundup/thursday-11092025/"&gt;For SSPs, What’s In A Name?; A Pillar Of The Community&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com"&gt;AdExchanger&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">For SSPs, What’s In A Name?; A Pillar Of The Community||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 04:03:19 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 04:03:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AsyncRAT Exploits ConnectWise ScreenConnect to Steal Credentials and Crypto</title><description>Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed details of a new campaign that leverages ConnectWise ScreenConnect, a legitimate Remote Monitoring and Management (RMM) software, to deliver a fleshless loader that drops a remote access trojan (RAT) called AsyncRAT to steal sensitive data from compromised hosts.
"The attacker used ScreenConnect to gain remote access, then executed a layered VBScript and</description><guid isPermaLink="false">AsyncRAT Exploits ConnectWise ScreenConnect to Steal Credentials and Crypto||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 11:32:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 11:32:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI’s gpt-realtime Enables Production-Ready Voice Agents with End-to-End Speech Processing</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/news/2025/09/openai-gpt-realtime/en/headerimage/GettyImages-1138451118-1757517374254.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;OpenAI launched gpt-realtime and the Realtime API, enabling production-ready AI voice agents with end-to-end speech processing, lower latency, and natural speech delivery. New features include SIP phone support, image input, MCP server integration, and improved safeguards. Early adopters like Zillow and T-Mobile are testing real-time customer service and search use cases.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Hien Luu&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">OpenAI’s gpt-realtime Enables Production-Ready Voice Agents with End-to-End Speech Processing||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 08:00:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fake Madgicx Plus and SocialMetrics Extensions Are Hijacking Meta Business Accounts</title><description>Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed two new campaigns that are serving fake browser extensions using malicious ads and fake websites to steal sensitive data.
The malvertising campaign, per Bitdefender, is designed to push fake "Meta Verified" browser extensions named SocialMetrics Pro that claim to unlock the blue check badge for Facebook and Instagram profiles. At least 37 malicious ads</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Fake Madgicx Plus and SocialMetrics Extensions Are Hijacking Meta Business Accounts||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 14:35:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 14:35:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Azure Service Groups Enter Public Preview Offering New Abstraction Layer for Resource Management</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/news/2025/09/azure-service-groups-preview/en/headerimage/generatedHeaderImage-1757411283972.jpg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft has launched Azure Service Groups in public preview, a new feature designed to simplify resource management and administration. Acting as a flexible, tenant-level container, Service Groups allow users to organize Azure resources from anywhere within their tenant without affecting RBAC or policy inheritance.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Steef-Jan Wiggers&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Azure Service Groups Enter Public Preview Offering New Abstraction Layer for Resource Management||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cracking the Boardroom Code: Helping CISOs Speak the Language of Business</title><description>CISOs know their field. They understand the threat landscape. They understand how to build a strong and cost-effective security stack. They understand how to staff out their organization. They understand the intricacies of compliance. They understand what it takes to reduce risk. Yet one question comes up again and again in our conversations with these security leaders: how do I make the impact</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Cracking the Boardroom Code: Helping CISOs Speak the Language of Business||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:03:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:03:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>SonicWall SSL VPN Flaw and Misconfigurations Actively Exploited by Akira Ransomware Hackers</title><description>Threat actors affiliated with the Akira ransomware group have continued to target SonicWall devices for initial access.
Cybersecurity firm Rapid7 said it observed a spike in intrusions involving SonicWall appliances over the past month, particularly following reports about renewed Akira ransomware activity since late July 2025.
SonicWall subsequently revealed the SSL VPN activity aimed at its</description><guid isPermaLink="false">SonicWall SSL VPN Flaw and Misconfigurations Actively Exploited by Akira Ransomware Hackers||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:03:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:03:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Lessons Learned from Growing from Junior to Staff and beyond</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/news/2025/09/growing-junior-staff/en/headerimage/generatedHeaderImage-1757449109449.jpg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bruno Rey suggested thinking about career growth in circles: self, team, company, and customers. Success comes from understanding broader impacts, embracing compromise, and acting fast, especially in startups. He advised seeking mentors for honest feedback, being open to unexpected or crisis-driven opportunities, and thriving in change with an anti-fragile mindset.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Ben Linders&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Lessons Learned from Growing from Junior to Staff and beyond||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 11:03:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 11:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Presentation: Thinking Like an Architect</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/presentations/architecture-best-practices/en/mediumimage/gregor-hohpe-medium-1756297866716.jpg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gregor Hohpe explains the role of a modern architect as an "IQ booster" for the organization. He discusses how to master communication and decision-making by riding the "Architect Elevator" to connect with all levels. He shares practical strategies for using metaphors, models, and understanding resistance to drive alignment and build resilient systems.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Gregor Hohpe&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Presentation: Thinking Like an Architect||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 12:08:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 12:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The latest AI-powered martech news and releases</title><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="" class="attachment-large size-large wp-post-image" height="457" src="https://martech.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/roundup999-800x457.jpg" style="margin-bottom: 15px;" width="800" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OpenAI just upped its burn rate for the next couple of years from $35 billion to $115 billion. That's a heck of a rounding error.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://martech.org/the-latest-ai-powered-martech-news-and-releases/"&gt;The latest AI-powered martech news and releases&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://martech.org"&gt;MarTech&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">The latest AI-powered martech news and releases||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 12:38:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 12:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Transaction IDs Can Reduce Auction Duplication, But A Fair Market Requires Some Duplication</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Transaction IDs (TIDs) have been the topic du jour on LinkedIn and Twitter – and for good reason. These OpenRTB identifiers let buyers deduplicate the cluttered bidstream.  The entire TID debate has a clear subtitle: “Duplication is waste.”  However, legitimate auction duplication provides benefits for publishers. And the use of TIDs drives publishers’ fears around [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com/the-sell-sider/transaction-ids-can-reduce-auction-duplication-but-a-fair-market-requires-some-duplication/"&gt;Transaction IDs Can Reduce Auction Duplication, But A Fair Market Requires Some Duplication&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com"&gt;AdExchanger&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Transaction IDs Can Reduce Auction Duplication, But A Fair Market Requires Some Duplication||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 13:38:11 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 13:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senator Wyden Urges FTC to Probe Microsoft for Ransomware-Linked Cybersecurity Negligence</title><description>U.S. Senator Ron Wyden has called on the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) to probe Microsoft and hold it responsible for what he called "gross cybersecurity negligence" that enabled ransomware attacks on U.S. critical infrastructure, including against healthcare networks.
"Without timely action, Microsoft's culture of negligent cybersecurity, combined with its de facto monopolization of the</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Senator Wyden Urges FTC to Probe Microsoft for Ransomware-Linked Cybersecurity Negligence||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 20:21:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 20:21:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Stop Building Super Agents; Build Effective AI Teams Instead</title><description>&lt;img alt="" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="684" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/8c5be5f4-christina-wocintechchat-com-kzu0ezl9tjo-unsplash-1024x684.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;While companies worldwide rush to adopt agentic AI for efficiency, data indicates that nearly half of all deployments will fail&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/stop-building-super-agents-build-effective-ai-teams-instead/"&gt;Stop Building Super Agents; Build Effective AI Teams Instead&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Stop Building Super Agents; Build Effective AI Teams Instead||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 15:00:40 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 15:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Google Pixel 10 Adds C2PA Support to Verify AI-Generated Media Authenticity</title><description>Google on Tuesday announced that its new Google Pixel 10 phones support the Coalition for Content Provenance and Authenticity (C2PA) standard out of the box to verify the origin and history of digital content.
To that end, support for C2PA's Content Credentials has been added to Pixel Camera and Google Photos apps for Android. The move, Google said, is designed to further digital media</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Google Pixel 10 Adds C2PA Support to Verify AI-Generated Media Authenticity||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 20:33:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 20:33:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>How Distributed Postgres Solves Cloud’s High-Availability Problem</title><description>&lt;img alt="&amp;quot;How Distributed Postgres Solves Cloud&amp;#039;s High Availability Problem&amp;quot; featured image" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/5da24611-distributed-postgres-cloud-ha-1024x576.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application availability and downtime are concerns no organization can afford to overlook. While the hard numbers vary by use case,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/how-distributed-postgres-solves-clouds-high-availability-problem/"&gt;How Distributed Postgres Solves Cloud&amp;#8217;s High-Availability Problem&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">How Distributed Postgres Solves Cloud’s High-Availability Problem||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:00:03 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dispelling Myths of Open Source Complexity With Apache Iceberg</title><description>&lt;img alt="People in a raft approaching an iceberg." class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/d44f92da-iceberg12-1024x576.jpeg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;While everyone agrees on the importance of an AI-ready data foundation, there&amp;#8217;s often a disconnect on the right tools for&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/dispelling-myths-of-open-source-complexity-with-apache-iceberg/"&gt;Dispelling Myths of Open Source Complexity With Apache Iceberg&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Dispelling Myths of Open Source Complexity With Apache Iceberg||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:00:07 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Understanding Log Events: Why Context Is Key</title><description>&lt;img alt="The five W questions: what, who, when, where, why." class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/a5de9851-fivews-1024x576.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Editor&amp;#8217;s Note: This article is an excerpt from Chapter 1 of The Manning book &amp;#8220;Logging Best Practices: A Practical Guide&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/understanding-log-events-why-context-is-key/"&gt;Understanding Log Events: Why Context Is Key&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Understanding Log Events: Why Context Is Key||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:00:31 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Google DeepMind Launches EmbeddingGemma, an Open Model for On-Device Embeddings</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/news/2025/09/embedding-gemma/en/headerimage/header+%2850%29-1757614506140.jpg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google DeepMind has introduced EmbeddingGemma, a 308M parameter open embedding model designed to run efficiently on-device. The model aims to make applications like retrieval-augmented generation (RAG), semantic search, and text classification accessible without the need for a server or internet connection.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Robert Krzaczyński&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Google DeepMind Launches EmbeddingGemma, an Open Model for On-Device Embeddings||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>3 Ways Security Teams Can Tame Autonomous AI Agents</title><description>&lt;img alt="A collage showcasing various aspects of cybersecurity with digital locks and cityscape in the background." class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/a5b09244-aisecurity-1024x576.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Security professionals understand the dangers of internal threats: adversaries or individuals with harmful objectives who operate from within the enterprise,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/3-ways-security-teams-can-tame-autonomous-ai-agents/"&gt;3 Ways Security Teams Can Tame Autonomous AI Agents&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">3 Ways Security Teams Can Tame Autonomous AI Agents||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 19:00:14 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 19:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Agentic Web: How AI Agents Are Shaping the Web’s Future</title><description>&lt;img alt="agentic web" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/c5c8dbb3-rubidium-beach-w2-krix1ztq-unsplash-1024x576.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his new memoir, This Is For Everyone, Sir Tim Berners-Lee makes it clear he thinks AI agents are the&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/the-agentic-web-how-ai-agents-are-shaping-the-webs-future/"&gt;The Agentic Web: How AI Agents Are Shaping the Web’s Future&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">The Agentic Web: How AI Agents Are Shaping the Web’s Future||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 20:00:25 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 20:00:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla’s robotaxi plans for Nevada move forward with testing permit</title><description>Tesla can now test its autonomous vehicle technology on public streets in Nevada, but it still has steps to take if it wants to offer paid rides like in Austin, Texas.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Tesla’s robotaxi plans for Nevada move forward with testing permit||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 20:20:24 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 20:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How the EU’s Cyber Act Burdens Lone Open Source Developers</title><description>&lt;img alt="At the Open Source Summit Europe, Christopher &amp;quot;Crob&amp;quot; Robinson of the Open Source Security Foundation highlighted concerns about how these regulations could impact open source maintainers" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/834e233f-for-thumbnail-2-1024x576.png" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;What&amp;#8217;s to come of open source software with the coming requirements that come with the Cyber Resiliency Act, now in&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/how-the-eus-cyber-act-burdens-lone-open-source-developers/"&gt;How the EU’s Cyber Act Burdens Lone Open Source Developers&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">How the EU’s Cyber Act Burdens Lone Open Source Developers||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:00:13 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:00:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The music industry is broken: OpenWav’s new app aims to change that</title><description>OpenWav is building a direct-to-fan platform for music artists that lets them keep more of the profits.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">The music industry is broken: OpenWav’s new app aims to change that||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:07:23 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:07:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How Maintainer Burnout Is Causing a Kubernetes Security Disaster</title><description>&lt;img alt="" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="768" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/0c405f89-eso-1024x768.png" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like far too many open source projects, we don&amp;#8217;t give Kubernetes External Secrets Operator (ESO) enough attention. We just assume&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/how-maintainer-burnout-is-causing-a-kubernetes-security-disaster/"&gt;How Maintainer Burnout Is Causing a Kubernetes Security Disaster&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">How Maintainer Burnout Is Causing a Kubernetes Security Disaster||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:00:21 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple’s latest iPhone security feature just made life more difficult for spyware makers</title><description>Apple launched a new security feature for iPhone 17 and iPhone Air designed to reduce the effect of memory corruption bugs, and in turn make spyware and zero-days more difficult to hack into iPhones.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Apple’s latest iPhone security feature just made life more difficult for spyware makers||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:00:46 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI secures Microsoft’s blessing to transition its for-profit arm</title><description>OpenAI and Microsoft say they reached a nonbinding agreement on a revised partnership.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">OpenAI secures Microsoft’s blessing to transition its for-profit arm||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:18:29 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:18:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>A California bill that would regulate AI companion chatbots is close to becoming law</title><description>If SB 243 is enacted, California would become the first state to require operators to implement safety protocols for AI companions and hold companies legally accountable if their chatbots fail to meet those standards.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">A California bill that would regulate AI companion chatbots is close to becoming law||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:23:09 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Trade Desk Gets A Downgrade; WBD Shakes Hands With Nielsen</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Morgan Stanley downgrades The Trade Desk; Warner Bros. Discovery and Nielsen announce a new deal; and brands aren't sold on virtual influencers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com/daily-news-roundup/friday-12092025/"&gt;The Trade Desk Gets A Downgrade; WBD Shakes Hands With Nielsen&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com"&gt;AdExchanger&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">The Trade Desk Gets A Downgrade; WBD Shakes Hands With Nielsen||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 04:03:17 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 04:03:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>From Branding To Action: Best Practices For Using QR Codes In Performance CTV</title><description>&lt;p&gt;At the most recent NewFronts, TV manufacturers Samsung and LG and Fox-owned streaming service Tubi all talked about integrating QR codes into their ad offerings. The technology, which grew in prominence to provide menus and other information during COVID-19, is making a marketing comeback. Will QR codes really be the tech that finally makes TV [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com/on-tv-and-video/from-branding-to-action-best-practices-for-using-qr-codes-in-performance-ctv/"&gt;From Branding To Action: Best Practices For Using QR Codes In Performance CTV&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com"&gt;AdExchanger&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">From Branding To Action: Best Practices For Using QR Codes In Performance CTV||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 04:35:26 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 04:35:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cursor AI Code Editor Flaw Enables Silent Code Execution via Malicious Repositories</title><description>A security weakness has been disclosed in the artificial intelligence (AI)-powered code editor Cursor that could trigger code execution when a maliciously crafted repository is opened using the program.
The issue stems from the fact that an out-of-the-box security setting is disabled by default, opening the door for attackers to run arbitrary code on users' computers with their privileges.
"</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Cursor AI Code Editor Flaw Enables Silent Code Execution via Malicious Repositories||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 10:19:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 10:19:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next for Streamr.ai Now That It’s Been Acquired By Magnite?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On Tuesday, Magnite announced it had acquired Streamr.ai, which specializes in developing AI-generated assets for small businesses to use in their CTV campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com/ctv-roundup/whats-next-for-streamr-ai-now-that-its-been-acquired-by-magnite/"&gt;What’s Next for Streamr.ai Now That It’s Been Acquired By Magnite?&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com"&gt;AdExchanger&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">What’s Next for Streamr.ai Now That It’s Been Acquired By Magnite?||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 05:00:32 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 05:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cloud-Native Security in 2025: Why Runtime Visibility Must Take Center Stage</title><description>The security landscape for cloud-native applications is undergoing a profound transformation. Containers, Kubernetes, and serverless technologies are now the default for modern enterprises, accelerating delivery but also expanding the attack surface in ways traditional security models can’t keep up with.
As adoption grows, so does complexity. Security teams are asked to monitor sprawling hybrid</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Cloud-Native Security in 2025: Why Runtime Visibility Must Take Center Stage||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:30:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:30:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Next.js 15.5 Ships - Turbopack Production Builds, Node.js Middleware, and Tighter Typescript DX</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/news/2025/09/nextjs-15-5-ships/en/headerimage/generatedHeaderImage-1757491256572.jpg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next.js 15.5 has landed, delivering faster builds and powerful server-side middleware. Key highlights include the Turbopack bundler, which boosts compilation speed by 2x to 5x, and Node.js middleware enhancements. TypeScript improvements enhance developer experience with stable typed routes and early error detection.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Daniel Curtis&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Next.js 15.5 Ships - Turbopack Production Builds, Node.js Middleware, and Tighter Typescript DX||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 08:00:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox News’ Eric Shawn Shares His Cancer Diagnosis Live On Air</title><description>Shawn believes his diagnosis is linked to his coverage of the 9/11 attacks.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Fox News’ Eric Shawn Shares His Cancer Diagnosis Live On Air||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 08:53:58 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 08:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Podcast: Why Software Development Sucks And 7 Mental Models To Help Fix It</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/podcasts/software-development-sucks-mental-models/en/smallimage/engineering-culture-podcast-thumbnail-1757334515552.jpg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shane Hastie, Lead Editor for Culture &amp; Methods, spoke to Thanos Diacakis about how teams often struggle with software delivery. He proposes a shift in mental models and a four-step framework to systematically improve software development by focusing on bottlenecks, balancing different types of work beyond just feature delivery, and investing 20-30% of effort in improving how the team works.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Thanos Diacakis&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Podcast: Why Software Development Sucks And 7 Mental Models To Help Fix It||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 09:00:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ads of the Week: 6 Campaigns That Caught Our Eye</title><description>Brands including Uber Eats, Apple, and Bumble made campaigns that caught our eye this week.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Ads of the Week: 6 Campaigns That Caught Our Eye||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 09:00:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bradley Cooper Has Beef With Uber Eats&amp;#8217; Big Football Conspiracy</title><description>Bradley Cooper wants to debunk Uber Eats' conspiracy that football is an elaborate scheme to get people. to buy more food.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Bradley Cooper Has Beef With Uber Eats&amp;#8217; Big Football Conspiracy||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 09:00:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Revolving Door Roundup: Elex Michaelson Joins CNN to Anchor West Coast-Based Newscast</title><description>CNN’s former London bureau chief has been named NPR’s new editor in chief.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Revolving Door Roundup: Elex Michaelson Joins CNN to Anchor West Coast-Based Newscast||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 09:13:28 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 09:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Presentation: Secure by Design: Building Security into Engineering Workflows and Teams</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/presentations/security-workflow-team/en/mediumimage/stefania-chaplin-medium-1756299628025.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stefania Chaplin explains how to integrate security into engineering workflows and teams using a "Secure by Design" approach. Drawing on her extensive experience, she shares practical strategies for a security-first culture by focusing on people, processes, and technology, including the use of security champions and automation to improve resilience and reduce costs.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Stefania Chaplin&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Presentation: Secure by Design: Building Security into Engineering Workflows and Teams||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 10:15:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Critical CVE-2025-5086 in DELMIA Apriso Actively Exploited, CISA Issues Warning</title><description>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Thursday added a critical security flaw impacting Dassault Systèmes DELMIA Apriso Manufacturing Operations Management (MOM) software to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2025-5086, carries a CVSS score of 9.0 out of 10.0. According to</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Critical CVE-2025-5086 in DELMIA Apriso Actively Exploited, CISA Issues Warning||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:33:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:33:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>New HybridPetya Ransomware Bypasses UEFI Secure Boot With CVE-2024-7344 Exploit</title><description>Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new ransomware strain dubbed HybridPetya that resembles the notorious Petya/NotPetya malware, while also incorporating the ability to bypass the Secure Boot mechanism in Unified Extensible Firmware Interface (UEFI) systems using a now-patched vulnerability disclosed earlier this year.
Slovakian cybersecurity company ESET said the samples were uploaded</description><guid isPermaLink="false">New HybridPetya Ransomware Bypasses UEFI Secure Boot With CVE-2024-7344 Exploit||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:20:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:20:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Vercel Introduces AI Gateway for Multi-Model Integration</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/news/2025/09/vercel-ai-gateway/en/headerimage/generatedHeaderImage-1757536485607.jpg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vercel has rolled out the AI Gateway for production workloads. The service provides a single API endpoint for accessing a wide range of large language and generative models, aiming to simplify integration and management for developers.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Daniel Dominguez&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Vercel Introduces AI Gateway for Multi-Model Integration||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:31:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>We are entering a golden age of robotics startups — and not just because of AI</title><description>The robotics startup market has matured over the last decade and the cost to produce robots has gone down significantly.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">We are entering a golden age of robotics startups — and not just because of AI||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Marketing on Reddit: What you need to know</title><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="MarTech what you need to know." class="attachment-large size-large wp-post-image" height="450" src="https://martech.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/WYNTK-personalize-800x450.png" style="margin-bottom: 15px;" width="800" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What you need to know about marketing on Reddit. Updated with details about the new community engagement metrics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://martech.org/a-marketers-guide-to-reddit/"&gt;Marketing on Reddit: What you need to know&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://martech.org"&gt;MarTech&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Marketing on Reddit: What you need to know||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Why impression-based advertising will redefine search and CTV</title><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="Illustration of impression-based advertising" class="attachment-large size-large wp-post-image" height="449" src="https://martech.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Gemini_Generated_Image_impression-based-advertising-800x449.png" style="margin-bottom: 15px;" width="800" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Ads is moving beyond clicks with impressions-based remarketing. Here’s what this shift means for channels, budgets and strategy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://martech.org/why-impression-based-advertising-will-redefine-search-and-ctv/"&gt;Why impression-based advertising will redefine search and CTV&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://martech.org"&gt;MarTech&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Why impression-based advertising will redefine search and CTV||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:06:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AJ Jones Named McCann UK Chief Strategy Officer</title><description>AJ Jones returns to the U.K. after spending nearly five years at McCann Canada.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">AJ Jones Named McCann UK Chief Strategy Officer||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:06:28 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:06:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Microsoft slips unscathed through EU competition probe after promising to unbundle Teams</title><description>Microsoft will escape largely unscathed from a major antitrust investigation by the European Commission that could have resulted in billion-dollar fines for the tech giant.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Microsoft slips unscathed through EU competition probe after promising to unbundle Teams||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:09:44 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:09:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple delays release of iPhone Air in China due to pending approval of eSIM</title><description>The eSIM-only iPhone Air's release is being delayed in China, likely due to regulatory issues around the approval of the embedded SIM.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Apple delays release of iPhone Air in China due to pending approval of eSIM||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:15:23 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Meta Introduces New Brand Tools for Its Social Media Platforms</title><description>Meta wants to help brands better tap into cultural moments taking place on its platforms.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Meta Introduces New Brand Tools for Its Social Media Platforms||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:17:29 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:17:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Marketers On the Move: Hires and Exits at Seen, Michelin, and More</title><description>A weekly roundup of the biggest U.S. and global brand leadership appointments.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Marketers On the Move: Hires and Exits at Seen, Michelin, and More||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:29:16 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind WBD&amp;#8217;s Mysterious Weapons Marketing Campaign</title><description>The Weapons campaign leaned into cryptic messaging and '90s nostalgia.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Behind WBD&amp;#8217;s Mysterious Weapons Marketing Campaign||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:57:46 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How an over-the-air update made Quilt’s heat pumps more powerful</title><description>Quilt's software update unlocked an additional 20% heating and cooling capacity for all of its heat pumps, including those installed in customers' homes.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">How an over-the-air update made Quilt’s heat pumps more powerful||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 14:42:31 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 14:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple Warns French Users of Fourth Spyware Campaign in 2025, CERT-FR Confirms</title><description>Apple has notified users in France of a spyware campaign targeting their devices, according to the Computer Emergency Response Team of France (CERT-FR).
The agency said the alerts were sent out on September 3, 2025, making it the fourth time this year that Apple has notified citizens in the county that at least one of the devices linked to their iCloud accounts may have been compromised as part</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Apple Warns French Users of Fourth Spyware Campaign in 2025, CERT-FR Confirms||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:19:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:19:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Last day to amplify your brand: Host your Side Event at TechCrunch Disrupt 2025</title><description>The application to host a Side Event at TechCrunch Disrupt 2025 closes tonight at 11:59 p.m. PT. Boost your brand during Disrupt Week in October. Apply now.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Last day to amplify your brand: Host your Side Event at TechCrunch Disrupt 2025||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:00:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Engineer in the AI Age: The Orchestrator and Architect</title><description>&lt;img alt="Illustration of an orchestra conductor." class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/a3cd1b3b-conductor12-1024x576.jpeg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rules of software development are being rewritten. Generative AI has moved far beyond autocomplete, upending the developer day and&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/the-engineer-in-the-ai-age-the-orchestrator-and-architect/"&gt;The Engineer in the AI Age: The Orchestrator and Architect&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">The Engineer in the AI Age: The Orchestrator and Architect||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:00:10 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Streaming Ratings, Week of Aug. 11: Wednesday Stays at No. 1 for the Second Week in a Row</title><description>KPop Demon Hunters continues to defy trends, remaining in the top half of the chart.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Streaming Ratings, Week of Aug. 11: Wednesday Stays at No. 1 for the Second Week in a Row||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:06:33 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:06:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Samsung Fixes Critical Zero-Day CVE-2025-21043 Exploited in Android Attacks</title><description>Samsung has released its monthly security updates for Android, including a fix for a security vulnerability that it said has been exploited in zero-day attacks.
The vulnerability, CVE-2025-21043 (CVSS score: 8.8), concerns an out-of-bounds write that could result in arbitrary code execution.
"Out-of-bounds Write in libimagecodec.quram.so prior to SMR Sep-2025 Release 1 allows remote attackers to</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Samsung Fixes Critical Zero-Day CVE-2025-21043 Exploited in Android Attacks||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:46:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:46:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Preparing for your later-stage raise: Insider strategies from top investors at TechCrunch Disrupt 2025</title><description>Planning your Series C and beyond? Hear from IVP’s Zeya Yang, Generation’s Lila Preston, and Diligent Robotics’ Andrea Thomaz on the Builders Stage at TechCrunch Disrupt 2025, October 27–29 in San Francisco.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Preparing for your later-stage raise: Insider strategies from top investors at TechCrunch Disrupt 2025||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:30:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Mastodon rolls out quote posts with protections to prevent ‘dunking’</title><description>Decentralized X alternative Mastodon adds support for quote posts, but with additional controls.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Mastodon rolls out quote posts with protections to prevent ‘dunking’||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:38:53 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenSSF Experts Weigh in on CISA’s SBOM Minimum Elements Update</title><description>&lt;img alt="Computer, magnifying glass and other icons to illustrate software bills of materials (SBOMs)." class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/7e80988c-sboms-1024x576.png" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#8217;s been high time for an update to the government guidance on minimum elements for software bills of materials (SBOMs),&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/openssf-experts-weigh-in-on-cisas-sbom-minimum-elements-update/"&gt;OpenSSF Experts Weigh in on CISA’s SBOM Minimum Elements Update&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">OpenSSF Experts Weigh in on CISA’s SBOM Minimum Elements Update||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:00:51 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:00:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Research: eBPF Not Always a ‘Silver Bullet’ for Network Apps</title><description>&lt;img alt="" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="683" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/caa3ae4b-wouter-de-praetere-elfmdiihktg-unsplash-1024x683.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;A research paper in the latest issue of the Proceedings of the ACM on Networking cast doubt on the performance&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/research-ebpf-not-always-a-silver-bullet-for-network-apps/"&gt;Research: eBPF Not Always a &amp;#8216;Silver Bullet&amp;#8217; for Network Apps&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Research: eBPF Not Always a ‘Silver Bullet’ for Network Apps||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:30:11 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>New FAA program will let eVTOL startups test some operations before full certification</title><description>It's a major change that paves the way for electric air taxi startups to perform more robust demonstrations of their technology before they begin any commercial flights.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">New FAA program will let eVTOL startups test some operations before full certification||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:33:06 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Micro1, a competitor to Scale AI, raises funds at $500M valuation</title><description>A three-year-old startup providing data for AI labs is trying to fill the gap in the market left by Scale AI.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Micro1, a competitor to Scale AI, raises funds at $500M valuation||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Your APIs Are Costing More Than You Think</title><description>&lt;img alt="" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/5b019691-dennis-irorere-yvb-g4g8uj8-unsplash-1024x576.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;APIs are the connective tissue of modern software, powering everything from microservices communication to critical business functions. But while their&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/your-apis-are-costing-more-than-you-think/"&gt;Your APIs Are Costing More Than You Think&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Your APIs Are Costing More Than You Think||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:00:40 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ticker: Fox News to Air Charlie Kirk Tribute Special Saturday</title><description>NBC News announced the hosts for its upcoming Dateline Live event in Nashville, Tenn.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Ticker: Fox News to Air Charlie Kirk Tribute Special Saturday||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:22:11 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:22:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>All of the iPhone 17 models compared</title><description>All four of the devices will be available to preorder on Friday and will be available on September 19.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">All of the iPhone 17 models compared||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 18:46:51 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 18:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Google is a ‘bad actor’ says People CEO, accusing the company of stealing content</title><description>People CEO Neil Vogel says Google's AI crawler can't be blocked because it would block the web crawler too. This lets the search giant steal its content for AI.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Google is a ‘bad actor’ says People CEO, accusing the company of stealing content||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 18:53:26 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 18:53:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>ServiceNow Says Windsurf Gave Its Engineers a 10% Productivity Boost</title><description>&lt;img alt="In this episode of The New Stack Agents, ServiceNow CTO and co-founder Pat Casey discusses why the company runs 90% of its workloads—including AI infrastructure—on its own physical servers rather than the public cloud." class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/6259c9b4-thumbnail-14-1024x576.png" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an era dominated by the public cloud, ServiceNow takes a different path: 90% of its workloads &amp;#8212; including most&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/servicenow-says-windsurf-gave-its-engineers-a-10-productivity-boost/"&gt;ServiceNow Says Windsurf Gave Its Engineers a 10% Productivity Boost&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">ServiceNow Says Windsurf Gave Its Engineers a 10% Productivity Boost||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:00:47 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Why the Oracle-OpenAI deal caught Wall Street by surprise</title><description>The $300B deal is a reminder that despite Oracle’s legacy status, it shouldn’t be overlooked when it comes to AI infrastructure. But key questions around power and how OpenAI will pay for this remain.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Why the Oracle-OpenAI deal caught Wall Street by surprise||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:01:41 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:01:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Pilot union urges FAA to reject Rainmaker’s drone cloud-seeding plan</title><description>Rainmaker wants to use flares to seed clouds — the airline pilots' union says it won't be safe.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Pilot union urges FAA to reject Rainmaker’s drone cloud-seeding plan||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:42:12 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Via shrugs off tepid open to end first day of trading slightly above IPO price</title><description>Transit tech software startup Via had its IPO debut on Friday, starting at below offering price before rising to close at nearly $50.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Via shrugs off tepid open to end first day of trading slightly above IPO price||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 21:16:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 21:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Enovix Corporation</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Enovix%2520Corporation</link><description>FREMONT, Calif., Sept.  12, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Enovix Corporation (Nasdaq: ENVX) (“Company” or “Enovix”), a leader in advanced silicon battery technology, announced today that Enovix Korea has...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Enovix%2520Corporation</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:27:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Ram ends EV pickup truck plans</title><description>Stellantis, the parent company of Ram, said Friday that it will no longer develop a battery-electric full-size pickup. The company cited low demand for full-size battery-electric trucks as the primary reason.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Ram ends EV pickup truck plans||||||Fri, 12 Sep 2025 22:56:16 +0000</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 22:56:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>No title</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/tech/772748/iphone-17-pro-air-preorder-price-how-to-buy-release-date</link><description>Feed refreshed 12:19 AM UTC</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/tech/772748/iphone-17-pro-air-preorder-price-how-to-buy-release-date</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 00:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Keefe, Bruyette &amp; Woods, Inc. (KBW)</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Keefeδ%2520Bruyette%2520&amp;%2520Woodsδ%2520Inc§%2520(KBW)?page=1</link><description>NEW YORK, Sept.  12, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Keefe, Bruyette &amp; Woods, Inc., a leading specialist investment bank to the financial services and fintech sectors, and a wholly owned subsidiary of...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Keefeδ%2520Bruyette%2520&amp;%2520Woodsδ%2520Inc§%2520(KBW)?page=1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:30:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Lucky Creek</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Lucky%2520Creek?page=1</link><description>Las Vegas, Sept.  12, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) --   CasinoTop10.net, a renowned online casino reviewer and guide, has voted Lucky Creek Casino the leading casino for quick payouts. This impressive feat...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Lucky%2520Creek?page=1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:40:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Uptown Aces</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Uptown%2520Aces?page=1</link><description>Dallas, Sept.  12, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) --   CasinoTop10.net, a respected voice in online gaming reviews, has ranked Uptown Aces' no deposit bonus as the best in the industry. The generous bonus...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Uptown%2520Aces?page=1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:42:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Hapbee Technologies, Inc.</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Hapbee%2520Technologiesδ%2520Inc§?page=1</link><description>VANCOUVER, British Columbia, Sept.  12, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Hapbee Technologies Inc. (“Hapbee” or the “Company”) (TSXV: HAPB | OTCQB: HAPBF | FWB: HA1) Hapbee Technologies, Inc. (“Hapbee” or the...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Hapbee%2520Technologiesδ%2520Inc§?page=1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 21:00:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Zahid F. Sarder Saddi, Activist</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Zahid%2520F§%2520Sarder%2520Saddiδ%2520Activist</link><description>WASHINGTON, Sept.  12, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Tributes poured in across the United States and abroad following the killing of conservative activist Charlie Kirk in Utah, with President Donald...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Zahid%2520F§%2520Sarder%2520Saddiδ%2520Activist</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 21:57:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Zahid F. Sarder Saddi, Activist</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Zahid%2520F§%2520Sarder%2520Saddiδ%2520Activist?page=1</link><description>WASHINGTON, Sept.  12, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Tributes poured in across the United States and abroad following the killing of conservative activist Charlie Kirk in Utah, with President Donald...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Zahid%2520F§%2520Sarder%2520Saddiδ%2520Activist?page=1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 21:57:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>MoneyHero Limited</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/MoneyHero%2520Limited?page=1</link><description>香港, Sept.  13, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- 大東南亞地區市場領先的個人金融整合與比較平台兼數碼保險經紀供應商 MoneyHero Limited (NASDAQ: MNY)（下稱「MoneyHero」或「公司」，於今日宣佈 Credit Hero Club 已向 MoneyHero 精選用戶推出僅限邀請測試版本，此前於 2025 年第二季度末已成功向內部...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/MoneyHero%2520Limited?page=1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 22:16:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Mount Logan Capital Intermediate LLC</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Mount%2520Logan%2520Capital%2520Intermediate%2520LLC?page=1</link><description>Establishes U.S.-based alternative asset management and insurance solutions platform  Merged Company, Mount Logan Capital Inc., expected to begin trading on NASDAQ under the symbol “MLCI” on Monday,...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Mount%2520Logan%2520Capital%2520Intermediate%2520LLC?page=1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:40:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Mount Logan Capital Inc</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Mount%2520Logan%2520Capital%2520Inc?page=1</link><description>NEW YORK, Sept.  12, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Mount Logan Capital Inc. (formerly Yukon New Parent, Inc., “New Mount Logan”) filed an early warning report today in connection with the closing of the...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Mount%2520Logan%2520Capital%2520Inc?page=1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:47:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Sylogist Ltd.</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Sylogist%2520Ltd§?page=1</link><description>CALGARY, Alberta, Sept.  13, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Sylogist Ltd. (TSX: SYZ) (“Sylogist” or the “Company”), a leading public sector SaaS company, today acknowledged the news release issued by...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Sylogist%2520Ltd§?page=1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 00:21:00 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>