<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Merged Feed</title><link>urn:merged-feed</link><description>Merged feed (100 items)</description><atom:link href="urn:merged-feed" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 23:36:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>45 Previously Unreported Domains Expose Longstanding Salt Typhoon Cyber Espionage</title><description>Threat hunters have discovered a set of previously unreported domains, some going back to May 2020, that are associated with China-linked threat actors Salt Typhoon and UNC4841.
"The domains date back several years, with the oldest registration activity occurring in May 2020, further confirming that the 2024 Salt Typhoon attacks were not the first activity carried out by this group," Silent Push</description><guid isPermaLink="false">45 Previously Unreported Domains Expose Longstanding Salt Typhoon Cyber Espionage||||||Tue, 09 Sep 2025 05:57:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 05:57:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>20 Popular npm Packages With 2 Billion Weekly Downloads Compromised in Supply Chain Attack</title><description>Multiple npm packages have been compromised as part of a software supply chain attack after a maintainer's account was compromised in a phishing attack.

The attack targeted Josh Junon (aka Qix), who received an email message that mimicked npm ("support@npmjs[.]help"), urging them to update their update their two-factor authentication (2FA) credentials before September 10, 2025, by clicking on</description><guid isPermaLink="false">20 Popular npm Packages With 2 Billion Weekly Downloads Compromised in Supply Chain Attack||||||Tue, 09 Sep 2025 11:43:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 11:43:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Article: FedCM: A New Proposed Identity Standard That Could Change How We Log In on the Web</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/articles/federated-credentials-management-w3c-proposal/en/headerimage/federated-credentials-management-w3c-proposal-header-1756976572775.jpg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;FedCM is a new proposed browser API  for secure, frictionless, privacy-preserving  federated logins. FedCM simplifies user authentication, for both user and developers and reduces the reliance on third-party cookies.  The proposal is currently a public working draft moving towards a candidate recommendation from the W3C  It's actively developed, with Chromium browsers already supporting it.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Dan Moore&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Article: FedCM: A New Proposed Identity Standard That Could Change How We Log In on the Web||||||Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:00:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TOR-Based Cryptojacking Attack Expands Through Misconfigured Docker APIs</title><description>Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a variant of a recently disclosed campaign that abuses the TOR network for cryptojacking attacks targeting exposed Docker APIs.
Akamai, which discovered the latest activity last month, said it's designed to block other actors from accessing the Docker API from the internet.
The findings build on a prior report from Trend Micro in late June 2025, which</description><guid isPermaLink="false">TOR-Based Cryptojacking Attack Expands Through Misconfigured Docker APIs||||||Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:32:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:32:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>How Leading CISOs are Getting Budget Approval</title><description>It’s budget season. Once again, security is being questioned, scrutinized, or deprioritized.
If you're a CISO or security leader, you've likely found yourself explaining why your program matters, why a given tool or headcount is essential, and how the next breach is one blind spot away. But these arguments often fall short unless they're framed in a way the board can understand and appreciate.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">How Leading CISOs are Getting Budget Approval||||||Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:56:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:56:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>From MostereRAT to ClickFix: New Malware Campaigns Highlight Rising AI and Phishing Risks</title><description>Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed details of a phishing campaign that delivers a stealthy banking malware-turned-remote access trojan called MostereRAT.
The phishing attack incorporates a number of advanced evasion techniques to gain complete control over compromised systems, siphon sensitive data, and extend its functionality by serving secondary plugins, Fortinet FortiGuard Labs said.
"</description><guid isPermaLink="false">From MostereRAT to ClickFix: New Malware Campaigns Highlight Rising AI and Phishing Risks||||||Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:57:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:57:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>[Webinar] Shadow AI Agents Multiply Fast —  Learn How to Detect and Control Them</title><description>⚠️ One click is all it takes.
An engineer spins up an “experimental” AI Agent to test a workflow. A business unit connects to automate reporting. A cloud platform quietly enables a new agent behind the scenes.
Individually, they look harmless. But together, they form an invisible swarm of Shadow AI Agents—operating outside security’s line of sight, tied to identities you don’t even know exist.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">[Webinar] Shadow AI Agents Multiply Fast —  Learn How to Detect and Control Them||||||Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:07:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:07:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>RatOn Android Malware Detected With NFC Relay and ATS Banking Fraud Capabilities</title><description>A new Android malware called RatOn&amp;nbsp;has evolved from a basic tool capable of conducting Near Field Communication (NFC) relay attacks&amp;nbsp;to a sophisticated remote access trojan with Automated Transfer System (ATS) capabilities to conduct device fraud.
"RatOn merges traditional overlay attacks with automatic money transfers and NFC relay functionality – making it a uniquely powerful threat,"</description><guid isPermaLink="false">RatOn Android Malware Detected With NFC Relay and ATS Banking Fraud Capabilities||||||Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:23:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:23:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>System Initiative Launches “AI Native” Platform to Simplify Infrastructure Automation</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/news/2025/09/system-initiative-ai-platform/en/headerimage/generatedHeaderImage-1757349502034.jpg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;System Initiative recently released its AI Native Infrastructure Automation platform, aiming to offer DevOps teams a new way to manage infrastructure through natural language.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Craig Risi&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">System Initiative Launches “AI Native” Platform to Simplify Infrastructure Automation||||||Tue, 09 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Development Is Stuck in 1996. Here’s How to Get to the Future.</title><description>&lt;img alt="Businessman looking out on futuristic city." class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/b0b8b8f1-future-1024x576.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;A funny thing is happening on the way to the AI future. We&amp;#8217;re getting bogged down in the same old&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/ai-development-is-stuck-in-1996-heres-how-to-get-to-the-future/"&gt;AI Development Is Stuck in 1996. Here&amp;#8217;s How to Get to the Future. &lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">AI Development Is Stuck in 1996. Here’s How to Get to the Future.||||||Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:00:16 +0000</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:00:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Presentation: Achieving Sustainable Mental Peace at Work Using GenAI</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/presentations/genai-well-being/en/mediumimage/john-gesimondo-medium-1756297240147.jpg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;John Gesimondo explains a framework for achieving sustainable mental peace at work. He shares practical recipes for using GenAI to improve emotional recovery, overcome task paralysis, and enhance planning and communication. He demonstrates how to leverage AI to outsource routine tasks, freeing up time for more engaging and meaningful work.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By John Gesimondo&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Presentation: Achieving Sustainable Mental Peace at Work Using GenAI||||||Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:25:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Your AI Co-Pilots Trapping Data in Isolated Silos?</title><description>&lt;img alt="" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="683" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/7d1db4d0-blake-connally-b3l0g6hlxr8-unsplash-1024x683.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The race is on. By now, virtually every software vendor offers some kind of AI co-pilot designed to assist users&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/are-your-ai-co-pilots-trapping-data-in-isolated-silos/"&gt;Are Your AI Co-Pilots Trapping Data in Isolated Silos?&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Are Your AI Co-Pilots Trapping Data in Isolated Silos?||||||Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:00:49 +0000</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Axios Abuse and Salty 2FA Kits Fuel Advanced Microsoft 365 Phishing Attacks</title><description>Threat actors are abusing HTTP client tools like Axios in conjunction with Microsoft's Direct Send feature to form a "highly efficient attack pipeline" in recent phishing campaigns, according to new findings from ReliaQuest.
"Axios user agent activity surged 241% from June to August 2025, dwarfing the 85% growth of all other flagged user agents combined," the cybersecurity company said in a</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Axios Abuse and Salty 2FA Kits Fuel Advanced Microsoft 365 Phishing Attacks||||||Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:44:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:44:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Agents and Their Life Cycle: What You Should Know</title><description>&lt;img alt="AI agents and their uses." class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/886809d3-agents12-1024x576.png" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;AI agents are changing the way you work, influencing everything from automated customer interactions to intelligent decision-making in industries like&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/ai-agents-and-their-life-cycle-what-you-should-know/"&gt;AI Agents and Their Life Cycle: What You Should Know&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">AI Agents and Their Life Cycle: What You Should Know||||||Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:00:40 +0000</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Vibe Coding: The Productivity Boom Hiding Massive Governance Risks</title><description>&lt;img alt="" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="683" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/5484ec15-austin-distel-vvacrva56fc-unsplash-1024x683.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The software development world is witnessing a fundamental shift. Dubbed &amp;#8220;vibe coding&amp;#8221; by AI researcher Andrej Karpathy, this emerging framework&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/vibe-coding-the-productivity-boom-hiding-massive-governance-risks/"&gt;Vibe Coding: The Productivity Boom Hiding Massive Governance Risks&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Vibe Coding: The Productivity Boom Hiding Massive Governance Risks||||||Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:00:49 +0000</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Taming LLM Sprawl: Why Enterprises Need an AI Gateway Now</title><description>&lt;img alt="&amp;quot;Taming LLM Sprawl: Why Enterprises Need an AI Gateway Now&amp;quot; featured image. Marbles being sorted" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/9fe04800-taming-llm-sprawl-gateway-1024x576.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;As AI becomes a cornerstone of digital transformation, IT leaders are under pressure to deliver innovation at scale while maintaining&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/taming-llm-sprawl-why-enterprises-need-an-ai-gateway-now/"&gt;Taming LLM Sprawl: Why Enterprises Need an AI Gateway Now&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Taming LLM Sprawl: Why Enterprises Need an AI Gateway Now||||||Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:00:20 +0000</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Future of Agentic Coding Is Multiplayer</title><description>&lt;img alt="Double exposure with people and network connections illustrating multiplayer AI engineering." class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/c2559637-connections-1024x576.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether you love it or hate it, by now most software developers have tried out some version of AI-coding tools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/the-future-of-agentic-coding-is-multiplayer/"&gt;The Future of Agentic Coding Is Multiplayer&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">The Future of Agentic Coding Is Multiplayer||||||Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:00:46 +0000</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>JFrog Upgrades AI Tooling, Governance To Speed up Software Delivery</title><description>&lt;img alt="" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="812" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/47472bd0-atlanta-2-1-1024x812.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artificial intelligence is no longer a mere curiosity inside enterprise developer stacks &amp;#8212; it&amp;#8217;s becoming the nervous system of how&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/jfrog-upgrades-ai-tooling-governance-to-speed-up-software-delivery/"&gt;JFrog Upgrades AI Tooling, Governance To Speed up Software Delivery&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">JFrog Upgrades AI Tooling, Governance To Speed up Software Delivery||||||Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:00:39 +0000</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SAP Patches Critical NetWeaver (CVSS Up to 10.0) and High-Severity S/4HANA Flaws</title><description>SAP on Tuesday released security updates to address multiple security flaws, including three critical vulnerabilities in SAP Netweaver that could result in code execution and the upload arbitrary files.
The vulnerabilities are listed below -

CVE-2025-42944 (CVSS score: 10.0) - A deserialization vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver that could allow an unauthenticated attacker to submit a malicious</description><guid isPermaLink="false">SAP Patches Critical NetWeaver (CVSS Up to 10.0) and High-Severity S/4HANA Flaws||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:33:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:33:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Adobe Commerce Flaw CVE-2025-54236 Lets Hackers Take Over Customer Accounts</title><description>Adobe has warned of a critical security flaw in its Commerce and Magento Open Source platforms that, if successfully exploited, could allow attackers to take control of customer accounts.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2025-54236 (aka SessionReaper), carries a CVSS score of 9.1 out of a maximum of 10.0. It has been described as an improper input validation flaw. Adobe said it's not aware of</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Adobe Commerce Flaw CVE-2025-54236 Lets Hackers Take Over Customer Accounts||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:38:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:38:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>China-Linked APT41 Hackers Target U.S. Trade Officials Amid 2025 Negotiations</title><description>The House Select Committee on China has formally issued an advisory warning of an "ongoing" series of highly targeted cyber espionage campaigns linked to the People's Republic of China (PRC) amid contentious U.S.–China trade talks.
"These campaigns seek to compromise organizations and individuals involved in U.S.-China trade policy and diplomacy, including U.S. government agencies, U.S. business</description><guid isPermaLink="false">China-Linked APT41 Hackers Target U.S. Trade Officials Amid 2025 Negotiations||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:23:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:23:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Watch Out for Salty2FA: New Phishing Kit Targeting US and EU Enterprises</title><description>Phishing-as-a-Service (PhaaS) platforms keep evolving, giving attackers faster and cheaper ways to break into corporate accounts. Now, researchers at ANY.RUN has uncovered a new entrant: Salty2FA, a phishing kit designed to bypass multiple two-factor authentication methods and slip past traditional defenses.&amp;nbsp;
Already spotted in campaigns across the US and EU, Salty2FA puts enterprises at</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Watch Out for Salty2FA: New Phishing Kit Targeting US and EU Enterprises||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:30:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:30:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Uber Shares Strategy for Controlling Risk in Monorepo Changes That Affect 3,000+ Microservices</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/news/2025/09/uber-monorepo-deployment/en/headerimage/generatedHeaderImage-1757488543470.jpg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Uber has published details on their approach to controlling rollouts of large-scale changes across monorepos that serve thousands of microservices, addressing one of the key challenges in continuous deployment at massive scale.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Claudio Masolo&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Uber Shares Strategy for Controlling Risk in Monorepo Changes That Affect 3,000+ Microservices||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 08:30:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Article: Engineering a Time Series Database Using Open Source: Rebuilding InfluxDB 3 in Apache Arrow and Rust</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/articles/timeseries-db-rust/en/headerimage/time-series-database-using-open-source-rebuilding-InfluxDB-in-apache-arrow-rust-header-1757058446201.jpg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;At times, to evolve your product, you need to rebuild it from scratch. The article provides the story behind the rewrite of InfluxDB from scratch using a different programming language - Rust - and stack -  Apache Flight, Data Fusion, Apache Arrow and Parquet (FDAP). It emphasises the benefits, as well as the mechanics behind its operation and the different versions of the product.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Paul Dix&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Article: Engineering a Time Series Database Using Open Source: Rebuilding InfluxDB 3 in Apache Arrow and Rust||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 09:00:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Time-Saving Guide for Service Providers: Automating vCISO and Compliance Services</title><description>Introduction
Managed service providers (MSPs) and managed security service providers (MSSPs) are under increasing pressure to deliver strong cybersecurity outcomes in a landscape marked by rising threats and evolving compliance requirements. At the same time, clients want better protection without managing cybersecurity themselves. Service providers must balance these growing demands with the</description><guid isPermaLink="false">The Time-Saving Guide for Service Providers: Automating vCISO and Compliance Services||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 14:55:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 14:55:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Honeycomb Hosted MCP Brings Observability Data into the IDE</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/news/2025/09/honeycomb-hosted-mcp/en/headerimage/header-1757190377363.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Honeycomb has launched its hosted Model Context Protocol (MCP), giving developers real-time access to observability data inside IDEs and AI tools like GitHub Copilot. Available as a managed service on AWS Marketplace, it removes the need for self-hosting and streamlines debugging by surfacing traces, metrics, and logs without context-switching.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Mark Silvester&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Honeycomb Hosted MCP Brings Observability Data into the IDE||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Clockwork’s FleetIQ Aims To Fix AI’s Costly Network Bottleneck</title><description>&lt;img alt="" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="683" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/51079913-donald-wu-mrgtyitjrna-unsplash-1024x683.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;GPUs are steadily getting faster, but as enterprises, neoclouds and the entrenched hyperscalers look to get more efficiency out of&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/clockworks-fleetiq-aims-to-fix-ais-costly-network-bottleneck/"&gt;Clockwork&amp;#8217;s FleetIQ Aims To Fix AI&amp;#8217;s Costly Network Bottleneck&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Clockwork’s FleetIQ Aims To Fix AI’s Costly Network Bottleneck||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:31 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple iPhone Air and iPhone 17 Feature A19 Chips With Spyware-Resistant Memory Safety</title><description>Apple on Tuesday revealed a new security feature called Memory Integrity Enforcement (MIE) that's built into its newly introduced iPhone models, including iPhone 17 and iPhone Air.
MIE, per the tech giant, offers "always-on memory safety protection" across critical attack surfaces such as the kernel and over 70 userland processes without sacrificing device performance by designing its A19 and</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Apple iPhone Air and iPhone 17 Feature A19 Chips With Spyware-Resistant Memory Safety||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:51:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:51:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Microsoft Fixes 80 Flaws — Including SMB PrivEsc and Azure CVSS 10.0 Bugs</title><description>Microsoft on Tuesday addressed a set of 80 security flaws in its software, including one vulnerability that has been disclosed as publicly known at the time of release.
Of the 80 vulnerabilities, eight are rated Critical and 72 are rated Important in severity. None of the shortcomings has been exploited in the wild as a zero-day. Like last month, 38 of the disclosed flaws are related to</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Microsoft Fixes 80 Flaws — Including SMB PrivEsc and Azure CVSS 10.0 Bugs||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:44:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:44:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Marketing on LinkedIn: What you need to know</title><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="MarTech what you need to know." class="attachment-large size-large wp-post-image" height="450" src="https://martech.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/WYNTK-personalize-800x450.png" style="margin-bottom: 15px;" width="800" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your guide to LinkedIn's tools, strategies and best practices. Updated with information on BrandLink videos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://martech.org/linkedin-the-marketers-guide/"&gt;Marketing on LinkedIn: What you need to know&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://martech.org"&gt;MarTech&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Marketing on LinkedIn: What you need to know||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:29:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Qodo Aware Is a ‘Second Brain’ for AI Coding Agents</title><description>&lt;img alt="A black and white brain." class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/bddc11e3-shawn-day-znkhpagiolm-unsplash-1024x576.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most AI coding agents use similar large language models (LLMs) under the hood. Where they differentiate is in their context&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/qodo-aware-is-a-second-brain-for-ai-coding-agents/"&gt;Qodo Aware Is a &amp;#8216;Second Brain&amp;#8217; for AI Coding Agents&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Qodo Aware Is a ‘Second Brain’ for AI Coding Agents||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:00:56 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CHILLYHELL macOS Backdoor and ZynorRAT RAT Threaten macOS, Windows, and Linux Systems</title><description>Cybersecurity researchers have discovered two new malware families, including a modular Apple macOS backdoor called CHILLYHELL and a Go-based remote access trojan (RAT) named ZynorRAT that can target both Windows and Linux systems.
According to an analysis from Jamf Threat Labs, ChillyHell is written in C++ and is developed for Intel architectures.
CHILLYHELL is the name assigned to a malware</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CHILLYHELL macOS Backdoor and ZynorRAT RAT Threaten macOS, Windows, and Linux Systems||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 18:34:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 18:34:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Presentation: The Data Backbone of LLM Systems</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/presentations/llm-data-code-model-prompt/en/mediumimage/paul-iusztin-medium-1756298947850.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drawing from his 8 years of experience in AI, Paul Iusztin breaks down the core components of a scalable architecture, emphasizing the importance of RAG. He shares practical patterns, including the Feature Training Inference architecture, and provides a detailed use case for creating a "Second Brain" AI assistant, covering everything from data pipelines to observability and agentic layers.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Paul Iusztin&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Presentation: The Data Backbone of LLM Systems||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:40:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Agents vs. Agentic AI: A Kubernetes Developer’s Guide</title><description>&lt;img alt="agents" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/77336087-aakash-dhage-plqw2qp-16k-unsplash-1024x576.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The distinction between AI agents and agentic AI has become critical for developers building containerized applications and microservices. While these&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/ai-agents-vs-agentic-ai-a-kubernetes-developers-guide/"&gt;AI Agents vs. Agentic AI: A Kubernetes Developer’s Guide&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">AI Agents vs. Agentic AI: A Kubernetes Developer’s Guide||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 14:00:36 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 14:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Health Care DSP DeepIntent Sells $637 Million Majority Stake To PE Firm Vitruvian Partners</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A dose of private equity is apparently just what the doctor ordered. On Tuesday, UK-based PE firm Vitruvian Partners made a $637 million strategic investment in DeepIntent, a health care-focused demand-side platform that specializes in helping pharma brands reach patients and providers using programmatic advertising. Although Vitruvian’s portfolio includes a bunch of software, consumer tech [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com/technology/health-care-dsp-deepintent-sells-637-million-majority-stake-to-pe-firm-vitruvian-partners/"&gt;Health Care DSP DeepIntent Sells $637 Million Majority Stake To PE Firm Vitruvian Partners&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com"&gt;AdExchanger&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Health Care DSP DeepIntent Sells $637 Million Majority Stake To PE Firm Vitruvian Partners||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 14:29:29 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 14:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>When Is MCP Actually Worth It?</title><description>&lt;img alt="Logo for the Model Context Protocol. This is a guide to when you should use MCP and when it&amp;#039;s unnecessary." class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/97717475-mcp-logo-2-1024x576.png" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Model Context Protocol (MCP) has emerged as an open standard for connecting AI agents with external data and services. Since&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/when-is-mcp-actually-worth-it/"&gt;When Is MCP Actually Worth It?&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">When Is MCP Actually Worth It?||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:00:08 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Chinese APT Deploys EggStreme Fileless Malware to Breach Philippine Military Systems</title><description>An advanced persistent threat (APT) group from China has been attributed to the compromise of a Philippines-based military company using a previously undocumented fileless malware framework called EggStreme.
"This multi-stage toolset achieves persistent, low-profile espionage by injecting malicious code directly into memory and leveraging DLL sideloading to execute payloads," Bitdefender</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Chinese APT Deploys EggStreme Fileless Malware to Breach Philippine Military Systems||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 21:16:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 21:16:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Work With Local AI in the Zed IDE</title><description>&lt;img alt="" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="683" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/81587bd6-tim-mossholder-qvwngmotbik-unsplash-1024x683.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those who believe AI is a great way to not only learn a new programming language but also to&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/how-to-work-with-local-ai-in-the-zed-ide/"&gt;How To Work With Local AI in the Zed IDE&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">How To Work With Local AI in the Zed IDE||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:00:44 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:00:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Five Steps to Build AI Agents that Actually Deliver Business Results</title><description>&lt;img alt="" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="683" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/ea8fc2db-thought-catalog-uk78i6vk3sc-unsplash-1024x683.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the age of digital transformation, businesses have faced a trade-off: Speed and scale often come at the cost of&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/five-steps-to-build-ai-agents-that-actually-deliver-business-results/"&gt;Five Steps to Build AI Agents that Actually Deliver Business Results&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Five Steps to Build AI Agents that Actually Deliver Business Results||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:00:37 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How the News Networks Covered the Charlie Kirk Shooting</title><description>Kirk was speaking at a student event in Utah when the shooting occurred.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">How the News Networks Covered the Charlie Kirk Shooting||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 19:12:09 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 19:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Is Hearst Buying So Many Texas Newspapers?</title><description>In this edition of On Background, the 138-year-old media giant might be the only one still trying to get into the news business these days.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Why Is Hearst Buying So Many Texas Newspapers?||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 20:28:30 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 20:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Thinking Machines Lab wants to make AI models more consistent</title><description>In a blog post shared Wednesday, Mira Murati's startup offered a rare glimpse into some of work its doing to improve AI models.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Thinking Machines Lab wants to make AI models more consistent||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 21:30:11 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 21:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Vibe Coding Fails Enterprise Reality Check</title><description>&lt;img alt="" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="683" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/b992c0c9-philip-oroni-_v-asnc8cve-unsplash-1024x683.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The promise is irresistible: Describe what you want in plain English, and AI spits out working code. This &amp;#8220;vibe coding&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/vibe-coding-fails-enterprise-reality-check/"&gt;Vibe Coding Fails Enterprise Reality Check&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Vibe Coding Fails Enterprise Reality Check||||||Wed, 10 Sep 2025 23:00:06 +0000</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 23:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Perplexity reportedly raised $200M at $20B valuation</title><description>The AI-powered search startup's valuation jumped from $18 billion two months earlier.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Perplexity reportedly raised $200M at $20B valuation||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 03:59:10 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 03:59:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>For SSPs, What’s In A Name?; A Pillar Of The Community</title><description>&lt;p&gt;SSPs aren't thrilled by TTD characterizing them as "resellers"; Amazon DSP just announced a new partnership to sell Netflix inventory; and pharma brands will be subject to stricter regulations, per the FDA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com/daily-news-roundup/thursday-11092025/"&gt;For SSPs, What’s In A Name?; A Pillar Of The Community&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com"&gt;AdExchanger&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">For SSPs, What’s In A Name?; A Pillar Of The Community||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 04:03:19 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 04:03:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>In a World of AI Slop, The Next Brand Fight Is About Staying Real</title><description>A shark wears blue Nikes. The pope sports a white puffer coat. Jesus rides a giant shrimp. These bizarre, viral images have come to define the current era of AI [&amp;hellip;]</description><guid isPermaLink="false">In a World of AI Slop, The Next Brand Fight Is About Staying Real||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 06:00:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Klarna CMO Says AI Is Driving Marketing Strategy as It Makes Trading Debut</title><description>The Swedish buy now, pay later firm made a strong trading debut with shares climbing nearly 15%</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Klarna CMO Says AI Is Driving Marketing Strategy as It Makes Trading Debut||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 06:00:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AsyncRAT Exploits ConnectWise ScreenConnect to Steal Credentials and Crypto</title><description>Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed details of a new campaign that leverages ConnectWise ScreenConnect, a legitimate Remote Monitoring and Management (RMM) software, to deliver a fleshless loader that drops a remote access trojan (RAT) called AsyncRAT to steal sensitive data from compromised hosts.
"The attacker used ScreenConnect to gain remote access, then executed a layered VBScript and</description><guid isPermaLink="false">AsyncRAT Exploits ConnectWise ScreenConnect to Steal Credentials and Crypto||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 11:32:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 11:32:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI’s gpt-realtime Enables Production-Ready Voice Agents with End-to-End Speech Processing</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/news/2025/09/openai-gpt-realtime/en/headerimage/GettyImages-1138451118-1757517374254.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;OpenAI launched gpt-realtime and the Realtime API, enabling production-ready AI voice agents with end-to-end speech processing, lower latency, and natural speech delivery. New features include SIP phone support, image input, MCP server integration, and improved safeguards. Early adopters like Zillow and T-Mobile are testing real-time customer service and search use cases.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Hien Luu&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">OpenAI’s gpt-realtime Enables Production-Ready Voice Agents with End-to-End Speech Processing||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 08:00:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fake Madgicx Plus and SocialMetrics Extensions Are Hijacking Meta Business Accounts</title><description>Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed two new campaigns that are serving fake browser extensions using malicious ads and fake websites to steal sensitive data.
The malvertising campaign, per Bitdefender, is designed to push fake "Meta Verified" browser extensions named SocialMetrics Pro that claim to unlock the blue check badge for Facebook and Instagram profiles. At least 37 malicious ads</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Fake Madgicx Plus and SocialMetrics Extensions Are Hijacking Meta Business Accounts||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 14:35:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 14:35:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Azure Service Groups Enter Public Preview Offering New Abstraction Layer for Resource Management</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/news/2025/09/azure-service-groups-preview/en/headerimage/generatedHeaderImage-1757411283972.jpg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft has launched Azure Service Groups in public preview, a new feature designed to simplify resource management and administration. Acting as a flexible, tenant-level container, Service Groups allow users to organize Azure resources from anywhere within their tenant without affecting RBAC or policy inheritance.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Steef-Jan Wiggers&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Azure Service Groups Enter Public Preview Offering New Abstraction Layer for Resource Management||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cracking the Boardroom Code: Helping CISOs Speak the Language of Business</title><description>CISOs know their field. They understand the threat landscape. They understand how to build a strong and cost-effective security stack. They understand how to staff out their organization. They understand the intricacies of compliance. They understand what it takes to reduce risk. Yet one question comes up again and again in our conversations with these security leaders: how do I make the impact</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Cracking the Boardroom Code: Helping CISOs Speak the Language of Business||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:03:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:03:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>SonicWall SSL VPN Flaw and Misconfigurations Actively Exploited by Akira Ransomware Hackers</title><description>Threat actors affiliated with the Akira ransomware group have continued to target SonicWall devices for initial access.
Cybersecurity firm Rapid7 said it observed a spike in intrusions involving SonicWall appliances over the past month, particularly following reports about renewed Akira ransomware activity since late July 2025.
SonicWall subsequently revealed the SSL VPN activity aimed at its</description><guid isPermaLink="false">SonicWall SSL VPN Flaw and Misconfigurations Actively Exploited by Akira Ransomware Hackers||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:03:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:03:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Lessons Learned from Growing from Junior to Staff and Beyond</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/news/2025/09/growing-junior-staff/en/headerimage/generatedHeaderImage-1757449109449.jpg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bruno Rey suggested thinking about career growth in circles: self, team, company, and customers. Success comes from understanding broader impacts, embracing compromise, and acting fast, especially in startups. He advised seeking mentors for honest feedback, being open to unexpected or crisis-driven opportunities, and thriving in change with an anti-fragile mindset.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Ben Linders&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Lessons Learned from Growing from Junior to Staff and Beyond||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 11:03:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 11:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Week of September 1 Cable News Ratings: CNN Starts the Month With Gains</title><description>Fox News was the most-watched cable news network.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Week of September 1 Cable News Ratings: CNN Starts the Month With Gains||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 11:50:02 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 11:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Presentation: Thinking Like an Architect</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/presentations/architecture-best-practices/en/mediumimage/gregor-hohpe-medium-1756297866716.jpg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gregor Hohpe explains the role of a modern architect as an "IQ booster" for the organization. He discusses how to master communication and decision-making by riding the "Architect Elevator" to connect with all levels. He shares practical strategies for using metaphors, models, and understanding resistance to drive alignment and build resilient systems.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Gregor Hohpe&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Presentation: Thinking Like an Architect||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 12:08:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 12:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The latest AI-powered martech news and releases</title><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="" class="attachment-large size-large wp-post-image" height="457" src="https://martech.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/roundup999-800x457.jpg" style="margin-bottom: 15px;" width="800" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OpenAI just upped its burn rate for the next couple of years from $35 billion to $115 billion. That's a heck of a rounding error.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://martech.org/the-latest-ai-powered-martech-news-and-releases/"&gt;The latest AI-powered martech news and releases&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://martech.org"&gt;MarTech&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">The latest AI-powered martech news and releases||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 12:38:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 12:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple’s new live translation feature for AirPods won’t be available in the EU at launch</title><description>On its official page detailing the features available on iOS 26, the company said EU residents or those with EU Apple IDs won't be able to use live translation, which is powered by Apple Intelligence and will also be coming to AirPods 4 and AirPods Pro 2.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Apple’s new live translation feature for AirPods won’t be available in the EU at launch||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 12:53:03 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 12:53:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How Bill Gates’s fellowship program is adapting to global uncertainty</title><description>As Breakthrough Energy Fellows welcomes a new cohort of 22 startups, it is also diversifying its portfolio to include more global founders.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">How Bill Gates’s fellowship program is adapting to global uncertainty||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>MSNBC Drops Matthew Dowd After Controversial Comments</title><description>MSNBC president Rebecca Kutler issued a statement saying his comments following the Charlie Kirk shooting were 'unacceptable.'</description><guid isPermaLink="false">MSNBC Drops Matthew Dowd After Controversial Comments||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 13:10:24 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 13:10:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Content Creators Can Now Access YouTube’s Multi-Language Audio Feature</title><description>YouTube is also piloting a feature allowing creators to add localized thumbnails.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Content Creators Can Now Access YouTube’s Multi-Language Audio Feature||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 13:27:01 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 13:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Transaction IDs Can Reduce Auction Duplication, But A Fair Market Requires Some Duplication</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Transaction IDs (TIDs) have been the topic du jour on LinkedIn and Twitter – and for good reason. These OpenRTB identifiers let buyers deduplicate the cluttered bidstream.  The entire TID debate has a clear subtitle: “Duplication is waste.”  However, legitimate auction duplication provides benefits for publishers. And the use of TIDs drives publishers’ fears around [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com/the-sell-sider/transaction-ids-can-reduce-auction-duplication-but-a-fair-market-requires-some-duplication/"&gt;Transaction IDs Can Reduce Auction Duplication, But A Fair Market Requires Some Duplication&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.adexchanger.com"&gt;AdExchanger&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Transaction IDs Can Reduce Auction Duplication, But A Fair Market Requires Some Duplication||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 13:38:11 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 13:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Report: Paramount Skydance Looks to Acquire Warner Bros. Discovery</title><description>According to the report, Paramount Skydance is preparing a bid for all of WBD.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Report: Paramount Skydance Looks to Acquire Warner Bros. Discovery||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 14:25:22 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 14:25:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Box CEO Aaron Levie on AI’s ‘era of context’</title><description>Box released a new set of AI tools at its Boxworks conference on Thursday, filling out CEO Aaron Levie's vision for an AI-led transformation of the enterprise.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Box CEO Aaron Levie on AI’s ‘era of context’||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 14:36:31 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 14:36:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Kids in the UK are hacking their own schools for dares and notoriety</title><description>Kids are making a mark in the U.K.'s cybersecurity arena, and not in the way their parents want them to.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Kids in the UK are hacking their own schools for dares and notoriety||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 14:42:14 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 14:42:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Crayola&amp;#8217;s Victoria Lozano on Why Creativity Is Our Greatest Skill in an AI-Driven World</title><description>Creativity is a life skill that prepares people for whatever lies ahead.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Crayola&amp;#8217;s Victoria Lozano on Why Creativity Is Our Greatest Skill in an AI-Driven World||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 14:44:10 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 14:44:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Senator Wyden Urges FTC to Probe Microsoft for Ransomware-Linked Cybersecurity Negligence</title><description>U.S. Senator Ron Wyden has called on the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) to probe Microsoft and hold it responsible for what he called "gross cybersecurity negligence" that enabled ransomware attacks on U.S. critical infrastructure, including against healthcare networks.
"Without timely action, Microsoft's culture of negligent cybersecurity, combined with its de facto monopolization of the</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Senator Wyden Urges FTC to Probe Microsoft for Ransomware-Linked Cybersecurity Negligence||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 20:21:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 20:21:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>HBO Max is going to get more expensive, Warner Bros. Discovery CEO says</title><description>Zaslav also said that the streaming service's crackdown on passwords will be coming in the future.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">HBO Max is going to get more expensive, Warner Bros. Discovery CEO says||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 14:59:02 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 14:59:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Stop Building Super Agents; Build Effective AI Teams Instead</title><description>&lt;img alt="" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="684" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/8c5be5f4-christina-wocintechchat-com-kzu0ezl9tjo-unsplash-1024x684.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;While companies worldwide rush to adopt agentic AI for efficiency, data indicates that nearly half of all deployments will fail&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/stop-building-super-agents-build-effective-ai-teams-instead/"&gt;Stop Building Super Agents; Build Effective AI Teams Instead&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Stop Building Super Agents; Build Effective AI Teams Instead||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 15:00:40 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 15:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Humanoids, AVs, and what’s next in AI hardware with Waabi and Apptronik at TechCrunch Disrupt 2025</title><description>TechCrunch Disrupt 2025 is bringing together 10,000+ startup and VC leaders for three days of bold ideas, groundbreaking tech, and future-shaping conversations.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Humanoids, AVs, and what’s next in AI hardware with Waabi and Apptronik at TechCrunch Disrupt 2025||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 15:02:50 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 15:02:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Google Pixel 10 Adds C2PA Support to Verify AI-Generated Media Authenticity</title><description>Google on Tuesday announced that its new Google Pixel 10 phones support the Coalition for Content Provenance and Authenticity (C2PA) standard out of the box to verify the origin and history of digital content.
To that end, support for C2PA's Content Credentials has been added to Pixel Camera and Google Photos apps for Android. The move, Google said, is designed to further digital media</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Google Pixel 10 Adds C2PA Support to Verify AI-Generated Media Authenticity||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 20:33:00 +0530</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 20:33:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Google is shutting down Tables, its Airtable rival</title><description>Google Tables, a work-tracking tool and competitor to the popular spreadsheet-database hybrid Airtable, is shutting down. The app will not be supported after December 16, 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Google is shutting down Tables, its Airtable rival||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 15:15:23 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 15:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>France says Apple notified victims of new spyware attacks</title><description>The French government says Apple sent out threat notifications to customers alerting them to spyware attacks earlier in September.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">France says Apple notified victims of new spyware attacks||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 15:32:05 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 15:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gmail makes it easier to track upcoming package deliveries</title><description>Google also announced on that it's updating the Promotion category in Gmail to allow users to sort by "most relevant" promotion emails.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Gmail makes it easier to track upcoming package deliveries||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How Distributed Postgres Solves Cloud’s High-Availability Problem</title><description>&lt;img alt="&amp;quot;How Distributed Postgres Solves Cloud&amp;#039;s High Availability Problem&amp;quot; featured image" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/5da24611-distributed-postgres-cloud-ha-1024x576.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application availability and downtime are concerns no organization can afford to overlook. While the hard numbers vary by use case,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/how-distributed-postgres-solves-clouds-high-availability-problem/"&gt;How Distributed Postgres Solves Cloud&amp;#8217;s High-Availability Problem&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">How Distributed Postgres Solves Cloud’s High-Availability Problem||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:00:03 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dispelling Myths of Open Source Complexity With Apache Iceberg</title><description>&lt;img alt="People in a raft approaching an iceberg." class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/d44f92da-iceberg12-1024x576.jpeg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;While everyone agrees on the importance of an AI-ready data foundation, there&amp;#8217;s often a disconnect on the right tools for&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/dispelling-myths-of-open-source-complexity-with-apache-iceberg/"&gt;Dispelling Myths of Open Source Complexity With Apache Iceberg&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Dispelling Myths of Open Source Complexity With Apache Iceberg||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:00:07 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Nielsen and Warner Bros. Discovery Sign Multi-Year Deal</title><description>WBD will utilize Nielsen’s big data + panel as currency for ad sales transactions, including its upfronts and beyond.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Nielsen and Warner Bros. Discovery Sign Multi-Year Deal||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:13:07 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Understanding Log Events: Why Context Is Key</title><description>&lt;img alt="The five W questions: what, who, when, where, why." class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/a5de9851-fivews-1024x576.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Editor&amp;#8217;s Note: This article is an excerpt from Chapter 1 of The Manning book &amp;#8220;Logging Best Practices: A Practical Guide&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/understanding-log-events-why-context-is-key/"&gt;Understanding Log Events: Why Context Is Key&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Understanding Log Events: Why Context Is Key||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:00:31 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>FTC launches inquiry into AI chatbot companions from Meta, OpenAI, and others</title><description>The federal consumer regulator seeks to learn about how AI companies evaluate the safety of their chatbots.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">FTC launches inquiry into AI chatbot companions from Meta, OpenAI, and others||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:06:15 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:06:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Google DeepMind Launches EmbeddingGemma, an Open Model for On-Device Embeddings</title><description>&lt;img src="https://res.infoq.com/news/2025/09/embedding-gemma/en/headerimage/header+%2850%29-1757614506140.jpg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google DeepMind has introduced EmbeddingGemma, a 308M parameter open embedding model designed to run efficiently on-device. The model aims to make applications like retrieval-augmented generation (RAG), semantic search, and text classification accessible without the need for a server or internet connection.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;i&gt;By Robert Krzaczyński&lt;/i&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Google DeepMind Launches EmbeddingGemma, an Open Model for On-Device Embeddings||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>VC leaders from 01 Advisors take the Builders Stage at TechCrunch Disrupt 2025 to share the scaling playbook</title><description>Adam Bain, Dick Costolo, and David Fischer — the operators behind Twitter and Meta’s growth — reunite at Disrupt 2025.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">VC leaders from 01 Advisors take the Builders Stage at TechCrunch Disrupt 2025 to share the scaling playbook||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:40:00 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Justice Department sues Uber for allegedly discriminating against people with disabilities</title><description>It's the latest in a long line of criticism — and action against — about the company's treatment of people with physical disabilities.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Justice Department sues Uber for allegedly discriminating against people with disabilities||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:43:35 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>3 Ways Security Teams Can Tame Autonomous AI Agents</title><description>&lt;img alt="A collage showcasing various aspects of cybersecurity with digital locks and cityscape in the background." class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/a5b09244-aisecurity-1024x576.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Security professionals understand the dangers of internal threats: adversaries or individuals with harmful objectives who operate from within the enterprise,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/3-ways-security-teams-can-tame-autonomous-ai-agents/"&gt;3 Ways Security Teams Can Tame Autonomous AI Agents&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">3 Ways Security Teams Can Tame Autonomous AI Agents||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 19:00:14 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 19:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk’s Boring Company suspends work on Vegas airport tunnel after ‘crushing injury’</title><description>A worker had to be rescued by the local fire department but is reportedly stable. Dozens of Boring Company workers have been injured over the years in Vegas.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Elon Musk’s Boring Company suspends work on Vegas airport tunnel after ‘crushing injury’||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 19:28:23 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 19:28:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Agentic Web: How AI Agents Are Shaping the Web’s Future</title><description>&lt;img alt="agentic web" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/c5c8dbb3-rubidium-beach-w2-krix1ztq-unsplash-1024x576.jpg" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his new memoir, This Is For Everyone, Sir Tim Berners-Lee makes it clear he thinks AI agents are the&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/the-agentic-web-how-ai-agents-are-shaping-the-webs-future/"&gt;The Agentic Web: How AI Agents Are Shaping the Web’s Future&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">The Agentic Web: How AI Agents Are Shaping the Web’s Future||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 20:00:25 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 20:00:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla’s robotaxi plans for Nevada move forward with testing permit</title><description>Tesla can now test its autonomous vehicle technology on public streets in Nevada, but it still has steps to take if it wants to offer paid rides like in Austin, Texas.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Tesla’s robotaxi plans for Nevada move forward with testing permit||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 20:20:24 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 20:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How the EU’s Cyber Act Burdens Lone Open Source Developers</title><description>&lt;img alt="At the Open Source Summit Europe, Christopher &amp;quot;Crob&amp;quot; Robinson of the Open Source Security Foundation highlighted concerns about how these regulations could impact open source maintainers" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="576" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/834e233f-for-thumbnail-2-1024x576.png" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;What&amp;#8217;s to come of open source software with the coming requirements that come with the Cyber Resiliency Act, now in&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/how-the-eus-cyber-act-burdens-lone-open-source-developers/"&gt;How the EU’s Cyber Act Burdens Lone Open Source Developers&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">How the EU’s Cyber Act Burdens Lone Open Source Developers||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:00:13 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:00:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The music industry is broken: OpenWav’s new app aims to change that</title><description>OpenWav is building a direct-to-fan platform for music artists that lets them keep more of the profits.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">The music industry is broken: OpenWav’s new app aims to change that||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:07:23 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:07:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How Maintainer Burnout Is Causing a Kubernetes Security Disaster</title><description>&lt;img alt="" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" height="768" src="https://cdn.thenewstack.io/media/2025/09/0c405f89-eso-1024x768.png" style="display: block; margin: auto; margin-bottom: 20px;" width="1024" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like far too many open source projects, we don&amp;#8217;t give Kubernetes External Secrets Operator (ESO) enough attention. We just assume&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io/how-maintainer-burnout-is-causing-a-kubernetes-security-disaster/"&gt;How Maintainer Burnout Is Causing a Kubernetes Security Disaster&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://thenewstack.io"&gt;The New Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">How Maintainer Burnout Is Causing a Kubernetes Security Disaster||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:00:21 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple’s latest iPhone security feature just made life more difficult for spyware makers</title><description>Apple launched a new security feature for iPhone 17 and iPhone Air designed to reduce the effect of memory corruption bugs, and in turn make spyware and zero-days more difficult to hack into iPhones.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">Apple’s latest iPhone security feature just made life more difficult for spyware makers||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:00:46 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI secures Microsoft’s blessing to transition its for-profit arm</title><description>OpenAI and Microsoft say they reached a non-binding agreement on a revised partnership.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">OpenAI secures Microsoft’s blessing to transition its for-profit arm||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:18:29 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:18:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>A California bill that would regulate AI companion chatbots is close to becoming law</title><description>SB 243 passed the California Senate on Thursday and heads to Gov. Newsom's desk. If SB 243 is enacted, California would become the first state to require operators to implement safety protocols for AI companions and hold companies legally accountable if their chatbots fail to meet those standards.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">A California bill that would regulate AI companion chatbots is close to becoming law||||||Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:23:09 +0000</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Chef's Deal Restaurant Equipment</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Chef's%2520Deal%2520Restaurant%2520Equipment?page=1</link><description>Nashville, Sept.  11, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Nashville, Tennessee - September 11, 2025  -    Chef's Deal, a leading commercial kitchen and restaurant supply company based in Nashville, Tennessee,...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Chef's%2520Deal%2520Restaurant%2520Equipment?page=1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:51:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Next Technology Holding Inc.</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Next%2520Technology%2520Holding%2520Inc§?page=1</link><description>CHEYENNE, Wyoming, Sept.  11, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) --  Next Technology Holding Inc. (“NXTT” or the “Company”) (NASDAQ: NXTT), a technology firm committed to delivering AI-enabled software...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Next%2520Technology%2520Holding%2520Inc§?page=1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:55:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Opus One Gold Corporation Inc.</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Opus%2520One%2520Gold%2520Corporation?page=1</link><description>MONTREAL, Sept.  11, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Opus One Gold Corporation (OOR: TSXV) (“Opus One Gold” or the “Company”), announces the grant under the Company’s stock option plan of 5,400,000 stock...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Opus%2520One%2520Gold%2520Corporation?page=1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 19:00:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Geotab Inc.</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Geotab%2520Inc§?page=1</link><description>SYDNEY, Sept.  11, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Geotab Inc. (“Geotab”), today announced it has achieved a new company milestone, surpassing 5 million connected vehicle subscriptions worldwide. This rapid...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Geotab%2520Inc§?page=1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 19:00:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Faruqi &amp; Faruqi LLP</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Faruqi%2520&amp;%2520Faruqi%2520LLP</link><description>Faruqi &amp; Faruqi, LLP Securities Litigation Partner James (Josh) Wilson Encourages Investors Who Suffered Losses In Alto To Contact Him Directly To Discuss Their Options  If you purchased or...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Faruqi%2520&amp;%2520Faruqi%2520LLP</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 19:18:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Faruqi &amp; Faruqi LLP</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Faruqi%2520&amp;%2520Faruqi%2520LLP?page=1</link><description>Faruqi &amp; Faruqi, LLP Securities Litigation Partner James (Josh) Wilson Encourages Investors Who Suffered Losses In Alto To Contact Him Directly To Discuss Their Options  If you purchased or...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Faruqi%2520&amp;%2520Faruqi%2520LLP?page=1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 19:18:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>The Rosen Law Firm PA</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/The%2520Rosen%2520Law%2520Firm%2520PA?page=1</link><description>NEW YORK, Sept.  11, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) --     WHY: Rosen Law Firm, a global investor rights law firm, continues to investigate potential securities claims on behalf of shareholders of KBR, Inc....</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/The%2520Rosen%2520Law%2520Firm%2520PA?page=1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 19:24:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Halper Sadeh LLC</title><link>https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Halper%2520Sadeh%2520LLC?page=1</link><description>NEW YORK, Sept.  11, 2025  (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Halper Sadeh LLC, an investor rights law firm, is investigating the following companies for potential violations of the federal securities laws and/or...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.globenewswire.com/en/search/organization/Halper%2520Sadeh%2520LLC?page=1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 19:31:00 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>